<tweet>
	The Muppets: The Pig with the Froggy Tattoo teaser trailer http://t.co/7jCsO6U1
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Killing Bono starring Ben Barnes, Krysten Ritter and Charlie Cox http://t.co/O28qmAbc
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for We Bought a Zoo starring Matt Damon, Scarlett Johansson and Thomas Haden Church http://t.co/yezHkKjv
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			We Bought a Zoo
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	J.J. Abrams confirmed to direct Star Trek 2 http://t.co/4mMMDBV (via @fantasysf)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Star Trek 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Theatrical trailer for Breaking Dawn Part 1 starring Kristen Stewart, Robert Pattinson and Taylor Lautner http://t.co/gxgAEqH
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Breaking Dawn Part 1
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @science: Microbiologists and immunologists helped create bacteria billboard to promote Contagion movie. http://t.co/fZC0MMi
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Contagion
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Contagion wins weekend box office http://t.co/P5jKyoZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Contagion
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First One for the Money movie poster revealed with  Katherine Heigl as Stephanie Plum http://t.co/nFh4WcA (via @books)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			One for the Money
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Conan the Barbarian screenwriter shares what it is like to have a movie flop. http://t.co/DwqxNMR (via @writerswrite)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Conan the Barbarian
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Blackthorn starring Sam Shepard, Eduardo Noriega and Stephen Rea http://t.co/xNkfcHI
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Blackthorn
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Help wins box office for third consecutive weekend http://t.co/VT1Gu5e
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Help
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Theatrical Trailer for Melancholia starring Kirsten Dunst, Alexander Skarsgard and Kiefer Sutherland http://t.co/u9Z40MR
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Melancholia
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	American Pie cast reunited for American Reunion movie http://t.co/LxPJTwu
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			American Reunion
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Greening of Whitney Brown starring Sammi Hanratty, Brooke Shields and Aidan Quinn http://t.co/ljAOYRa
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Greening of Whitney Brown
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You can also get movie updates from Watchers Watch on Facebook http://t.co/vAWr1K9
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Deadline says some hardcore Star Wars object to changes in Blu-ray saga http://t.co/uUczjAU
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Star Wars
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Second Trailer for Killer Elite starring Jason Statham, Clive Owen and Robert De Niro http://t.co/TfQ8sOs
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Killer Elite
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Seven Days in Utopia starring Robert Duvall, Lucas Black and Melissa Leo http://t.co/nv3zPU8 (via @golf)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Seven Days in Utopia
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Matt Damon talks Contagion http://t.co/N7o4iA4
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Contagion
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Ides of March starring Ryan Gosling, George Clooney, Paul Giamatti http://t.co/U4N5dKq
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Ides of March
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser trailer for The Hunger Games http://t.co/iqUUGcW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Hunger Games
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Help wins box office for second consecutive weekend http://t.co/Aqvx0iU
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Help
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video tour of real life Up house built by Bangerter Homes http://t.co/i4cO3mx
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Up
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Rum Diary, stars Johnny Depp, Amber Heard and Aaron Eckhart - adaption of Hunter S. Thompson story http://t.co/dhNXiOB
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Rum Diary
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Fireflies in the Garden starring Julia Roberts, Ryan Reynolds, Willem Dafoe and Emily Watson http://t.co/lo0A81U
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Fireflies in the Garden
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Lady starring Michelle Yeoh and David Thewlis http://t.co/RFrk8MN
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Lady
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Help wins weekend box office - defeats Conan the Barbarian and Fright Night. http://t.co/eDtph7O
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Help
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Conan the Barbarian
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Fright Night
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Harry Potter director and screenwriter to bring Stephen King's The Stand to the big screen http://t.co/7oc15wR (via @writerswrite)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pixar announces two new original film projects at D23 expo. No titles yet for these film concepts. http://t.co/MLfKJ0u (via @watcherswatch)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Machine Gun Preacher starring Gerard Butler, Michelle Monaghan and Michael Shannon http://t.co/PWhWYR4
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Machine Gun Preacher
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Tanner Hall starring Rooney Mara, Amy Sedaris, Tom Everett Scott and Brie Larson http://t.co/cHb08kH
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Tanner Hall
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Carnage starring Jodie Foster, Kate Winslet, Christoph Waltz and John C. Reilly http://t.co/kL9MGVr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Carnage
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Underworld Awakening starring Kate Beckinsale and Michael Ealy http://t.co/5lgURAw (via @fantasysf)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Underworld Awakening
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Summit releases new stills from Breaking Dawn Part 1 http://t.co/ero1Z05
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Breaking Dawn
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Page Eight starring Rachel Weisz, Bill Nighy and Michael Gambon http://t.co/tknZOh2
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Page Eight
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ridley Scott to write and direct new Blade Runner film http://t.co/fHy2G8I (via @fantasysf)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Blade Runner
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Puncture starring Chris Evans and Vinessa Shaw http://t.co/ysD8prw
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Puncture
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Official teaser trailer for The Woman In Black starring Radcliffe, Ciaran Hinds and Janet McTeer http://t.co/CUuUxxm
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Woman In Black
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	U.S. Postal Service to launch Pixar stamps on August 19. http://t.co/qnQVuxI
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rise of the Planet of the Apes was the number one movie this weekend for the second consecutive weekend. http://t.co/NlaAi82
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Rise of the Planet of the Apes
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lionsgate announces film date for Catching Fire, second book in Hunger Game series http://t.co/T0FzwkZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Catching Fire
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mike Meyers signs on for Austin Powers 4 http://t.co/J2AgJaB
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Austin Powers 4
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Father of Invention starring Kevin Spacey, Camilla Belle and Heather Graham http://t.co/7HArMEg
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Father of Invention
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Swinging With the Finkels starring Mandy Moore, Martin Freeman and Melissa George http://t.co/9mNL87e
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Swinging With the Finkels
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Footloose starring Julianne Hough, Kenny Wormald and Dennis Quaid http://t.co/XffTBC3
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Footloose
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for 50/50 starring Joseph Gordon-Levitt, Seth Rogen and Anna Kendrick http://bit.ly/ruE2j9
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			50/50
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for A Very Harold and Kumar 3D Christmas starring John Cho, Kal Penn and Neil Patrick Harris http://bit.ly/oVvYD8
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			A Very Harold and Kumar 3D Christmas
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Odd Life of Timothy Green starring Jennifer Garner and Joel Edgerton http://bit.ly/pe3UGF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Odd Life of Timothy Green
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WPXI gets great footage of The Dark Knight Rises fight scene filmed in Oakland http://bit.ly/pixbMj
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Dark Knight Rises
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Sitter starring Jonah Hill, Ari Graynor and Max Records http://bit.ly/q6HDbf
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Sitter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Caller starring Rachelle Lefevre and Stephen Moyer http://bit.ly/n5xwKL
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Caller
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Darkest Hour starring Emile Hirsch, Olivia Thirlby and Max Minghella http://bit.ly/pHhRcT
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Darkest Hour
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New still from The Amazing Spider-Man: Peter Parker and Gwen http://bit.ly/oQt4Op
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Amazing Spider-Man
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Dirty Girl starring Juno Temple, Jeremy Dozier, Milla Jovovich and Tim McGraw http://bit.ly/ruK6EB
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Dirty Girl
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Update: Cowboys & Aliens overtakes Smurfs to win weekend box office. http://bit.ly/nFSmdj
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Cowboys & Aliens
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Smurfs
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser Trailer for The Avengers starring Chris Evans, Robert Downey, Jr. and Chris Hemsworth http://bit.ly/qynkIM
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Avengers
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Tower Heist starring Ben Stiller, Eddie Murphy, and Gabourey Sidibe http://bit.ly/qKlKQM
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Tower Heist
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Red Tails starring Terrence Howard, Cuba Gooding Jr. and Bryan Cranston http://bit.ly/oSNUkv
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Red Tails
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New posters for The Muppets movie unveiled http://bit.ly/oyAkl4
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Muppets
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Funny or Die: Steve Carrell hates the promotional posters for Crazy Stupid Love http://bit.ly/oLiK1l
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Crazy Stupid Love
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Director Steven Spielberg talks being a Comic-Con virgin, favorite costumes http://bit.ly/nRXMUH
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Extended clip from Fright Night starring David Tennant and Anton Yelchin http://bit.ly/p2Tzoa
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Fright Night
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Andrew Garfield makes surprise appearance at Comic-Con, gives emotional speech about Spider-Man http://bit.ly/ocBsjG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Spider-Man
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Haywire starring Gina Carano, Michael Fassbender and Channing Tatum http://bit.ly/nm3JRq
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Haywire
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for In Time starring Justin Timberlake, Amanda Seyfried, Olivia Wilde and Matt Bomer http://bit.ly/o4VM8Q
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			In Time
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Dream House starring Daniel Craig, Rachel Weisz and Naomi Watts http://bit.ly/oaUZ3P
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Dream House
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Attack the Block starring Jodie Whittaker, John Boyega and Alex Esmail http://bit.ly/roqoBq
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Attack the Block
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser trailer for The Amazing Spider-Man http://bit.ly/qVOouP
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Amazing Spider-Man
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser trailer for The Dark Knight Rises starring Christian Bale http://bit.ly/p3rJQy
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Dark Knight Rises
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Blitz starring Jason Statham http://bit.ly/oegf7N
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Blitz
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Pirates: Band of Misfits starring the voices of Hugh Grant, Jeremy Piven and Salma Hayek http://bit.ly/qYkVQq
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Pirates: Band of Misfits
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Contagion starring Gwyneth Paltrow, Matt Damon, Kate Winslet and Jude Law http://bit.ly/rsr4vY
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Contagion
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser trailer for John Carter starring Taylor Kitsch and Lynn Collins http://bit.ly/nX803r
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			John Carter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Thing prequel starring Mary Elizabeth Winstead and Joel Edgerton http://bit.ly/nWB9dJ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Thing prequel
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Myth of the American Sleepover http://bit.ly/qc3k0P
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Myth of the American Sleepover
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Arthur Christmas starring the voices of James McAvoy, Hugh Laurie and Jim Broadbent http://bit.ly/pD0S4K
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Arthur Christmas
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First poster for The Dark Knight Rises unveiled http://bit.ly/oReSiO
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Dark Knight Rises
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Jack and Jill starring Adam Sandler, Katie Holmes and Al Pacino. Sandler plays both Jack and Jill http://bit.ly/nsm0Zr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Jack and Jill
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser trailer for The Iron Lady starring Meryl Streep http://bit.ly/nX27Z5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Iron Lady
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Report: Disney developing movie based on Matterhorn ride http://bit.ly/kxU7yI
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Matterhorn
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @awards The Social Network won "Best in Show" at the 12th annual Golden Trailer Awards http://bit.ly/jJdEGz
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Social Network
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy starring Colin Firth, Tom Hardy and Gary Oldman http://bit.ly/jgdg3q
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser trailer for Mission Impossible: Ghost Protocol starring Tom Cruise, Josh Holloway and Jeremy Renner http://bit.ly/mM4NnZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Mission Impossible: Ghost Protocol
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Immortals starring Henry Cavill and Freida Pinto http://bit.ly/j2b2kc
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Immortals
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Flypaper starring Patrick Dempsey, Ashley Judd and Mekhi Phifer http://bit.ly/iBkGcu
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Flypaper
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser trailer for Pixar's Brave starring the voices of Emma Thompson, Kevin McKidd and Robbie Coltrane http://bit.ly/m4puT4
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Brave
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Apollo 18, a thriller about a secret moon landing mission in 1974. http://bit.ly/l9FmJc
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Apollo 18
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Freida Pinto Immortals poster revealed http://bit.ly/mvwnME
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Immortals
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cars 2 may be first Pixar film to get unfresh rating on Rotten Tomatoes http://bit.ly/mmqHfP
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Cars 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Killer Elite starring Jason Statham, Clive Owen and Robert De Niro http://bit.ly/jkI3Ym
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Killer Elite
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Official full-length trailer for The Muppets released http://bit.ly/k1sWnQ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Muppets
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Michael Bay says Steven Spielberg ordered him to fire actress Megan Fox http://lnk.ms/P9yMt
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Muppets spoof Green Lantern in new trailer http://bit.ly/kuwgPn
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Green Lantern
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Moneyball starring Brad Pitt and Jonah Hill http://bit.ly/jgr106
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Moneyball
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Academy adds new Best Picture Oscar twist http://bit.ly/mtaGYh
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Vidoe: J.J. Abrams and Joel Courtney talk Super 8 http://bit.ly/mBQUMq
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Super 8
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love, Wedding, Marriage has a dismal 0% fresh score on Rotten Tomatoes http://bit.ly/lQIHc5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Love, Wedding, Marriage
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Super 8 Clip: Scientists examine the creature, fail to take appropriate precautions http://bit.ly/lMd1uR
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Super 8
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	2011 MTV Movie Awards opening film channels The Hangover II http://bit.ly/lkQclV
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Hangover II
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Vow starring Rachel McAdams and Channing Tatum http://bit.ly/jWox79
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Vow
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Whistleblower starring Rachel Weisz, Vanessa Redgrave and Monica Bellucci http://bit.ly/le9sub
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Whistleblower
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Second trailer for Rise of the Planet of the Apes starring James Franco, Tom Felton and Freida Pinto http://bit.ly/jvFw40
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Rise of the Planet of the Apes
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Spy Kids: All the Time in the World starring Jessica Alba, Joel McHale and Ricky Gervais http://bit.ly/jVoiDX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Spy Kids: All the Time in the World
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First Look: Rosie Huntington-Whiteley in Transformers: Dark of the Moon http://bit.ly/jpAyDm
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Transformers: Dark of the Moon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Don't Be Afraid of the Dark starring Katie Holmes and Guy Pearce http://bit.ly/lRcZoY
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Don't Be Afraid of the Dark
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Girl With the Dragon Tattoo starring Daniel Craig, Rooney Mara and Stellan Skarsgard http://bit.ly/jbQoGO
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Girl With the Dragon Tattoo
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Good Neighbors, a psychological thriller, starring Jay Baruchel, Emily Hampshire and Scott Speedman http://bit.ly/mhEekL
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Good Neighbors
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser trailer for Happy Feet Two http://bit.ly/lkzpdi
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Happy Feet Two
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Second teaser trailer for Muppets movie starring Amy Adams and Jason Segel http://bit.ly/km7NfW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Muppets
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First Look: January Jones as Emma Frost in X-Men: First Class http://bit.ly/kU5Ujx
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			X-Men: First Class
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cars 2 trailer made using Lego bricks http://bit.ly/lEEYFj
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Cars 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Kirsten Dunst horrified as Melancholia director jokes about being a Nazi http://bit.ly/iPR5QW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Melancholia
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Zookeeper starring Kevin James, Rosario Dawson and Leslie Bibb http://bit.ly/iotrPI
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Zookeeper
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Our Idiot Brother starring Paul Rudd, Elizabeth Banks and Zooey Deschanel http://bit.ly/jr8Fyi
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Our Idiot Brother
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Cars 2 starring Owen Wilson, Larry the Cable Guy and Michael Caine http://bit.ly/lF9IsM
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Cars 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Fright Night starring Colin Farrell, Anton Yelchin and Toni Collette http://bit.ly/mvnLnZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Fright Night
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer: Jim Carry Stars in Mr. Popper's Penguins http://bit.ly/mCBRDw
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Mr. Popper's Penguins
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Straw Dogs starring James Marsden, Kate Bosworth and Alexander Skarsgard http://bit.ly/jKPpV4
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Straw Dogs
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thor's Mighty Hammer could be yours in toy form. http://bit.ly/mdGLTK
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Thor
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Barry Sonnenfeld announces plans for Dinosaurs Versus Aliens movie and graphic novel http://bit.ly/jI9SC4 (via @fantasysf)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Dinosaurs Versus Aliens
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Final Destination 5, a movie about young people being pursued unrelentingly by death. http://bit.ly/ipMf1b
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Final Destination 5
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Documentary alleging Princess Diana was murdered premieres at Cannes Film Festival http://bit.ly/ktNgkP
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Horrible Bosses starring Jennifer Aniston, Jason Bateman, Colin Farrell and Kevin Spacey http://bit.ly/kVR6vi
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Horrible Bosses
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Theatrical trailer for Real Steel starring Hugh Jackman and Evangeline Lilly http://bit.ly/kLax21
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Real Steel
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Martha Marcy May Marlene starring Elizabeth Olsen and Hugh Dancy http://bit.ly/lRTiDU
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Martha Marcy May Marlene
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Home Alone home for sale http://bit.ly/lVWDHK
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Home Alone
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for One Day starring Anne Hathaway and Jim Sturgess http://bit.ly/kAm1AI
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			One Day
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Red Band Trailer for Ironclad starring James Purefoy, Paul Giamatti and Kate Mara http://bit.ly/jP7R64
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Ironclad
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fast Five dominates box office with $83 million weekend http://bit.ly/lGi9pX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Fast Five
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fast Five off to a fast start - on track for an $80 million opening http://bit.ly/mK1om2
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Fast Five
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Transformers 3: Dark of the Moon http://bit.ly/l0o7oX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Transformers 3: Dark of the Moon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First Trailer for Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows - Part 2 http://bit.ly/jwubl2
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kristen Wiig and Wendi McLendon-Covy say Bridesmaids is no chick flick http://bit.ly/mwP7ik
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Bridesmaids
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Immortals starring Henry Cavill, Freida Pinto and Mickey Rourke http://bit.ly/jWUbgF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Immortals
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for What's Your Number? starring Anna Faris, Chris Evans and Ryan Phillippe http://bit.ly/ik91cr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			What's Your Number
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Devil's Double starring Dominic Cooper http://bit.ly/ff3Jhr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Devil's Double
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rio defeats Madea to win box office for second straight weekend http://bit.ly/dJONUP
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Rio
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Art of Getting By starring Emma Roberts, Freddie Highmore and Michael Angarano http://bit.ly/g2zbip
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Art of Getting By
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Disney Naturefilms' documentary Chimpanzee http://bit.ly/fSqAQn
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Chimpanzee
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Maggie Q takes on motorcycle gang in Priest http://bit.ly/gR3RcM
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Maggie Q
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Peter Jackson's video blog from the set of The Hobbit http://bit.ly/etW4aT
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Hobbit
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Red Band trailer for 30 Minutes or Less starring Jesse Eisenberg http://bit.ly/gzCdDE
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Red Band
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Rules for being a good Disney sidekick http://bit.ly/gorPGm
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Craig Gillespie (Fright Nigh)to direct Pride and Prejudice and Zombies movie. http://bit.ly/e1gHmk
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Pride and Prejudice and Zombies
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Second trailer for Cowboys and Aliens starring Daniel Craig, Harrison Ford and Olivia Wilde. http://bit.ly/hT6ERY
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Cowboys and Aliens
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rio slays Scream 4 to win weekend box office. The Conspirator makes $4m despite opening in just 707 theaters. http://bit.ly/gRJRo0
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Rio
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Scream 4
		</mention>
		<mention>
			The Conspirator
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for William and Kate, the Movie http://bit.ly/faQQGd
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			William and Kate
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Tyler Perry's Madea's Big Happy Family http://bit.ly/ecqOPR
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Big Happy Family
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Casa De Mi Padre starring Will Ferrell, Diego Luna and Gael Garcia Bernal http://bit.ly/f72hNW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Casa De Mi Padre
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Rise of the Planet of the Apes starring James Franco, Andy Serkis, Freida Pinto and Tom Felton http://bit.ly/eFwXkO
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Rise of the Planet of the Apes
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer: Bridesmaids starring Kristen Wiig, Maya Rudolph and Rose Byrne http://bit.ly/eg1BVw
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Bridesmaids
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Abduction starring Taylor Lautner, Lily Collins and Sigourney Weaver http://bit.ly/g9DawO
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Abduction
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Love Wedding Marriage starring Mandy Moore and Kellan Lutz http://bit.ly/h5iERO
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Love Wedding Marriage
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Dolphin Tale starring Morgan Freeman, Ashley Judd and Harry Connick, Jr. http://bit.ly/erYXQW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Dolphin Tale
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @writerswrite Roland Emmerich's latest film takes aim at Shakespeare controversy. http://bit.ly/etND56
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @celebritygossip: Will Smith to star opposite son Jaden in M. Night Shyamalan sci-fi movie - Willow not slated to sing though http:// ...
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			M
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	4 minutes of footage from The Green Lantern starring Ryan Reynolds from WonderCon http://bit.ly/e08MBm
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Green Lantern
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Hangover: Part 2 starring Zach Galifianakis, Bradley Cooper, Justin Bartha, and Ed Helms http://bit.ly/e8TJ6H
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Hangover: Part 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Everything Must Go starring Will Ferrell http://bit.ly/gXoYSN
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Everything Must Go
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Midnight in Paris starring Owen Wilson, Rachel Adams, Marion Cotillard and Adrien Brody http://bit.ly/hYrBle
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Midnight in Paris
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Amy Adams cast as Lois Lane in new Superman movie http://bit.ly/fbuAKW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Superman
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Wimpy Kid film tops Sucker Punch at box office http://bit.ly/hqikHz
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Sucker Punch
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Three Musketeers starring Logan Lerman, Orlando Bloom and Milla Jovovich http://bit.ly/h3j1Hm
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Three Musketeers
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Marvel releases first full length trailer of Captain America: The First Avenger http://bit.ly/hfKh0l
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Captain America: The First Avenger
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Happiness Is a Warm Blanket, Charlie Brown http://bit.ly/dLLn5F
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Happiness Is a Warm Blanket
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Peter Jackson poses inside Bilbo's home as production begins on The Hobbit http://bit.ly/ewpD2U
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Hobbit
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New theatrical trailer for Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides http://bit.ly/f7YFRX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Pom Wonderful Presents: The Greatest Movie Ever Sold - film explores use of product placement in movies. http://bit.ly/gCl9XV
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Pom Wonderful Presents: The Greatest Movie Ever Sold
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Larry Crowne starring Tom Hanks and Julia Roberts http://bit.ly/g34msE
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Larry Crowne
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Aaron Eckhart talks about breaking his arm on set of Battle Los Angeles http://bit.ly/eryotX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Battle Los Angeles
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Fast Five starring Vin Diesel, Paul Walker and Jordana Brewster http://bit.ly/igNdR8
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Fast Five
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Puss in Boots poster and teaser trailer http://bit.ly/e90vhK
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Puss in Boots
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rango wins weekend box office with $38 million take. http://bit.ly/gJby6s
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Rango
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Dylan Dog: Dead of Night starring Brandon Routh http://bit.ly/fcP7BT
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Dylan Dog
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	DreamWorks Animation SKG has announced plans to bring Rumblewick to the big screen. http://bit.ly/egU0CG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Rumblewick
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Priest starring Paul Bettany, Cam Gigandet and Maggie Q http://bit.ly/dIuMdh
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Priest
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Limitless starring Bradley Cooper and Robert De Niro http://bit.ly/fGlTSr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Limitless
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disney-Pixar release teaser for Toy Story short called "Hawaiian Vacation." http://bit.ly/eTV6VG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Hawaiian Vacation
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	No Oscars for True Grit despite ten nominations http://bit.ly/fLPHjp
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			True Grit
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First Teaser Trailer for The Hangover Part II http://bit.ly/hR0d6n
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Hangover Part II
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Red Band Trailer for Bad Teacher starring Cameron Diaz, Jason Segel, Phyllis Smith, Jason Timberlake http://bit.ly/gMa8qb
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Bad Teacher
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Something Borrowed starring Kate Hudson, Ginnifer Goodwin and John Krasinski http://bit.ly/h3YZPZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Something Borrowed
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Prom starring Aimee Teegarden and Thomas McDonnell http://bit.ly/f9LPEP
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Prom
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Arthur starring Russell Brand, Jennifer Garner and Helen Mirren http://bit.ly/gH6WJD
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Arthur
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for X-Men: First Class Starring James McAvoy, Michael Fassbender and January Jones http://bit.ly/feUkK9
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			X-Men: First Class
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Black Death starring Sean Bean and Kimberly Nixon http://bit.ly/dQi8fu
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Black Death
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Unknown starring Liam Neeson and Diane Kruger http://bit.ly/f6QSgq
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Unknown
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Rite, a horror movie starring Anthony Hopkins, claimed the #1 spot at the box office this weekend. http://bit.ly/fnfTsP
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Rite
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	James Cameron joins Twitter. His account is @JimCameron http://bit.ly/epb7xg
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First Look at the upcoming line of Green Lantern toys. http://bit.ly/gvOK2v
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Green Lantern
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	List of the 83rd Academy Awards nominees for Best Picture  http://bit.ly/eU1Ufq
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Razzies Worst Picture: Last Airbender, Twilight Saga: Eclipse, The Bounty Hunter, Sex and the City 2 and Vampires Suck http://bit.ly/dKxW96
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Last Airbender
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Twilight Saga: Eclipse
		</mention>
		<mention>
			The Bounty Hunter
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Sex and the City 2
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Vampires Suck
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Company Men starring Ben Affleck, Tommy Lee Jones and Maria Bello http://bit.ly/hJUb18
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Company Men
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sacha Baron Cohen to play Saddam Hussein in movie http://bit.ly/fEjqp5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Star Wars: The Complete Saga for Blu-ray announced at the Consumer Electronics Show (CES) http://bit.ly/fhmnZT
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Star Wars
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Early teaser Trailer for Ice Age: Continental Drift which is not coming out until Summer 2012. http://bit.ly/hT1Y5R
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Ice Age: Continental Drift
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Mechanic starring Jason Statham, Ben Foster and Donald Sutherland http://bit.ly/eiDIkT
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			 The Mechanic
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Interview with the cast of True Grit http://bit.ly/e0D87K Trailer http://bit.ly/gfGjQ7
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			True Grit
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Your Highness starring James Franco and Natalie Portman http://bit.ly/ees8al
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Your Highness
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Easy A, Salt and Wall Street: Money Never Sleeps out on DVD, Blu-ray on Tuesday, 12-21 http://bit.ly/ibxXFU
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Easy A
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Salt
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Wall Street: Money Never Sleeps
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Yogi Bear starring Dan Ackroyd and Justin Timberlake http://bit.ly/eClFeC
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Yogi Bear
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Fast Five starring Vin Diesel, Paul Walker and Dwayne Johnson http://bit.ly/g02AuI
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Fast Five
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides starring Johnny Depp and Penelope Cruz http://bit.ly/fzo2v8
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Thor poster and first Thor trailer released http://bit.ly/fbyc2F
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Thor
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Real Steel starring Hugh Jackman and Evangeline Lilly http://bit.ly/f8kHwF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Real Steel
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Beaver starring Mel Gibson and Jodie Foster http://bit.ly/hinta5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Beaver
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Beastly starring Vanessa Hudgens, Neil Patrick Harris and Alex Pettyfer http://bit.ly/h80bNk
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Beastly
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disney will set sail for 'Pirates of the Caribbean' 5 & 6 back-to-back http://bit.ly/gbLHaG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Pirates of the Caribbean
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Red Riding Hood starring Amanda Seyfried and Billy Burke http://bit.ly/aNCQDg
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Red Riding Hood
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Green Lantern starring Ryan Reynolds and Blake Lively http://bit.ly/ddygdF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Green Lantern
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Cowboys and Aliens starring Harrison Ford, Daniel Craig and Olivia Wilde http://bit.ly/aE0yaO
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Cowboys and Aliens
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disney releases Winnie the Pooh trailer http://bit.ly/a8sMMt
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Winnie the Pooh
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @celebritygossip Bill Clinton joins cast of The Hangover 2 http://bit.ly/ccsylu
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Hangover 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Little Fockers starring Ben Stiller, Jessica Alba and Robert DeNiro http://bit.ly/csuyi6
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Little Fockers
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Scarlett Johansson to play sexy alien seductress in Under the Skin http://bit.ly/9wsW0C
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Under the Skin
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Gulliver's Travels starring Jack Black. http://bit.ly/dfC3rE
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Gulliver's Travels
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Roland Emmerich prepping super secret alien invasion movie - shot with unknowns, tiny budget http://bit.ly/9zCz6C
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Will Smith nabs Nicole Scherzinger, Betty White for Men in Black 3 http://eonli.ne/bwmmjr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Men in Black 3
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fourth Mission: Impossible film to be called Ghost Protocol http://bit.ly/av8sTP
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Mission Impossible: Ghost Protocol
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Danny DeVito to Voice the Lorax in Animated Film http://bit.ly/bqKoyF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Lorax
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mad Max fans celebrate Wasteland Weekend in Southern California Desert http://bit.ly/bzaWyF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Mad Max
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Hereafter starring Matt Damon http://bit.ly/952cOa
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Hereafter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Colin Farrell Is frontrunner for 'Total Recall' lead http://bit.ly/aRqPCi
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Total Recall
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Murray in Ghostbusters uniform at 2010 Scream Awards http://bit.ly/ce0wgc
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Ghostbusters
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Justin Theroux says Derek and Hansel will return for Zoolander 2 http://bit.ly/ayekR8
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Zoolander 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for drive Angry 3D starring Nicolas Cage http://bit.ly/aEHHBe
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Drive Angry 3D
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Time says Top Gun 2 in the works with Tom Cruise returning as Maverick http://bit.ly/9Ow7Rv
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Top Gun 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Matt Damon reportedly will not be involved in the next Bourne movie. http://bit.ly/cLiLE3
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Social Network wins weekend box office for second straight week. http://bit.ly/aeOzKN
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Social Network
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Trailer for Dilemma with gay reference removed http://bit.ly/an2XfX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Dilemma
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for the Tempest starring Helen Mirren, Russell Brand and Djimon Honsou http://bit.ly/9F13xz
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Tempest
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dan Aykroyd on Ghostbusters 3 script - says Bill Murray has "comic role of a lifetime." http://bit.ly/cmaTKh
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Ghostbusters 3
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rubies launches official line of Avatar costumes, masks, wigs, spears and Na'vi makeup for Halloween. http://bit.ly/a2zOwV
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Avatar
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Diane Lane talks Secretariat movie http://bit.ly/9nrCxz
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Secretariat
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Social Network wins weekend box office. It made $23 million. http://bit.ly/b8Zpre
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Social Network
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mark Ruffalo says he will take inspiration from the Bill Bixby version of the Hulk for Avengers movie. http://bit.ly/c5hyqL
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Avengers
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Inception has grossed $753 million worldwide so far http://bit.ly/aeT4et
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Inception
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Steven Spielberg wants to make a film about the Robopocalypse http://bit.ly/d9R3Q2
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kevin James to star in martial arts movie. http://bit.ly/aonP3e (via @celebritygossip)
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Tourist starring Johnny Depp and Angelina Jolie http://bit.ly/cuik59
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Tourist
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Country Strong trailer released. Gwyneth Paltrow plays an alcoholic country singer in the film. http://bit.ly/b8hAnX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Country Strong
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Paula Patton has joined the cast of Mission: Impossible 4 http://bit.ly/cuRriy
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Mission: Impossible 4
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	John Cusack to play Edgar Allan Poe in movie http://bit.ly/9rp9JZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for the Next Three Days starring Russell Crowe, Elizabeth Banks and Liam Neeson. http://bit.ly/aybFGU
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Next Three Days
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Associated Press loves the crap out of Piranha 3-D http://bit.ly/a4n01p
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Piranha 3-D
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Steven R. McQueen talks Vampire Diaries, Piranha 3D http://bit.ly/cRtrFi
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Vampire Diaries
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Piranha 3D
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Black Swan starring Natalie Portman and Mila Kunis http://bit.ly/byFRoC
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Black Swan
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer: Joaquin Phoenix looks crazy in I'm Still Here Trailer http://bit.ly/cCBarK
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			I'm Still Here
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @celebritygossip Leonardo DiCaprio stands to make at least $50 million from Inception. http://bit.ly/9glTQQ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Inception
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for M. Night Shyamalan's next movie, the supernatural thriller called Devil. http://bit.ly/dgFPRO
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Devil
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Radiohead's "Creep" song used in trailer for The Social Network movie about Facebook. http://bit.ly/bQKDoj
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Social Network
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Adrien Brody talks about his role in Predators, in which he plays a former US army special forces operative. http://bit.ly/bJCZt4
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Predators
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Next James Bond film could be years away http://bit.ly/d4SNie
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New King Kong attraction, created by Peter Jackson, launches at Universal Studios on July 1st. http://bit.ly/cfiNw5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			King Kong
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Matt Damon is considering making a movie based on Benjamin Mee's memoir, We Bought a Zoo. http://bit.ly/coVk7N
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			We Bought a Zoo
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rock 'Em Sock 'Em robots headed to the big screen http://bit.ly/9q0d5i
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Twilight fans already camping out for Eclipse premiere http://bit.ly/dkyyVL
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Twilight
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaser Trailer for the Smurfs Live Action Movie http://bit.ly/9BvVZL
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Smurfs
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Karate Kid is weekend's number one film - beat The A-Team by $30 million. http://bit.ly/aFgECA
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Karate Kid
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Paramount Pictures and MTV Films say a Les Grossman Movie is in the works http://bit.ly/av6ila
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Michael Bay's website welcomes Rosie Huntington Whiteley to Transformers 3 team. http://bit.ly/b8BQl6
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Transformers 3
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Actress Jodelle Ferland explains Bree Tanner character in new Twilight Eclipse clip. http://bit.ly/aJbR9g
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Twilight Eclipse
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Scott Pilgrim Vs. The World movie trailer. Stars Michael Cera as Scott Pilgrim. http://bit.ly/dySelQ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Scott Pilgrim Vs. The World
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ticket prices jump again - in some Manhattan IMAX theaters consumers will pay $20 for a ticket for the first time. http://bit.ly/9NyYES
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Megan Fox says it was her decision to leave Transformers http://bit.ly/9YnRfm
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg portrayed as ruthless, untrustworthy sex maniac in upcoming movie http://bit.ly/d5yJl5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Field of Dreams baseball field for sale http://bit.ly/91FFoo
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Field of Dreams
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	3D Shark Night film in the works from Snakes on a Plane director. http://bit.ly/9oK68z
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			3D Shark Night
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Snakes on a Plane
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Human Centipede - the most disturbing movie ever made? asks CNN http://bit.ly/cJXc5h
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Human Centipede
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	FCC to allow On Demand movies before DVD or Blu Ray release dates http://bit.ly/bPiVZ9
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Patrick Dempsey is joining the cast of Transformers 3 http://bit.ly/9MKLfh
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Transformers 3
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Paramount has passed on making Anchorman 2 even after cast cut their budget down. http://bit.ly/dhsZJC
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Anchorman 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A movie is being made based on Mattel's Magic 8 Ball. http://bit.ly/93QE2n
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First Jonah Hex trailer released - stars Josh Brolin and Megan Fox. Release date: 6-18-10 http://bit.ly/9CRq4A
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Jonah Hex
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Line has problems getting everyone back for another trip to the Center of the Earth http://bit.ly/aaypbl
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Center of the Earth
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lego version of the Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time trailer  http://bit.ly/c3cHN2
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dr. Pepper launches Iron Man 2 Dr. Pepper cans  http://bit.ly/dtpLp6
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Iron Man 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	James Cameron: Ocean of Pandora is focus of Avatar sequel http://bit.ly/9qorlw
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Ocean of Pandora
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	007 producers have suspended development on the next James Bond film previously scheduled for release 2011/2012. http://bit.ly/drJDe5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Volcanic ash cloud cancels Iron Man 2 London premiere http://bit.ly/dzHMEW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Iron Man 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How to Train Your Dragon wins box office for the second time, Kick-Ass struggles  http://bit.ly/dowXSg
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			How to Train Your Dragon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Digital exhibit at The Grove in L.A. morphs shoppers faces Into Na'vis  http://bit.ly/dBN7Ok
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Grove
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Astrid Berges Frisbey to play mermaid in fourth Pirates film http://bit.ly/b7B2yC
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Joss Whedon in final negotiations to direct Marvel Studios' The Avengers. http://bit.ly/bWW1B3
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Avengers
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Steve Carell and Tina Fey's Date Night tops box office - just barely beats 'Titans' http://bit.ly/9vAIqM
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Titans
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for The Other Guys starring Will Ferrell and Mark Wahlberg http://bit.ly/cxuqoQ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Other Guys
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Tina Fey and Steve Carell talk Date Night  http://bit.ly/9KZmsk
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Date Night
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Anna Friel likely to join Bradley Cooper in The Dark Fields thriller http://bit.ly/9o6loF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Dark Fields
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	UD Replicas unveiled a Wolverine Motorcycle Suit at Wizard World Toronto Comic-Con.  http://bit.ly/9eopsS
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Wolverine
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Baja Earthquake serves up 4D Kraken moment in Clash of the Titans http://bit.ly/9DSh3u
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Clash of the Titans
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Clash of the Titans wins Box Office - beat Easter weekend record set by Scary Movie 4 http://bit.ly/92d8a7
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Clash of the Titans
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Scary Movie 4
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Anna Faris is slated to star in a remake of Private Benjamin. http://bit.ly/9D6GAS
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Private Benjamin
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Iron Man 2 poster has been unveiled - includes image of Scarlett Johansson as Black Widow. http://bit.ly/aJc56F
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Iron Man 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Netflix will be hurt if Post Office has its way and ends Saturday delivery. http://bit.ly/dlta6R
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Godzilla coming back to the big screen again in 2012.  http://bit.ly/bbpr33
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Godzilla
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Movie prices soaring - IMAX 3D ticket prices hit nearly $20 for an adult ticket in New York City  http://bit.ly/dgntXV
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Will Ferrell says the Anchorman sequel has been put on hold.  http://bit.ly/dDzlXZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Anchorman
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Medusa clip from upcoming Clash of the Titans movie released. http://bit.ly/dla5B3
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Clash of the Titans
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ian McKellen (Gandalf) posted about the 2 Hobbit films - says filming in NZ will take over a year, casting has started. http://bit.ly/dfWPNB
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Hobbit
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Harry Potter's Hogwarts set destroyed as explosions trigger blaze http://bit.ly/cs8vXA
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fox delays Wall Street sequel - release date will be  September 24th instead of April 23. http://bit.ly/aL2jAf
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sandra Bullock pulls out of UK premiere of The Blind Side after model claims affair with her husband Jesse James http://bit.ly/9z8Ypr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Blind Side
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video of a very short teaser trailer for Twilight: Eclipse - only ten seconds long. http://bit.ly/d2joQh
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Twilight: Eclipse
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Gilligan's Island Motion Picture in the Works http://bit.ly/9uAYCk
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	CNN explains how Oscar Ballots are counted and delivered - counted in a secure room with no windows http://bit.ly/d94NZ9
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tim Burton's Alice in Wonderland headed for record $115 million opening weekend.  http://bit.ly/c8vbYG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Alice in Wonderland
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Line is looking for recruits for a relaunched Police Academy movie.  http://bit.ly/brW3Ip
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Police Academy
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Actress Rachel Nichols to play Tamara in Conan the Barbarian remake. http://bit.ly/cHguIN
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Conan the Barbarian
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Harris Poll finds most Americans think Avatar should win Best Picture http://bit.ly/b1pqQf
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Avatar
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oscar preparations continue as the Big Day nears  http://bit.ly/b51v8Z
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Warner Bros. and Atlas Entertainment plot film version of "Gilligan's Island" http://bit.ly/bxeaQm
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Gilligan's Island
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Actress/singer Ashely Tisdale will star in a musical remake of Teen Witch. http://bit.ly/92kVfH
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Teen Witch
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Angelina Jolie turns down Wanted 2. Sequel will now die. http://bit.ly/csfwCn
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Angelina Jolie
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	David Goyer hired to write Superman: The Man of Steel script http://bit.ly/dt3Omk
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Superman: The Man of Steel
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Erector Set movie being developed by Helix Films  http://bit.ly/cQZrCl
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Best Picture themed dishes created for New York Oscars Party http://bit.ly/9kDKi5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disney-Pixars Toy Story 3 helped kick off the Toy Fair in New York City http://bit.ly/9bc6qw
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Toy Story 3
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Star-studded Valentine's Day movie wins weekend box office.  http://bit.ly/9oNwPN
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Valentine's Day
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stephenie Meyer's novel Breaking Dawn will definitely be made into two more Twilight movies. http://bit.ly/bVdful
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Breaking Dawn
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tom Cruise signs on for Mission Impossible 4. Film slated to arrive in theaters Memorial Day weekend, 2011 http://bit.ly/bM6mmU
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Mission Impossible 4
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	DreamWorks to air short animated films promoting How to Train Your Dragon during NBC's Olympics coverage  http://bit.ly/aYmA0t
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			How to Train Your Dragon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Super Bowl Ads: HomeAway's Hotel Hell Vacation trailer featuring the Griswolds. http://bit.ly/aekdZG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			HomeAway's Hotel Hell Vacation
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dear John wins weekend Box Office. Avatar falls to second.  http://bit.ly/96SerN
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Dear John
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Wizarding World of Harry Potter Super Bowl Ad  http://bit.ly/9QFM5B
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A new trailer for Robin Hood starring Russell Crowe and Cate Blanchett will air during the Superbowl.  http://bit.ly/9keMo0
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Robin Hood
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stan Lee loves the idea of a Spider-Man reboot http://bit.ly/buur6A
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Spider-Man
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Anne Hathaway talks Alice in Wonderland - she plays the White Queen  http://bit.ly/9fZVBp
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Alice in Wonderland
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Matt Damon says the next Bourne film could be a prequel. http://bit.ly/c25BwB
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for Wall Street 2: Money Never Sleeps starring Michael Douglas and Shia LaBeouf  http://bit.ly/dpgZHz
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Wall Street 2: Money Never Sleeps
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Avatar tops Titanic to become all-Time worldwide box office leader  http://bit.ly/c6ID7b
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Avatar
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Titanic
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Gremlins is reportedly being remade. It will be in stereoscopic 3D http://bit.ly/6AZNUp
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Gremlins
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Zach Efron tells Nancy O'Dell that playing Spider-Man would be a dream come true. http://bit.ly/4pYcx5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Spider-Man
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A-Team's no "easy, breezy Cover Girl version" of the old TV show, says writer-director Joe Carnahan. http://bit.ly/6ZQaUB
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			A-Team
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Blockbuster bonanza: 25 big movies to look out for in 2010 http://bit.ly/68iqx2
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	DHD says Spider-Man 4 scrapped and series will be completely rebooted for 2012. http://bit.ly/5M32R0
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Spider-Man 4
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trailer for A-Team starring Liam Neeson and Bradley Cooper  http://bit.ly/8EzmDQ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			A-Team
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Avatar makes $1 billion worldwide in 17 days - now 5th on all-time worldwide box office chart.  http://bit.ly/8FRmJw
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Avatar
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sandra Bullock named top money making movie star of 2009 by poll of movie theater owners and filmmakers. http://bit.ly/8vdoSh
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New trailer for The Sorcerer's Apprentice starring Nicolas Cage  http://bit.ly/5WDb8q
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Sorcerer's Apprentice
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A Poster, an Image, and the synopsis and release date (12-17-2010) for Tron Legacy http://bit.ly/6ckYws
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Tron Legacy
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: James Cameron and Sigourney Weaver talk Avatar  http://bit.ly/93hupX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Avatar
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Michael Bay directs a Victoria's Secret commercial  http://bit.ly/5l6AAp
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fox says 'Avatar' is costliest film it's ever made- speculation is budget was over $300 million but Fox won't say. http://bit.ly/8qBFbg
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Avatar
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The first official trailer is out for part one of Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows.  http://bit.ly/86MaPF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Woman arrested for trying to record Twilight on a digital camera http://bit.ly/4HiTjW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Twilight
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Be Italian: New Nine movie posters revealed  http://bit.ly/7JNKJZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Nine
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Critics slam New Moon - 30% on Rotten Tomatoes http://bit.ly/1U6it
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			New Moon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Moon is breaking pre-sale ticket records at Fandango, AMC and MovieTickets.com.  http://bit.ly/UkbWa
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			New Moon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kate Hudson sings Cinema Italiano in new Nine trailer  http://bit.ly/48QXzn
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Nine
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Retro movie posters released to promote up.  http://bit.ly/cISqU
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Twilight fans already lining up for Monday's 'New Moon' premiere http://bit.ly/1dlluh
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			New Moon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Harvey Keitel has joined the cast of the "Meet the Fockers" sequel. http://bit.ly/3iM30N
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Meet the Fockers
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The first trailer for Kick-Ass, a film based on the Marvel comic book written by Mark Millar, has been released. http://bit.ly/3Rqk1V
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Kick-Ass
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	MySpace is hosting an exclusive live stream of the red carpet at the New Moon premiere on Monday, November, 16th. http://bit.ly/4t5kAZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			New Moon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hasbro's board game Risk being transformed Into a movie  http://bit.ly/1sTMI8
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	IGN has some Kick-Ass movie posters. http://bit.ly/CzqbX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Kick-Ass
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Walmart, Amazon.com and Target price war knocks down the price of hot new upcoming DVD releases like Star Trek to $10. http://bit.ly/4Divmf
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Star Trek
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Johnny Depp to star with Angelina Jolie in The Tourist http://bit.ly/1P6jPf
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Tourist
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tom Selleck, Ted Danson and Steve Guttenberg are said to be returning for a third "Three Men" movie.  http://bit.ly/1n0uc1
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Three Men
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @celebritygossip Steve Martin, Alec Baldwin to co-host Oscars in March, 2010. http://bit.ly/2wUOr9
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Prince of Persia trailer is out. Jake Gyllenhaal & his feisty sidekick are on a mission to stop the end of the world. http://bit.ly/1HdFiX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Prince of Persia
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The rights to the Terminator film franchise will be auctioned this month. http://bit.ly/4yW8fC
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Terminator
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Theater owners are scrambling to ensure they have enough 3-D screens in time for the holiday movie fare. http://bit.ly/tTfsr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Twilight themed restaurant called Volterra to open in Forks, Washington. http://bit.ly/ydk0
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Twilight
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bruce Lee's daughter Shannon Lee and LeeWay media launch BruceLee.com http://bit.ly/yYl1z
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: The Volturi walk the red carpet in Rome  http://bit.ly/2vi9bS
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tyler Perry says characters like Madea are bait so he can discuss "God, love, faith, forgiveness, family" in his films http://bit.ly/4tIWr9
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First Look at the New A-Team  http://bit.ly/1KAClc
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			A-Team
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Researchers discovered that when children watch scary movies with their parents it actually makes the movie more scary. http://bit.ly/25Qu2F
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cover your electronics with Edward http://bit.ly/3vNDxQ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	rt @weather The Weather Channel plans to start showing movies. http://bit.ly/2QKkUx
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cinema Blend says the Scary Movie 5 will be a reboot http://bit.ly/xJoeL
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Scary Movie 5
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Where the Wild Things Are wins weekend box office but it may not have made enough - could fade next week. http://bit.ly/3wmwTU
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Where the Wild Things Are
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Couples Retreat is weekend's number one film  http://bit.ly/lUFDh
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Couples Retreat
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Line plotting sequel to the 1983 film Vacation http://bit.ly/wcPoD
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Vacation
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	John Cassar, co-executive producer and director for "24", has inked a deal for his first feature film called Motorcade. http://bit.ly/XPtt
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Motorcade
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	John Cusack ponders the End of the World in upcoming film, 2012 http://bit.ly/1xtSs1
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	MTV says Disney is preparing to replace Johnny Depp in 4th Pirates film if/when he decides to abandon ship.  http://bit.ly/3ctWJ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Barbie heads to the big screen - will be a live action film with a decent budget. http://bit.ly/w0lmX
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Johnny Depp may back out of fourth Pirates of the Caribbean film, now that Dick Cook is no longer Disney boss http://bit.ly/P0zE7
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Pirates of the Caribbean
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Urban Outfitters is selling Where the Wild Things Are tees  http://bit.ly/x1vBW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Where the Wild Things Are
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Transformers crew calls Megan Fox unprofessional and "dumb as a rock" in letter removed from Michael Bay's website. http://bit.ly/oinQ1
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New trailer for New Moon has been leaked online.  http://bit.ly/paAYt
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			New Moon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Will Smith, Charlize Theron and Jason Bateman set to reunite for a Hancock sequel. http://bit.ly/U18eN
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Hancock
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Taylor Lautner does a backflip in set photo posted by Eclipse director, David A. Slade. http://bit.ly/voGWG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Eclipse
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Poster offers first glimpse of CGI Smurf from upcoming film. http://bit.ly/i8WVe
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Smurf
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Seems a bit early for this - Fox has decided to reboot The Fantastic Four film franchise. http://bit.ly/WgdxW
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Fantastic Four
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Steven Spielberg developing film out of a posthumously published novel by the late Michael Crichton - Pirate Latitudes http://bit.ly/LOjMD
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Pirate Latitudes
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Summit is taking its Twilight hit on the road with a number of Twilight fan conventions. http://bit.ly/38xzk3
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Twilight
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tarantino's Inglourious Basterds was able to fend off the surprise science fiction hit District 9 to claim the #1 spot. http://bit.ly/O8Thq
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Inglourious Basterds
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Warner Bros. is building a Lego movie - an action adventure set in a Lego world.  http://bit.ly/wox1Q
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	G I Joe rises to the top of the box office  http://bit.ly/gxwyQ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			G I Joe
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Jennifer Aniston signs on for Pumas, which features two 30-something women who pursue younger men  http://bit.ly/vEdGI
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Actress switch in the 3rd Twilight movie: In Eclipse, Bryce Dallas Howard will replace Rachelle Lefevre as Victoria. http://bit.ly/eh7eG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Eclipse
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sam Raimi (Evil Dead, Spider-Man) has signed on to direct the World of Warcraft movie. http://bit.ly/14Yzad
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			World of Warcraft
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Universal Designs store will soon be selling a replica of the Dark Knight's motorcycle outfit. http://bit.ly/byXnr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Dark Knight
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hobbit film could be jeopardized by Tolkien heirs' lawsuit http://bit.ly/4Fhlkb
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Hobbit
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince  breaks box office records with $22.5 million midnight opening. http://bit.ly/RJ2wk
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Half-Blood Prince to push Harry Potter franchise's box office gross past that of the James Bond franchise. http://bit.ly/rHNUg
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bruno was the number one film this weekend although it made less per theater than Borat. http://bit.ly/ecb4E
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Bruno
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Borat
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bruno did David Letterman's top ten list last night about why you should see Bruno. http://bit.ly/XKsVm
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Bruno
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Raja Gosnell (Scooby-Doo) has signed on to direct the Smurfs movie for Columbia Pictures and Sony Animation. http://bit.ly/4yHT9x
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Scooby-Doo
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Torrential rain soaks London premiere of new Harry Potter film http://bit.ly/9COpu
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Harry Potter star Rupert Grint bettter after bout w swine flu. Says it was "quite scary" - stayed in bed for a few days http://bit.ly/5ECon
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ice Age & Transformers2 tied for #1 July 4 weekend box office slot - each made $42.5 million. Public Enemies came in 3rd http://is.gd/1oWCQ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Ice Age
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Transformers 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Transformers 2 opened huge with midnight screenings which took in a whopping $16 million bucks.  http://bit.ly/djNos
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Transformers 2
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Proposal was a big hit this weekend. It made $34.1 million - a career best for both Sandra Bullock and Ryan Reynolds http://bit.ly/KOOl6
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Proposal
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Trailer for Love Happens starring Jennifer Aniston and Aaron Eckhart  http://bit.ly/bXf5n
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Love Happens
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince images and posters are out. http://bit.ly/JEPQY
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Winona Ryder says a Heathers sequel is in the works. She says Christian Slater has also agreed to come back. http://bit.ly/RNgb9
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Heathers
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Alien 5 film has been confirmed to be a prequel. http://bit.ly/MRPYA
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Alien 5
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A teaser trailer for Toy Story 3 has been released. Film will be out in 2010. http://bit.ly/17F31e
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Toy Story 3
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Natalie Portman has signed on to play a warrior princess in a comedy film called Your Highness.  http://bit.ly/t6WXb
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Your Highness
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ridiculously short 14-second New Moon teaser trailer released, with kissing. http://bit.ly/RbQvr
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			New Moon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Opening this weekend: Terminator Salvation, Night at the Museum 2, Dance Flick, The Girlfriend Experience. http://is.gd/C6aG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Terminator Salvation
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Night at the Museum 2
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Dance Flick
		</mention>
		<mention>
			The Girlfriend Experience
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Will Smith, Sony acquire Katrina story. John Lee Hancock (The Rookie, The Alamo) will write and direct. http://bit.ly/vmuod
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The new trailer for Guy Ritchie's Sherlock Holmes is out. Film stars Robert Downey, Jr. as Holmes & Jude Law as Watson  http://bit.ly/HDiI
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Sherlock Holmes
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Angels & Demons wins box office with $48 m opening - also had huge overseas opening. Star Trek had strong second week. http://bit.ly/3IOouL
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Angels & Demons
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Star Trek
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Star Trek beams in new fans with its $72.5 million opening weekend. http://bit.ly/xoR9h
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Star Trek
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Huge weekend opening expected for Star Trek. Opens in 3,800 U.S. theaters tonight and this weekend. http://bit.ly/lsJG4
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Star Trek
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Harry Potter: The Exhibition opens today at the Chicago's Museum of Science and Industry. http://bit.ly/ZYDao
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Moviegoers Obsessed With Beyonce and Ali Larter. 17 Again also had a strong second weekend in theaters. http://bit.ly/QSfAE
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			17 Again
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A Clueless sequel - Alicia Silverstone to reprise her role as Cher Horowitz in a sequel to the 1995 hit film. http://is.gd/u7Nz
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Clueless
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hannah Montana: The Movie scores second biggest Easter weekend opening ever. http://bit.ly/145x6N
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Hannah Montana
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Seth Rogen's dark comedy Observe and Report  criticized for date rape scene. http://bit.ly/20diep
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Observe and Report
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The funny trailer for Sasha Baron Cohen's new film Bruno is out. http://tr.im/iaB5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Bruno
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	ne Hathaway has been signed by Harvey Weinstein to play Judy Garland in film and stage adaptations of a biography. http://tr.im/i1dP
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Buzz begins for Astro Boy movie, which is based on a manga comic. Movie will open in October, 2009. http://tr.im/hVYh
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Astro Boy
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Where The Wild Things Are poster and happy, upbeat trailer hit the Internet.  http://tr.im/hOgF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Where The Wild Things Are
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Robert Pattinson's lack of personal hygiene habits freaking out the cast and crew of New Moon. http://tr.im/hM5a
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			New Moon
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yahoo movies posts list of 100 movies to see before you die. http://tr.im/hJeC
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hollywood is embracing 3-D movies this summer with big budget 3-D films including Monsters vs. Aliens. http://tr.im/hFxf
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Monsters vs. Aliens
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kevin Costner and Tommy Lee Jones set to star in The Company Men with Ben Affleck. http://tr.im/hznD
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Company Men
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Race to Witch Mountain knocks Watchmen off the #1 box office slot. http://tr.im/hqtF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Race to Witch Mountain
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Watchmen
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	There's a rumor that Freida Pinto could be the next Bond girl. Jennifer Aniston would also like the role. http://tr.im/hoT4
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watchmen Lego Minifigs - all real minifigs apparently except for Dr. Manhattan, who was made with Photoshop. http://tr.im/hhjn
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Watchmen
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watchmen Cupcakes: Here's some cupcakes based on the blockbuster Watchmen movie and graphic novel.  http://bit.ly/4KToZ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Watchmen
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watchmen makes $25 million on opening day but it's only the 8th highest superhero opening day. http://tr.im/h7DJ
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Watchmen
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Jonas Brothers' movie is likely to win this weekend's box office thanks to mobs of teen girls. http://tr.im/gOiK
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Warner Bros. is looking at a remake of the 1980s film, Never Ending Story. http://tr.im/gOiF
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Never Ending Story
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mike Myers and Paris Hilton are the unfortunate winners of Razzie Awards given out to worst films and for worst acting. http://bit.ly/Y6wlw
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Dark Knight blockbuster movie has topped the $1 billion mark at the box office. http://bit.ly/jtDg
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Dark Knight
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Greg Behrendt, co-author of He's Just Not That Into You, explains how the book came to be. It was the #1 film Friday. http://bit.ly/1rlNZG
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			He's Just Not That Into You
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sienna Miller plays the Baroness, a sexy villain in the upcoming G.I. Joe movie, G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra.  http://bit.ly/Vrgm
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bruno movie has been delayed until July. Bruno is another character played by comedian Sacha Baron Cohen (Borat). http://tr.im/cmw5
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Bruno
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Paul Blart: Mall Cop is the nation's number one movie. It's the first hit for Kevin James where he has the lead role. http://is.gd/gqTy
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Jackie Chan is in final negotiations to star in the remake of the hit film, The Karate Kid. http://bit.ly/cqIFA
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Karate Kid
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Twilight dvd goes up for pre-order on Amazon. Includes bonus scene from Midnight Sun, fifth book in Twilight series. http://bit.ly/aNhv
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Twilight
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Slumdog nearly swept the Critics' Choice Awards. Heath Ledger won Best Supporting Actor. http://bit.ly/11Cgp
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Slumdog
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hugh Jackman has dropped out of Steven Soderbergh's upcoming musical version of Cleopatra starring Catherine Zeta-Jones. http://bit.ly/dCv3
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Cleopatra
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Will Smith voted top Money Making Star of 2008  http://bit.ly/OZip
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Jennifer Aniston, Owen Wilson and Marley claimed box office gold over the Christmas holiday. Film made over $50 million. http://bit.ly/dHIC
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Five Big Films Opening Christmas Day including Bedtimes Stories, Marley & Me, Benjamin Button, The Spirit and Valkyrie. http://bit.ly/1y7t
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Bedtimes Stories
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Marley & Me
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Benjamin Button
		</mention>
		<mention>
			The Spirit
		</mention>
		<mention>
			Valkyrie
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	2008 Holiday DVD Gift Ideas - a look at 20+ of the best films and tv shows that were released on dvd/blu-ray in 2008. http://bit.ly/YlZE
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	9-year-old Alex Greven from Colorado - who wrote a book for boys about how to talk to girls - now has film deal with Fox http://bit.ly/EFdA
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Harry Potter: The Exhibition will open at the Museum of Science and Industry in Chicago on April 30, 2009.  http://bit.ly/3J3rbv
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Harry Potter
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Keanu Reeves says he jumped when offered the chance to play an alien for new film "The Day the Earth Stood Still" http://bit.ly/61sS
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Day the Earth Stood Still
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Dark Knight Released on DVD and Blu-ray - some reviewers were not impressed with the extras on the discs. http://bit.ly/fA0K
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Dark Knight
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Noah Wylie returns as The Librarian once again this Sunday night on TNT.  http://bit.ly/mIqA
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			The Librarian
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The film version of the children's book classic Where The Wild Things Are has reportedly run into trouble. http://bit.ly/jgus
	<mentions>
		<mention>
			Where The Wild Things Are
		</mention>
	</mentions>
</tweet>
