<tweet>
	Rin's favorite manga genres
are: action, comedy, and
emotional drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@simiyu_hastings Booked in your complaint under ref.no. 816628 will be communicated to our respective office for action please,thank you.^SO
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NatbyNature you are truly classy. Always amazing seeing you in action out there. You remind me alot of women like Wendi Ritcher.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BitchesH8_Shan @EvilLynnnn a bitch going need a whole Hennessy bottle to take action lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	one thing i do not do is kiss these bitches.... that is the most passionate sexual action to me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm the type that's about more action than words
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@najamsethi sir before leaving government please take action on my bike stolen 1.5 year old FIR..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MMXNewscaster #WithCanvas3D, no serial director wud repeat the action scenes thrice!! After all it is 3D! ;) One look will kill & thrill..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	lights camera Action!!1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Syrian troops retake villages in Homs http://t.co/0JO4TkhWNf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lights camera action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just flew 155m in an action packed game of Jetpack Joyride on iPad. Any challengers? http://t.co/KkdrzmBPWi http://t.co/w2JKkkfG8f
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BREAKING NEWS All exams have been pstpned till further notice due 2 a strike action by the invigilators. visit http://t.co/cdrWQbxp7t
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why climate change is causing upset stomachs in Europe.  http://t.co/6jYO5onil6
</tweet>
<tweet>
	David Cameron and Prince Harry catch the bus for N ... http://t.co/udfju1qXcE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Today's plan of action: 1) Get kids to school. 2) get bike out.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Yeiizzle needa see that hello kitty bag in action! Lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@rankalee_ Be lot better if they did live action version of episode 12 concert scene. :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	So the live action movie is really coming out huh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps. Confucious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A fresh Killzone: Mercenary gameplay video has surfaced. Check out the PS Vita shooter in action - http://t.co/QtfzDiYf6J #psvita ^ADo
</tweet>
<tweet>
	VersCradle Rifle demonstration with different rifles including a scoped bolt action rifle and M4 Carbine.  Watch!  http://t.co/CalNeQmjLq
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Goodnight I hope I wake up to hear of some emmandrew action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If you want something you've never had, you'll have to do something you've never done. --> Choose to be BodyPROUD #Take #ACTION
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Implement long running processes a.k.a workflows in distributed systems - See Mass Transit Sagas in Action #dwx13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Interesting to see how the 'master' sets the 'caged parrot' free...action under SC directive...wl govt demolish the conflict of 'interest'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	British troops face longer tours in Afghanistan http://t.co/IPPS6zEmAz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	- 1TightSlap to @chetan_bhagat by PM through his action & by @gsurya through his Tweet  @abpnewstv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is like photography. Focus is an ingredient to have a good shot. I align my Vision with Soul and Action. *nuthin is beyond Reach*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps. Confucious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @bharti_vyas1: Angelina Joli has been brave and inspirational in telling the world about her double mastectomy..proactive with her actio…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I don't know whats more shocking the number of reported child abuse cases or the lack of legal action https://t.co/aO0qJhZh4B
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What does it take to really relax into life & let that begin to seep into the world of action & interaction? ~ Jeanette Amlie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps. Confucious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I wish companies would pay me to tweet shit. I would SO like a piece of that action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This movie rules. Boob action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Gulcin1905: His citizen Emanuel Eboue. He is also GALATASARAY'S player. What do you think about this racist action? @rihanna
</tweet>
<tweet>
	True RT @austinmadinga: @jkainja next time they should name prominent people in society from the area... if that will shame them into action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps. Confucious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@HenryLee95 @CallumWhiteee what 3 minutes worth of action compared to 120 I know which one ill take
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Schwarzenegger: Back in action for The Expendables 2! I'm having a fantastic time on set with Bruce and Sly in Bulgaria. http://t.co/6G…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Don't forget to tune in to Fox Sports from tomorrow to catch all the action from the 2013 Aussies!

Broadcast... http://t.co/PwX3BGyLR1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JFKennedys: Do not participate in the election puppet show that your enemies put on for you. Take direct action towards overthrowing th…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Post Offices refuse to sort mail in first industrial action for over 100 years via @Telegraph http://t.co/QuI0oc5b1K
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Loving AngularJS in Action by @briantford and @simpulton, *but* you guys really need a proofreader...I work for free if you're interested :)
</tweet>
