<tweet>
	“@larryyusuf: An Army Is Forming To Battle Patent Trolls http://t.co/4cAIhtQ27G << action forming.. ” about time! 2001 first time I saw it.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SriSriSpeaks: When you make 'Service' your sole purpose in life, it eliminates fear, brings focus in your mind, purposefulness in actio…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DavidHKMurray82 @The100Bus @MayorJodieH I like the thought of a @griffithchad action figurine.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why is @Wendys opposing "one of the greatest human rights success stories of our time?" http://t.co/z1WVEnNBT3 via @Sum_Of_Us
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Get_Headspace: We kick start our new @huffingtonpost feature off with 5 tips on integrating mindfulness in to your life http://t.co/4nX…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@VYRGOLICIOUS aw man hope they get u right so u can get back in action!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RCdeWinter: Thank the LA Times staffers who said they will quit if the Koch Brothers buy the newspaper - please sign/share, TY
 http://…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	snitches get stitches “@ACTION_JAXON31: @ThankMyCreator @__DonDon I told you she call is weiners Bro”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	to LA city:  in the next few days both campaigns will be calling you. Don't be rude.  It's democracy in action.  Just state your pref.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Evicted market traders consider legal action http://t.co/pGKepVFi0Y #London
</tweet>
<tweet>
	On the way to mars! bye. :D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@justinpickard @AlabasterC No urgent action. I seem to have a spare ticket (£8) so just let me know if you'd like it! :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PamGrier: Check out the latest issue of the Sierra Club Insider! http://t.co/Ya7eLC6c2m
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A-list lineup for the #NZSL in Action Awards this Sat @mojomathers @celiawbnz @ruthdysonmp @BatmanNZ @MissPivacHere @nortikiwi @smstargurl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	IS GEJ AFRAID OF D NORTH? EMERGENCY RULE and YET GOVERNOR, ELECTED OFFICIALS TO REMAIN IN OFFICE, WHO IS FOOLING WHO? WORD WITHOUT ACTION.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Will Smith pimping his son out to be an action movie star. Gawd.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Old phone back in action B-)
Yeah...!!! :-D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WE NEED ACTION AND LESS TALK AND LIKING PICTURES.  PUT YOUR ENERGY INTO HELPING FIND HIM - PLEASE ??????  HERE IS... http://t.co/7odk7jRMza
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @K_Seubert11: Change with action, not words.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MaximusInvest: Despite some overnight action the various implied vol curved did little. In  Fact 1M Gold is lower at 19.95 vs a close o…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Get_Headspace: We kick start our new @huffingtonpost feature off with 5 tips on integrating mindfulness in to your life http://t.co/4nX…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CoFemale Yes really. For defending the establishment clause in the constitution. We are a nation of laws, legal action is how to solve it.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Numbers in Action is a fucking sick video
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DalaiLama: It’s unrealistic to think that the future of humanity can be achieved only on the basis of prayer, what we need is to take a…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DHgovuk  "Over 50 cities, towns,villages taking local action to become #dementia friendly" good news for #carers of relatives w/ #dementia
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Talking bout that back seat action whoaaa lmao??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iamEROC: Less talk more action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@vernon_macklin looking forward for an action-packed game tonight! FTW! best of luck to the whole team.. :) #alloutsupport #neversaydie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Swamiparamtej: We all are tied. Realize it & do something to be free before its too late. Meditate and experience freedom in action. ht…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Our Executive Director Kumi Naidoo on civil disobedience and the importance of taking peaceful, direct action... http://t.co/aUZNhXRSDk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ask India to enforce laws that should protect hens from the cruelest confinement http://t.co/BNNra2NKbq (via @HSIglobal)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Get_Headspace: We kick start our new @huffingtonpost feature off with 5 tips on integrating mindfulness in to your life http://t.co/4nX…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And some of these girls be trapping niggas, playing with niggas emotions like they some action figures
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Y'all think I just be talking lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Angelina Jolie's mastectomy has inspired CNN's anchor to do the same due to her breast cancer. How one action inspires others :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	To Retrieve the Childhood: Arale Action Figure 3 Designs Optional $19.49 With Free http://t.co/3KrZt81k1i  #FullMetalHero
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The challenge for most of us isn’t knowing what to do. It is maintaining the sense of urgency to turn intention into action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TorieNaShay: “@ACTION_JAXON31: Got girls righting my name on they booty cheeks ?” byyyeee!!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@ImMissSexy: "The more you motivated by love, the more fearless and free your action will be." Dalai Lama"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ripe Nectarines on the Tree http://t.co/fjTQ2uGAtu
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Innovative Cloud based Machine Translation Platform KantanMT Announces Members Subscription Price Plans http://t.co/OklGsSfIHP #xl8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dream without action are just delusion
</tweet>
