<tweet>
	Turkish Airlines employees start strike action in a dispute over pay and the reinstatement of sacked workers - ... http://t.co/WCCzQTKgWW
</tweet>
<tweet>
	For every male action, there is a female overreaction
</tweet>
<tweet>
	FREE Barclays #startups seminar, all boroughs eligible, now running in Edmonton http://t.co/oyysaYMlj7 @harringayonline @haringeyJCP @_NLCF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	john kenneth galbraith~ buenos aires is often a spot wherever people reward courage and also take action in detailed particular cost-benefit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A friend pointed out that social media opens up society to superficial activism and less proactive action. There might be a point to this...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nighealthwatch: Radical action to reduce maternal mortality in #Nigeria: “FG Pays Pregnant Women to Attend Hospitals” http://t.co/BJZ63…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"An idea not coupled with action will never get any bigger than the brain cell it occupied". Hav a gr8t day.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @alavisher: Love David Gemmell? Looking for dark, heroic fantasy? Try Whispers of a Storm, the medieval action adventure http://t.co/fZK…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@eden_eritrea Unexpected action? Really. Oh, what a naive comment. Any thing is possibile. Expect the worst, hope for the better from Isreal
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Well, everyone knows friend is more important and I realised now from ur action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	National and local VCS bodies must work with wider civil society to promote vibrant community and voluntary action before it's too late!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SAADMALIK183: SOME MQM TWITTER USERS R CREATING THE FAKE ACCOUNTS OF FAMOUS PPL 2 PUT BLAME ON #PTI USERS TAKE ACTION #PTI @ArsalanGhum…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@HyakujuNoKaido Exactly.. Tobirama is the one that can't to fight Madara. I wanna see him in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ItsMindBIowing: Have you ever walked into a room & forgot why you went there? What  if thats god playing Sims & he just cancelled your …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Beings are owners of their action, heirs of their action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	ready to hit the road Gather http://t.co/1hhMzmC5hD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Leicester League Action tonight vs Hinckley and Bullet Dodgers. Good practice before East Qualifiers on Sunday May 19th. #Ligers #Dodgeball
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stand With Elizabeth Warren:  Let Students Borrow at the Same Low Rate Big Banks Get - http://t.co/yjvi7jZwhk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#iGetAnnoyedWhenPeople started to be over action. -_-
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Speaking today at press conference for 'Let's Do It' environmental action 18 May in #bosnia #bih see their site here http://t.co/K0uNlcb45R
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Another European Final day for #CFC.

#Benfica Vs. #CFC

#UELfinal at Amsterdam Arena

On Ten Action, 11.15 pm IST kick off

#OnTVToday
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We about that action y'all ain't about nothing
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@reedtimmerTVN N. IL look to get into the action for Sunday/Monday still?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disgusted by your action .
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SandyLGallagher: Establish a meaningful goal, one that will motivate you to take action and grow daily. http://t.co/M6G70NIfGl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Action man plaster haha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AnimeNewsNet: Interest: This Is Not the Live-Action Attack of Titan Poster http://t.co/PrSSANYdmU #anime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GoGingham: Stand w/ #Organic Valley farmers and ask Congress to support healthy and sustainable farming: http://t.co/nvGl9vxnB5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SkyCharlotte if this is so, I wonder will/can people take action for what would be a form of stealing!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Jetlife_Jack please direct me to the action kind sir
</tweet>
<tweet>
	JGB 10Y yield up again but the real action in the 5Y
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ShaseMoney you know I'm around for dat action lol just get at me man rs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I don't have to figure out my life. Allah got His own plans already in action. It just don't get any better than that.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Only you , yourself can determine what kind of person you are and what action you takes .
</tweet>
<tweet>
	No Action Talk Only
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Capello calls for action on racism: Fabio Capello believes Italian football authorities must follow the exampl... http://t.co/fgTrDTy6Gx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@D_Ramon02: @jaytotaylord we ain't really bout that talkin, bitch we bout that action!”--stop talking den hoe
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When you make 'Service' your sole purpose in life, it eliminates fear, brings focus in your mind, purposefulness in action, & long-term joy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Capello calls for action on racism: Fabio Capello believes Italian football authorities must follow the exampl... http://t.co/tmUyy69Zmb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Smaller QOF being considered by NHS England - inside skinny on future of GP contract from @sofialind_Pulse #nhs 
http://t.co/F9mXgB0GzG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#NCIS i want #S11E1 now i cant wait till next season starts specially i want ZIva and tony more in TIVA action I will miss my tuesday nights
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@joefooty is tensports showing tonights final in india? I dnt hv ten action here.. :(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@aishu_s @DelhiBureauWife if this has occurred inside the flight, the airline needs to take legal action immediately against offenders !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	we r a nation of armchair fighters not a bad thing but govt know we wont backup with action and thats why they do all they do direct action
</tweet>
