<tweet>
	Its not cheating if you send a text to your girlfriend telling her you love her during the action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@alansynnott in the context of news publishers, who rely on sources, this action is repressive
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thanks to Facebook Heineken has taken action: "We want to thank our consumers on-line for bringing this issue to our attention." WAY TO GO!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @EuropaLeague: UEFA is constantly monitoring the internet and reserves its right to take legal action in case of unauthorised sellers of…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Every job you take, getting tired is your risk!  "@assannisa: Talk Only No Action! Fuck you."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	attitudes and action-competent, ethical and right action with awareness are important to have
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	For every male action, there is a female overreaction.
- Newton's 3rd law of eMotion
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @UEFAcom: UEFA is constantly monitoring the internet and reserves its right to take legal action in case of unauthorised sellers offerin…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It Doesn't have to be pretty to look good. : Gather http://t.co/FUbvyLPR2K
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SeppBlatter: Appalled to read about racist abuse in Serie A last night. Tackling this issue is complex, but we’re committed to action, …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Funny how u meet some people for the 1st then meet them everywhr afta that. Like where the fuck were u all this tym?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Live-action #Abstraction - Leidy Churchman at Robert Miller is the Daily Pic by Blake Gopnik http://t.co/4t2Aiz7BN3 via @thedailybeast
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	time for action, conversating, we ralaxing kickin back, got you curious for thug passion now picture that
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps. Confucious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I only watch Action Movies. Because. I am. A Man! ....What are you talking about? I don't know who Nicholas Sparks is?......#AwkwardSilence
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Everytime I check http://t.co/EYB1IDntTI I get a bit more frustrated.Come on family & friends.Even £1 is appreciated for such a worthy cause
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@georgie_bailey  lost in action after first Maths exam.. #bringbaileyback
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps. Confucious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#EpicLiveBabes Julie is currently Live Free Chat http://t.co/YlSktxTl2m
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps. Confucious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Oprah_World: Whether you think you’re ready or not, just start right now.  There is magic in action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	pls Stop ur childish action~~~~~
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Julian Knight is taking legal action to get himself a playstation.
Maybe they could just give him the power cord so he can knock himself
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @EuropaLeague: UEFA is constantly monitoring the internet and reserves its right to take legal action in case of unauthorised sellers of…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps. Confucious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @EuropaLeague: UEFA is constantly monitoring the internet and reserves its right to take legal action in case of unauthorised sellers of…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	EFFORT is just a small word that requires a great action if they can't afford to give a little one then they don't deserve to receive one?~?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JakeMiosge: Entrago is going to be amazing! Excited for everyone to see this project in action! Not long left! #JoinChrisBrown http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GreatestQuotes: "You can adopt the attitude there is nothing you can do, or you can see the challenge as your call to action." - Cather…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Grooving to the new @ScreamOfficial album!  My head in danger of falling off due to excessive bobbing action!  Rock on! :-)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#LiveBabes Julie is currently Live Free Chat http://t.co/9sC2z7y5EU #Horny
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#LiveBabes Tenderness is currently Live Free Chat http://t.co/3b0ApJU8HD #Horny
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @jumurke: Whether you think you’re ready or not, just start right now. There is magic in action"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#LiveBabes Julie is currently Live Free Chat http://t.co/lj0X4QACaR #Horny
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AFLTribunal dont like to be wrong you lot. The two closest people to that action told you what happened yet you'd rather use a scratchy vid
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#LiveWomen Tenderness is currently Live Free Chat http://t.co/Q5bz2A7PgL #boobs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RediTlhabi: great that Zuma responded to desperate cry of a mother& community fed up with drugs& crime. Positive step,NOW ACTION pls fr…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#LiveBabes Tenderness is currently Live Free Chat http://t.co/HPxYNSU0nr #Horny
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#EpicLiveBabes Julie is currently Live Free Chat http://t.co/fLHXVgI7k8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@RE_Spiffmeister: I want action shots of me playing so bad but nobody ever goes to my games it won't happen." @Tyler_Napkins =photographer
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teaching without words, performing without action, these are the way of the master
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LostWords_: You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Oprah_World: Whether you think you’re ready or not, just start right now.  There is magic in action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We ain't really with that talking...we bout that action.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Oprah_World: Whether you think you’re ready or not, just start right now.  There is magic in action
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @UEFAcom: UEFA is constantly monitoring the internet and reserves its right to take legal action in case of unauthorised sellers offerin…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You don't have to be afraid to put your dreams in action.
</tweet>
