<tweet>
	adventure time with @_Lana_Marie_
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Idiot and the Elephant http://t.co/aKCTBkyram
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Am I lost or Am I on an Adventure?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You should see them perform live here at Ocean Adventure in Subic! #WILD Regram from @chinoluipio :) http://t.co/UnxBKX0iug
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Looking for a unique hen do? You'll love this outdoor adventure! Featuring Pure Flavour and The Original Hut Company http://t.co/2XyWgBu6K9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@WallSuptSimon best wishes on you next adventure! Great blog entry.  -mrod
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wish adventure time was on .. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Sabrinalahais: adventure time new episodes released last night. mehehhehe
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ErinZariah: In Napa with my mom for Mother's Day.  But who am I kidding -- do we need an excuse to go on an adventure?  She's my favori…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Good luck to @AnthGarbutt as his amazing cycle adventure draws closer. Keeping everything crossed for you
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I've always wanted to go take a adventure with someone
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sam_concepcion: Just got splashed by a dolphin here at Ocean Adventure in subic! Watch out for it on Pop Myx!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I always knew something was fishy about Adventure Time.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ItsMeganLaRae: everyone says that hate adventure time but once you start watching it you just like get sucked in and you never wanna st…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just watched a preview of Guwapings: The First Adventure. Guwapings: The First Adventure: http://t.co/jlvCLuYgYV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @shekharkapur: Lessons of Life: The past a memory. An addiction. Future an unknown. An adventure. Change is nature of creativity. Why no…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm off on a adventure, Mr. Rager;
Tell me some of your  stories, Tell us of your travels.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Here's a great quote - The biggest adventure you can take is to live the life of your dreams-Oprah Winfrey   Are you living your dreams?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	http://t.co/UIgyse1mIS “In the creative state, life’s an adventure. You love the exhilaration of every single moment. It’s the oppos...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I barely watch tv but when I do its history channel or adventure time . #thatsmyshit #hateoneit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I need someone with alot of Xbox games I'm bored of the few I got I need more!!!!! Adventure more than likely lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Apparently I have Adventure Time season one on my laptop.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	everyone says that hate adventure time but once you start watching it you just like get sucked in and you never wanna stop thinkin about it
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sammy_lou85: An advert for islands of adventure just came on @tween1 #harrypotter #waterrides #excited #1week2days
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And adventure time.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AmazingPhil: out of all the christmas adventure prizes my dad chose mine & dan's sex tape
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AmazingPhil: out of all the christmas adventure prizes my dad chose mine & dan's sex tape
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Is it Urii Nightly Adventure Time? :3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AmazingPhil: out of all the christmas adventure prizes my dad chose mine & dan's sex tape
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'll be Marceline and you be Finn, and lets go off to adventure time in the far away land
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Morning all, another days graft on Doris (series2#Landrover)off to #landrover Spring Adventure at Harrogate this week end,
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DarkndLovely_ y'all got to be home to hold down the fort while we on our adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chicken Adventure Begins -  We have decided to begin raising chickens, and are... http://t.co/HGp00aoOeB
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure time in the 206
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Buying brand medications from resellers is a tricky adventure! Choose trusted vendors!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hipstering it up on a food adventure with @geliee ??? http://t.co/rvgC9HTzaQ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Dread_Confusion: Everyday a new adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i love adventure time it's so weird and funny lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just this last episode of Adventure Time && then I'm off too sleep, if not ima be in big trouble with @CossioHD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Solid adventure with @GinaHuss
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Alexander William Gaskarth how was Emoji adventure hahahaha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	not enough adventure time merchandise in this country
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Marybelle Quinata speaking to participants of a Humatak Watershed Adventure.  Marybelle is the coordinator of our... http://t.co/zWi0S0WJvf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SwansBlog: Swansea City goal ace Michu vows to stay with Swans ahead of European adventure http://t.co/r1bSienFcD #swans
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@hauntedanna Things pop in from Salem's Lot and The Stand. It's a crazy adventure.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Cool_Running: Heading out for a family adventure? Here are the essential items you should bring with you: http://t.co/bNgufY7nhk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oh yeah, before I forget, gonna be streaming later. Another classic adventure game for all to enjoy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BackAtWaldo: @TRAPG0DHEiDi Sounds like an adventure to me.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Think of how cool a Bear Grylls, Steve Erwin adventure would have been
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure time..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Baby you're an adventure, so let me come and explore ya ;)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Everyday a new adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	wow Alissa got me adventure time on dvd for my birthday I'm happy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MMXNewscaster #WithCanvas3D I can flirt around with the dual SIM - dual dostis, dual Adventure, dual Roller-Coaster  ;-P
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TRAPG0DHEiDi Sounds like an adventure to me.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sljackson87 they're gone! It's sad. Even though adventure time and regular show are actually really funny.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Tnation_37 it a cartoon baby on adventure time Foo lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is like an adventure. Sometimes the sun is shining, sometimes you encounter a storm...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Our first podcast will be available on the blog tonight! We will discuss the curious, mysterious, exciting adventure of Benjamin Button!
</tweet>
