<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	All I need is a decent adventure game to keep me busy, then this Abuja boredom won't be a thing.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @NVR_Ruimtevaart: "NASA, a Human Adventure" exhibition opens in Utrecht on 13 June. Watch the preview of this exciting event: http://t.c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Our new blog post: Adventure-moons in the heart of #Africa with @governorscamps http://t.co/QrUY9ovA3i #travel #ttot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What kind of man would live a life without daring?Is life so sweet that we should criticize men that seek adventure?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bhairavigoswami do u have ur own horses in Mumbai? I am from Army and love horses too. We run an adventure camp
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Went on an adventure with @kevinleemcbee and found this. http://t.co/C8HlQBmkp2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure times with @skitzo_dancer are the highlight of my life. <3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Would you leave your home country for the one you love? — Yea.. Why not.. I'm always up for adventure! http://t.co/ved7s0fbve
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RanbirAddict: 'Those roller coasters are the maximum adventure I can take' Ranbir Kapoor on Adventure holidays! CUTE!! He's so much lik…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Rave_Hard: BMO Noire is THE BEST episode of adventure time ever made
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @FatWill_Laflare: So who invented them sloth pictures....cause it's the funniest shit ever for no reason
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I changed it to Adventure Time coz I'm awesome http://t.co/kwpZa7VO5N
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dan Brown's new book - Inferno - is available today. Come and get your copy of Robert Langdon's next adventure NOW.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@flyinglotus scored an Adventure Time episode?! How does it just keep getting better....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HammersndVogues: "@Adventure_Gang: @HammersndVogues but they stay bring up old memories in old pain they just know how to cut you deep"…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Get Wild In Ireland - 7 Day Coastline Adventure http://t.co/JqZFTblWPB
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TimOfLegend We're a new adventure games company inspired by your work and KickStarter. If you'd send some folk our way, it'd make us smile.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@Adventure_Gang: @HammersndVogues but they stay bring up old memories in old pain they just know how to cut you deep"and ur right
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RanbirAddict: 'Those roller coasters are the maximum adventure I can take' Ranbir Kapoor on Adventure holidays! CUTE!! He's so much lik…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BMO Noire is THE BEST episode of adventure time ever made
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Ampera reflects the spirit of adventure. Unleash the spirit and be inspired by this video of a true pioneer http://t.co/usf07Vpb9X
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bathmums Get your little monkeys, bring them down to explore Adventure Gym. Today 2-3, £4.00 per child Childre aged 4 and under
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sunnydisposish @claypotricee hey dudes if i order http://t.co/ypgMVLvDQg this can i ship it to your house??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watch the epic new adventure featuring Captain Morgan. http://t.co/TH8HyhD44F
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bornavictory_ Mondays are ADVENTURE TIME!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	??????? Her ideas were far in (  ) of the age in which she lived. ? 1.adventure 2.advance 3.addition 4.advantage
</tweet>
<tweet>
	todays adventure will take me to Eastbourne #TobyOnTour
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fucktyler: “@LolCoffee: @fucktyler If you could get on any TV show, What show would it be?” ADVENTURE TIME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching Into the Wild makes me wanna go on an adventure. Well except for the dying part
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheNCSNetwork: Are you in Lewes today? Curious about #NCS facing a challenging & adventure filled summer? Get down to @sussexdowns betw…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Alot of niggas died trying to come up
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Karebear1794: Maybe, I'll stay up long enough to see the sunrise. Going on a picture adventure. #adventure @hecalledmeseven
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @croftersorganic: Thank you @teensturngreen we look forward to the next great adventure with you! #ConsciousCollege #organic #NonGMO #fo…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ovum Industries Congress charting a weather forecast for the ICT industry  ... essential info for planning your next ICT adventure! #OIC13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ndhhh: "I know I mess things up sometimes, but I really try." -Adventure Time
</tweet>
<tweet>
	No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	my adventure begins here. I am in Vilnius now chatting with my frend Vilius Streckis about everything and... http://t.co/zHi52JKRoe #VNO
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Decided to wake my mom up and make her lay with me and watch Adventure time until i fall asleep<3 cure for everything. #goodnight
</tweet>
<tweet>
	-stares absently at the leaves in the tree, recalling my amazonian "adventure"-
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Maybe, I'll stay up long enough to see the sunrise. Going on a picture adventure. #adventure @hecalledmeseven
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @NVR_Ruimtevaart: "NASA, a Human Adventure" exhibition opens in Utrecht on 13 June. Watch the preview of this exciting event: http://t.c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pee-Wee's Big Adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sam_concepcion: Just got splashed by a dolphin here at Ocean Adventure in subic! Watch out for it on Pop Myx!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AKDread OMG I love woona! I haven't finished the comic yet though, surprising cuz I love MSPA based adventure comics XD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Skintightshibby woahhh that's a real adventure! Write me a letter if you get time, I want to read about these funny occurrences.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@LarrysBear On this excruciatingly painful note, I have to sleep now. Thanks for the feels adventure! XD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sydneeey011: It was fun going on an adventure with @KayyCray and @RandeeznuTS, but I need sleep ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@rotl2013 Be sure to let us all know how you get on. Will be great to follow that adventure.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Find a boy/girl who travels because you deserve a life of adventure and possibility. You deserve to live light and embrace simplicity #date
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"I know I mess things up sometimes, but I really try." -Adventure Time
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Now, what to do? What's next? Excited for the next adventure! Another rollercoaster ride :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @disneywords: No matter what happens to me, nothing ever happens. But, who knows someday an adventure just may happen to me? –Piglet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Those roller coasters are the maximum adventure I can take' Ranbir Kapoor on Adventure holidays! CUTE!! He's so much like me in this case.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @hecalledmeseven: Do it for the adventure.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure? It should have counting for hide and seek years ago.
</tweet>
