<tweet>
	The adventure of jimmy neutron/m\ yeaaaaaaah
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@megan_lau best use of an adventure time meme :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TooMuchSciFi: And I want it all to be an adventure.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @turbo_023: Glad that my soul mate came to visit had tones of fun From swimming to in n out to our adventure and trolling in davis Ha lo…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @alavisher: Love David Gemmell? Looking for dark, heroic fantasy? Try Whispers of a Storm, the medieval action adventure http://t.co/fZK…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is an adventure.
Dare it.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm playing the gorgeous card battle & mini-garden game "Valkyrie Crusade"! Let's go on an adventure in this world together!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My life: my choice,my adventure and my style
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TScpAries: Aries needs excitement and adventure whereas Taurus needs security and stability. http://t.co/XsrPSVyky5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DammitOmar: But baby you're an adventure
So please let me come explore you
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What a fun tweet up #wine30 today @TravelLaneCo Adventure Center. I do love all regions of @Oregon_Wine!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Every night is an adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I want to have an Adventure Time marathon. This will be added to my summer to do list. Lolol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thennnnnn came home. Re-watched loiter squad and now it's a adventure time marathon !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @bdgrabinski: I'd pay a monthly fee if I could get Siri to sound like BMO from ADVENTURE TIME.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@FierceSavior adventure. Hey (She points to two that catch her eye) this ones nice or maybe ~ http://t.co/cRdMqLcIt1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Noooo dad stop using netflix! I want to watch adventure timeee D;
</tweet>
<tweet>
	These wings about to slap
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@kmjw_: I wanna go adventure cove :( especially hot weather like thisss.” <<
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_OMJeeJee: Scary seeing your name after R.i.P.....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure time
</tweet>
<tweet>
	adventure time for Megan ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"That's because I always belive that we can meet each other again" - Takeru [Digimon Adventure 1]
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I wanna go adventure cove :( especially hot weather like thisss.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	But baby you're an adventure
So please let me come explore you
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Let your adventure reading take flight - The Egypt adventure thriller series http://t.co/MeDzeTnqgm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	my life is so full of adventure ok
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That was an adventure...never again. @christine_ake @yas_minb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I really love adventure time (':
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fxck adventure time funny
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure Tip - The Boy Scouts motto "Always Be Prepared" is a motto to live by.  Keep a BSA Fieldbook by the toilet and prepare at home.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Invitation to Free Desert Adventure on May 31 - http://t.co/DyycCHM2CC
</tweet>
<tweet>
	theyre gonna be all fresh for my weekend adventure with best friend #thankgod
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure is not outside man; it is within. -David Grayson
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Hidden Chamber in the Great Sphinx is a children's action adventure story http://t.co/HWXwx352wf @LindaACadose
</tweet>
<tweet>
	& now adventure club started playing...pandora is on one
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why was Abe Lincoln a God on adventure time??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Don't think I'd want to be on an adventure camp today,  weather awful! Abe is definatley coming home wet and dirty
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Alright, Robert Langdon, let's see what's in store for you on your fourth adventure. #Inferno
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@VampyBitme What an adventure that tour must've been! I wonder which #Ghibli film this fellow derives from... Which short did you watch?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@planetjedward of course you guys everyday is like a new adventure =:) #Jepic
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Separated by fate, joined by destiny. Whispers of a Storm, a dark, epic fantasy. Experience adventure today! http://t.co/fZKEbrzyi4 #kindle
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LisaFLloyd: Connect with your sense of adventure today! What makes you feel excited, expansive... on fire? You are the hero of... http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Now I need season 4 of Adventure Time..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	watching adventure time woohooo
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching The Chronicles of Narnia: The Voyage of the Day Treader with my adventure-loving little nymph. I love Holiday weekends!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	mich and xuan watching adventure time at my house hahahaha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@laouraholt @lauren_jane95 @amiebethcarr we was going on an adventure ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I miss @_Dyamond_ she be one of the people down with me for an adventure!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm playing the gorgeous card battle & mini-garden game "Valkyrie Crusade"! Let's go on an adventure together!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Experience Adventure on a Charter Fishing Trip in Charleston, SC - #chs #fishing http://t.co/woF6W099OE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure time :D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Be careful going in search of adventure - it's ridiculously easy to find.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @kateynicoley: Just close your eyes and let's go on an adventure. @rileyy_shaffer
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_alltimelowlife: @YupJustKirsten yes omg thank you 
adventure time > any other show
</tweet>
