<tweet>
	Watch a life drawing turn into a 3D animation... "Life Drawing at The Book Club": http://t.co/YyLo45XVMa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @arrahman: Had a sneek preview of Rajini Sir's motion capture results for one of the songs from Kochadiyan..looks like animation on Ster…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @2454tadreeb: Don't forget to join us at @ADU_tweets today at 2pm to learn all about our Gaming Academy & @CartoonNetwork Animation Acad…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Saga_210 animation or not?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Triple ICT, it's going to be evil but the fast is to finish my animation
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheTuftyWomble: @BeenieBomb :D also not rush on the drawing/animation, the dayz series might have something special for you to animate!…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Do not stop beleiving in yourself, you are this nation's future - Animation Art
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Photos - or 873 of them - are powerful, as this Getty Images stop-motion animation "From Love to Bingo" shows. http://t.co/YgcWLQVpsP
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @designindaba: Africa's biggest animation studio will soon be its biggest gaming developer too @TriggerfishZA http://t.co/okPi4nMUia
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I added a video to a @YouTube playlist http://t.co/UnMwJIGOsc The Last Train To Paradise! (Minecraft Animation)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Need to make a new video for you company,contact us and well do it all !

Watch our work on youtube by typing Animation Art dubai, Enjoy!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In the food industry find out why thousands are asking about the BFAWU short animation on why also latest news  http://t.co/auX5uSf6PS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	emp-lit class,this week:representing video on paper.Sonny's game http://t.co/G426Ucf30A stage cues,animation,flip book? must think of others
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Paranorman was interesting. I loved the stunning animation & charming characters but the climax fell flat for me. Also not child-friendly.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Shingeki no Kyojin. Probs the best anime to come out this spring. The animation & plot are A++! Reading the manga now, too. #imsuchageek {8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Alola07 you should make a short animation of you two x'D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @arrahman: Had a sneek preview of Rajini Sir's motion capture results for one of the songs from Kochadiyan..looks like animation on Ster…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JacobDiesels some kind of polish 2d animation conference which i bet will be shit haha and then small convention
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Video: Academy Leader project. Traditional animation. Inked cells, scanned into and colored in Photoshop.... http://t.co/uFGGm3ZThJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Motorized TV cart, the perfect hi-tech solution for boardrooms, classrooms etc. Watch the 3D animation video now. http://t.co/RCAMgrPK43
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sweet baby Jesus I have one finished animation final #iseethelight
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Animated Explainers The Cleveland Show officially cancelled - In would seem as though Cleveland Brown's days of ha... http://t.co/bVvRREvt7m
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Animated Explainers Sesame Street welcomes a new amigo - Sesame Street acknowledges diversity with a multi-ethnic ... http://t.co/dlrV0gTIkv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Animated Explainers Planes sequel Fire & Rescue gets a teaser poster! http://t.co/KeVzAfMM8c
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Animated Explainers Forget disco ball Mike, try Spaceship Earth Mike http://t.co/YDlke9yila
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@matteopenzo i liked that fire animation :) #mblt13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Kuma_Style dude love the little animation intro of your review with the bear taking pictures also nice photo http://t.co/AYMGx3jjQe
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Animation of Wilt Chamberlain Talking About His Life http://t.co/gn1XpE13yx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Robot Chicken Couch Gag | THE SIMPSONS | ANIMATION on FOX: http://t.co/bto0NtDOrR vía @youtube
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ComedyHighTweet Please sign and retweet Help me get my own idea to the White House to build a Special Ed college!
http://t.co/vakdm3HZJD…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @pudiharicharan: #Epic is indeed epic. Brilliant out of this world animation experience. It takes you inside a world never seen before. …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Is it sad that I want the mail application in OSX to make a paper airplane animation when I click send on my messages ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	watched jack reacher...did some animation...watched iron man 3...about to animate some more. now if i could just get paid for this!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	jiyong just posted photo on instagram with t-shirt initial G and beside him girl with t-shirt animation K. everyone knows who 'K' omg lmao
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CryButNotCry so far Im talking about the animation/characters and the songs ^-^!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/AOulWEhHTG Robot Chicken Couch Gag | THE SIMPSONS | ANIMATION on FOX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And it interfaces well with almost every graphics/animation software plus it supports most scripting languages...its just awesome!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PeterSheff Blockout keys for my zombie animation, still a work in progress. Eventually it'll turn into pixel art http://t.co/vjMqXSKWTV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BeenieBomb :D also not rush on the drawing/animation, the dayz series might have something special for you to animate! ;) <3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SudhishKamath do you enjoy animation flicks? That's news to me :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@immaSRKholic Please sign and retweet Help me get my own idea to the White House to build a Special Ed college!
http://t.co/vakdm3HZJD…
Thx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Animation of Wilt Chamberlain Talking About His Life http://t.co/nj2CN9wShJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MekennaMelvin Please sign and retweet Help me get my own idea to the White House to build a Special Ed college!
http://t.co/vakdm3HZJD…
Thx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @montyoum: I started animating in grade school making fight animation flip books in the corners of the books I was supposed to be reading
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Epic is indeed epic. Brilliant out of this world animation experience. It takes you inside a world never seen before. perfect summer treat
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@urBuddha2me Please sign and retweet Help me get my own idea to the White House to build a Special Ed college!
http://t.co/vakdm3HZJD…
Thx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Interesting perspective: Animation in email http://t.co/ASPujJ03QB
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@KerriD16 Please sign and retweet Help me get my own idea to the White House to build a Special Ed college!
http://t.co/vakdm3HZJD…
Thanks
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/UFjaWcxdKG Comet ISON C/2012-S1 Coming in 2013 (Animation) The Brightest Comet in Human History!
</tweet>
