<tweet>
	Watched Escape From Planet Earth. The same thing with most of the ordinary animation movies. Boring story. 6/10.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	animation is so impressive ///
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The fruit of my 5-minute twitch tv animation session.http://t.co/zuoaQdulZ0
</tweet>
<tweet>
	we are watching flash animation projects in class
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@Nathan3DWilkes: OMG! You were an animator on Being Bradford Dillman! That's one of my favourite shorts of all time! Superb Animation!” :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	going to do an android customised boot animation later~
</tweet>
<tweet>
	im sometimes more interested in the animation of background characters in cartoons than the main characters.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Congrats to our winner of our first animation quiz contest. U will get a deluxe tshirt from wiz http://t.co/xzQ2Fg48mZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Check out my day 64! Cartoon animation with @Destorm @J355f4c3 @Cosondra and some bowling! http://t.co/IgrpNPXkgX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@kelseyrsd do computer animation for me in exchange?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Google has released the animation of Earth timelapse imagery showing the earth's surface over time, using high resolution satellite image..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	com animation sucked all my brain cells.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@catfish_tweets OMG! You were an animator and Being Bradford Dillman! That's one of my favourite shorts of all time! Superb Animation!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@leamicheless does your animation bar look like this? http://t.co/bSO9uiRUsR
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Their animation style and Justice League are the only things that keep me going back to DC Comics.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	S/O  to @GuttamindDotCom  and his animation  I watched it for 2 hours on YouTube @adultswim  should be calling soon my man GOOD STUFF !!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#CGMantra offers a lot of professional Animation course #gaming  web designing courses suited to students http://t.co/oPo6tfFvV7
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SixDinnersLater: @frenchlottie Thanks for following Here's a new press piece we love http://t.co/HRzD2EwdqS & Jim for a bit more info h…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@tigertub in ur lame ass animation class
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rockstar Games' L.A Noire pushed the bar in facial animation with its MotionScan technology. Did you play it? http://t.co/umCGPV6wkX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @judacris: #bronies are the folks who scans every frame of pony animation and go "HEY. THAT'S A MISTAKE. WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#bronies are the folks who scans every frame of pony animation and go "HEY. THAT'S A MISTAKE. WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Found the Bravestarr animation stills @xxNerdOrgasmxx posted to me in my old room, thought I'd lost them! #EyesoftheHawk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@fucktyler Favourite animation of all time??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	working on a new animation
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Animation is unique. Numbers for names. Yes, unique. Though the plot probably isn't as unique. http://t.co/veA0jdGMnn #GetGlue #9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Google has released the animation of Earth timelapse imagery showing the earth's surface over time, using high resolution satellite image..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How did feathers evolve? Interesting animation, involving dinosaurs. http://t.co/tgl9djGHZU
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Infographic animation really fun but not easy. It took away my time and sleep ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Photoset: Yesterday i went to this animation office that i just began training there, me and the manager... http://t.co/aNZzBVpMYG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Going to make a quick 5-minute animation before going to bed. Care to watch? http://t.co/NCjFAHSdLh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	is really not sure what to make of the motivation behind all of the humor-ridden CGI Animation Videos that are on offer, courtesy of @NMAtv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The show Rocket Monkeys that I worked on is nominated for a three Leo awards! Good luck team #leoawards #animation #television
</tweet>
<tweet>
	gusto ko talaga ng maya 3D animation software D:
</tweet>
<tweet>
	never want to do another project w/ mass amounts of video & animation again.  The amount of endless tweaks makes me want to tear my hair out
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'll be happy when my FMP, advert, ident and animation are all handed in :)
</tweet>
