<tweet>
	Google has released the animation of Earth timelapse imagery showing the earth's surface over time, using high resolution satellite image..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	woohoo animation done, just need to final spray my model and finish my presentation! :D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tomorrow is Animation. Yesss im free from Final Exam ....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@assassin__ezio Not sure… Two thousand something? I was in suspended animation for a very long time.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Our new animation on our homepage, I hope you like it http://t.co/qDL3yc2eBa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ini asli?? RT @fistimdr: Shingekyo live action movie with US' animation technology and German-face actor
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oreo celebrates 100th birthday with animated typography treat http://t.co/Rq27OOU46X
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CL_Journal: latest animation on student expectations from Leaving to Learn http://t.co/GDvfHOmune
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@OugonNoOu I'm watching an animation on Pelton wheels to understand wtf my hw is talking about.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Rather than create an animation of a firework, I taught the computer to render a firework, so each one is slightly unique.” SLD #FOWD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @cartoonart: The Latino Comics Expo just keeps getting bigger and better! http://t.co/sokHTF9zcS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	huhu the animation is so flawless I WANT TO CRY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Google has released the animation of Earth timelapse imagery showing the earth's surface over time, using high resolution satellite image..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Epic animation from Fox out 24th May-Check out featurette at http://t.co/N3E8qvHWYy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@melmation yep. My bad. Animation event is Thursday, not Wednesday! Oops.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fistimdr: Shingekyo live action movie with US' animation technology and German-face actors/actresses.NAH.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Google has released the animation of Earth timelapse imagery showing the earth's surface over time, using high resolution satellite image..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Brilliantly funny animation starts @pgorgels talk - using over 200 images from the collection using Rijksstudio
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MichelleSuiter That show was great. Such great animation, voice acting, etc.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @eddieharran: Where can i find an outsourcing firm that does 3D animation well?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	10 Award Winning and Beautiful 3D Animation Videos and TV Commercials  http://t.co/DRQwN39ilC via @mywebneel
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oreo celebrates 100th birthday with animated typography treat  @CreativeBloQ http://t.co/EwnsKAwigY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Looking forward to Danganronpa Animation.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Charming little animation. I love their faces. http://t.co/IVez1AoPMa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Study about how to do animation in 3D at college.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fistimdr: Shingekyo live action movie with US' animation technology and German-face actors/actresses.NAH.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The animation bananas in pyjamas is the biggest joke like what impostors!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Never expected to find this one
http://t.co/vwlYJcC9jC
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fistimdr: Shingekyo live action movie with US' animation technology and German-face actors/actresses.NAH.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fistimdr: Shingekyo live action movie with US' animation technology and German-face actors/actresses.NAH.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fistimdr: Shingekyo live action movie with US' animation technology and German-face actors/actresses.NAH.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fistimdr: Shingekyo live action movie with US' animation technology and German-face actors/actresses.NAH.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @fistimdr: Shingekyo live action movie with US' animation technology and German-face actors/actresses.NAH.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oreo‘s #WonderfilledAnthem by Owl City. Dip into this feelgood video and share the love. http://t.co/A8d9bcXeK4 #animation #oreo
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@PrimeIsHere haha when they first created the animation by any chance lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Always like the lyrics to Olvidate 
http://t.co/hS0uTi7M5E
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I found nice site for cursive writing http://t.co/LAWZfBmmaL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	By some strange chance I always happen to be listening to songs like this one everytime Reina post adorable photos http://t.co/WgUraJfJcI
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Google has released the animation of Earth timelapse imagery showing the earth's surface over time, using high resolution satellite image..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@gruffghost if i could animate i would make a lil animation of you waking up in bed inside of a pizza hut surrounded by pizzas 4 u 4 ur bday
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ellrics the animation style might put u off at first (when they're fighting witches) but just ignore that lmao
</tweet>
