<tweet>
	RT @firstshowing: Awww man! New Richard Curtis love story with time travel thrown in?! This looks totally adorable/amazing. Trailer: http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	???!"@Stupid__Comedy: *Standing on a high balcony*   Normal person: What a breathtaking view! Me: I could totaly snipe that guy from here."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I write poetry & got offers to do stand up comedy #YoonEvenKnowIt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	True!"@Stupid__Comedy: *Standing on a high balcony*   Normal person: What a breathtaking view! Me: I could totaly snipe that guy from here."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	On the train to the big smoke for cigars and comedy, for which tickets are still available - http://t.co/0mXuQ6AMg4

@cigarmonologues
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @THlNK2: Life is a tragedy when seen in close-up, but a comedy in long-shot. - Charlie Chaplin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SarahMillican75 2 tickets booked for Feb 13th show in Belfast,no pressure but expecting utter comedy brilliance! :-)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/gUkbiw2WPd Singam Tamil Movie Comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I dont have his number, he doesnt have mine, we both have his mum's and of course, she's switched it off. Comedy of errors scripting here.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@dg4G This is a piece of comedy genius! Thanks for again for dinner, I couldn't eat breakfast this I was so stuffed.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@oxfordtimes @OxfordshireLife Free musical comedy gig @thekillingworth  this Sunday 8pm Spandex Ballet http://t.co/XvLZyaVK08
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Those lovely pals @smallportions asked us a few questions about our nights, and this is what came of it: http://t.co/Fu7pGFj1xu Good times!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @1PhoebeJTonkin: I just watched 2nd ep of Zach Stone and its truly HILARIOUS and @shelleyhennig is perfect comedy gold. #fayana #forlife
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thanks to @AndyJTee for uploading this rippa about the highs and lows of being the office jokester... READ: http://t.co/Wn46aYxVjS #comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What kind of movies do you like? — action one, horror,comedy http://t.co/IXmOGwaAUH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Vinayam clashes with nan padam eduka poren NPEP and 7 kabadi players thriller vs comedy vs actioncomedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A Case Study from the recent work we did for the Comedy Club
http://t.co/zILldlCNfc
#weAREevvnt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mau coba stand-up comedy ah.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ciddy really r the comedy club that keep on giving #massivemongs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Caught #GoGoaGone yesterday.. Still not over it... An urban comedy I'd call it.. Good shit @thevirdas super comic timing as always
</tweet>
<tweet>
	this is comedy!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @dhanushkraja: How is this for a comedy ? Me on the piano and rahman sir standing by me :) http://t.co/0U0IMXarWT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Manchester City Comedy Club...you couldn't write this stuff. Laughing stock of Europe.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BellaSwannID: Did you ever wonder what's the worst breakup text ever typed? Check out these to see the top 15! http://t.co/kDhMz0N9te
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'better life without kids' says who? @Stupid__Comedy: Sex is 10 times better without condoms. But life is (cont) http://t.co/i8KlnW0bmf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @smallportions: Good Night! @Monster_Comedy is the latest (second) in our series hearing from the people behind great comedy nights http…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedy is all about timing
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just can't take the pre-recorded laughing on these subpar comedy shows anymore. ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	LOL "@Stupid__Comedy: My girlfriend got mad and told me that I treat her like a child. So I gave her a sticker for standing up for herself."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How to know when you partied too hard last night. http://t.co/Zli9AhU4v6
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Holy ish, I can't believe this is the first time I've watched this. Awesome -> PLEASE STOP DOING THE HARLEM SHAKE http://t.co/7EcHCQPUN0
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thekillingworth: The Social Presents musical comedy from Spandex Ballet this Sunday from 8pm! Not for the faint hearted!! http://t.co/M…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	On tour in the states.  Doing my best comedy.  (in suggestion boxes)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	These tweeps that tell us to follow stupid comedy's mxm -__-
</tweet>
<tweet>
	AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHHA HAHAHAHAHAHHAHA Oh Arthur Sinodinos I thought the Comedy Festival was over! #TheDrum
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#SHELL "@Stupid__Comedy: Cop: Do you know why I was following you? Me: Because I have good tweets?"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	He stared at her, her expression setting fire to something in his chest. "And it matters to you what I think?" #IRInk http://t.co/cblx38jB1H
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Did you ever wonder what's the worst breakup text ever typed? Check out these to see the top 15! http://t.co/kDhMz0N9te
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@jazzt There's loads. Freedom of Speech and all that but there is not a lot of comedy mileage in mastectomy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @smallportions: Good Night! @Monster_Comedy is the latest (second) in our series hearing from the people behind great comedy nights http…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	LOL"@Stupid__Comedy: STUPID FACT: Take your age, subtract 13 from it. That's exactly how old you were thirteen years ago. RT if it is true."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	On tour in the states.  Doing my best comedy.  (in suggestion boxes)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A raunchy musical comedy about a libertine transvestite gardener from outer space - The Rockery Horticulture Picture Show.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Google's Eric Schmidt recently made an appearance on NPR's Wait Wait??¦ Don't Tell Me!, which is weekly comedy trivia show...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I met you, you're smile at me. I give you some comedy, and we are laughing together. And when you smile, that's my happiness (?´?`?)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PollocksNo_5: Luke Dunphy is a comedy genius.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Greg Ellis's show at comedy fest, great show, very clever!! At Fox Glove
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@Stupid__Comedy: "I'm 19 how old are you?" 17 "Aww, your still a baby" Bitch I ain't too young to give you this dick."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Google's Eric Schmidt recently made an appearance on NPR's Wait Wait??¦ Don't Tell Me!, which is weekly comedy trivia show...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @markthomasinfo: Isy Sutitie won Sony best comedy last night, she is also at Comedy Store, 27th May,benefit: Belarus Free Theatre. ?http…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tumblr translates the fluff pixiv comics. /a/ translates the comedy pixiv comics. Guess which one i love more?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@HH_Fan_Grace14 @digitalspy Americans can't do our type of comedy, we have a different sense of humor.
</tweet>
