<tweet>
	Being A Google Intern Is So Funny, Hollywood Made It Into A Comedy Movie > http://t.co/pTgd56Cprl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@thatchickNATI word I fuck with him & kelso straight comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RalphGarman: HBO's #FamilyTree is the most promising comedy I've seen in a while. Great seeing @MJMcKean back. Healthy, funny, and crus…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MQIMagesInc Check me out in InAPP COMEDY playing in theaters RIGHT NOW !! Go see the movie dammit ;-) Watch.. http://t.co/PCf1RacMyv RT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TheEvilZeta lol I mean why they tex- I mean they pure comedy lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My gran's house is like one big comedy show
</tweet>
<tweet>
	See Funny Comedian Corey Holcomb sunday @Uptown Comedy Club RSVP For FREE Tickets Txt Names to 678-223-3699 Now! http://t.co/0nCTK1iWdr
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hypocrisy runs rapid, Irony is comedy, therefore twitter is comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Indie movie night at our place. Just finished a Quirky Comedy flick now on to Horror… (wife’s choice) #iaintscared
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Anth3aG I generally prefer things darker tho #LikeSVU ..comedy/light crime doesn't sit too well
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @YouTube: .@Schwarzenegger What does the Commando of Comedy have to say about @angelaR5_ ’s eat-like-animals pick? http://t.co/aBJJ6U3YQC
</tweet>
<tweet>
	stand up comedy out
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedy Circus Fame Bharti Singh in Jatt n Juliet 2
First look of this movie will coming in a week 
stay tuned... http://t.co/ISwL8ilE8K
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Chilln2theMaxx lmao on god these niggas comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dave Attell will try to make you laugh @ Helium Comedy Club - Buffalo this Friday and Saturday. http://t.co/w9Do4RKrm6
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Seems my plan to fall asleep listening to podcasts has backfired tonight. Now stifling fits of giggles. Thanks, Comedy Bang Bang!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedy Show Sunday at Uptown Comedy Corner For Free Tickets to the 8:00pm Show! Txt Names to 678-223-3699 Now! http://t.co/uNIVNTYcRj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JP_702 i know fuckn comedy i was laughing when she pulled us all out she was so dumb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@awryaditi great taste in comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@babybudgeting sand dune jumping, comedy photo burying kids up to their neck and pretending its someone's head fallen off, shadow puppets..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MikeyB3333 Iiiinteresting. I like a little philosophy in my comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BLOWNMlND: If there's a wheelchair-bound comedian, is it still called "stand-up" comedy?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JuleaDoll lmao that is comedy. You killed his shit off. Hahaha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @keiakarie94: This is all pure comedy. How am I supposed to write an essay? ?????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BlueJayOnToast local comedy radio show, intern was carrying a huge stack of boxes into the studio and drops them when <cont>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RedCapRadio: Talking @insanityleague show last night in Durban, it was absolute COMEDY CARNAGE!! Seriously a show not to be missed - do…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BanTheBBC @peteprodge 
Wow, you actually got repeated the week later.....swoon.... Mixing with comedy royalty here
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@murtazasolangi @Shahidmasooddr we also missed comedy/horror shows as well
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RealMurf comedy bang bang??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ToverdresseD: The hangover 3 is everything i hate about the movie and comedy industry yet I'm still going to see it.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@FarwaIsmail Now watch and tell me howz this. otherwise more suggestions in the row like feminist/comedy :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Videos on Channel 6 are kaea the maynes! They need to put some Samoan comedy! #WastingPower
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My sister is staying the night and she snores like a man. Can't sleep! #snoring #comedy https://t.co/e7ozJAhs9Y
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Peter pretending to dress up as himself to fool people *Kanye shrug* comedy lol:)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Arquipimp @ShawnaWTF yeah but the screen writer/ director is a fan of that kinda comedy. Only thing left was for tony stark to be drunk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@craigdavidlong yes, but one's a tragedy and the other a comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	HOLY SHIT just got offered a future spot on Til Two's comedy night roster. Better get irreverent. *tugs actual collar*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@uhhhh_itsmikey Comedy Central....?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	go goa rocksss guys... ultimate comedy movie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Pontifex  shy and cry Of the world. Sending the maggots to finish the lush In the midst grievous fallen temptuous comedy visitors
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Pontifex   shy and cry Of the world. Sending the maggots to finish the lush In the midst grievous fallen temptuous comedy visitors.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @keiakarie94: This is all pure comedy. How am I supposed to write an essay? ?????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	See Funny Comedian Corey Holcomb sunday @Uptown Comedy Club RSVP For FREE Tickets Txt Names to 678-223-3699 Now! http://t.co/Ted4mLYfJG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Please recommend a good comedy, desperately wanting a good laugh.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Life_InLaces: Jalens definition of Mexican fat is comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/NoinUp0iRK You Can't say that on YouTube Comedy Week.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I've given up trying to be funny on Twitter and am just going to occasionally retweet my comedy clients and @TheTweetOfGod
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@standupmetrotv Di Stand Up Comedy Festival ada kak Raditya Dika ga?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Iron Man 3 was sooo good, the perfect balance of comedy, action, and romance (:
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedy is simply a funny way of being serious..xU xQ!! ;) (Y)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Come See Comedian Corey Holcomb Live Sunday Uptown Comedy Club! http://t.co/eOzvjUIt68 Use PromoCode: TWITTER for Free Tickets!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PerthComedyFest: John Conway @newconway takes his comedy to new heights this week at Velvet Lounge. 10:45pm, tonight until Sat. http://…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lmfao twitter is to comedy.....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedian Eric BIG 'e' Johnson Comedy DVD's available now!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedian Eric BIG 'e' Johnson Comedy DVD's available now!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#crazy #humor #Joke #funny http://t.co/gFWaHLlDdS If you die in an elevator, be sure to press the UP button More fun http://t.co/2qbP2lTJSC
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedian Eric BIG 'e' Johnson Comedy DVD's available now!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedian Eric BIG 'e' Johnson Comedy DVD's available now!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedian Eric BIG 'e' Johnson Comedy DVD's available now!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedian Eric BIG 'e' Johnson Comedy DVD's available now!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedian Eric BIG 'e' Johnson Comedy DVD's available now!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedienne Felicia Comedy DVD's available now
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedienne Felicia Comedy DVD's available now
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedienne Felicia Comedy DVD's available now
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Comedienne Felicia Comedy DVD's available now
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Omg my umbrella has blown inside out and snapped off the handle cos of the wind!! It was like a cheap comedy! Shamed! #embarrassing
</tweet>
