<tweet>
	RT @KayyyylaKinns: I love watching stand up comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Check Out These FUNNY Pics of Celebs that Look Like Cartoons! #6 of Rihanna is perfect! http://t.co/WaZiBBAsWI
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rin's favorite manga genres
are: action, comedy, and
emotional drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KaviKrazyKomedy: @Rosaslondon Great Comedy this Tuesday at 8pm,The Fallen Angel in Islington.Free,funny people to entertain You
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Asses_Of Check me out in InAPP COMEDY playing in theaters RIGHT NOW !! Go see the movie dammit ;-) Watch.. http://t.co/PCf1RacMyv RT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/kiRDuWLwSl Arnold pumps you up for YouTube Comedy Week - Join in May 19-25
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bhavpreet_dhatt @mediacrooks 
This guy has a rocking sense of humour. Put him on comedy circus.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lmfao some vines are comedy ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @THlNK2: Life is a tragedy when seen in close-up, but a comedy in long-shot. - Charlie Chaplin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BenSaadna @djcharlottes I'm not really sure if there's a show for that... Like comedy, drama, romance? Can I get a genre lawl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Momma Killed My Vibe Part 2 http://t.co/fH46QPm4ae via @youtube LATE NIGHT SNACK OF COMEDY. NEW COMEDY SKIT UP.... RT RT RT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@misslisamorales Check me out in InAPP COMEDY playing in theaters RIGHT NOW !! Go see the movie dammit ;-) Watch.. http://t.co/PCf1RacMyv RT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BEAUTY AND THE BEASTS  A ROMANTIC COMEDY CONCERT #????????? http://t.co/9Q4xrsUrOq via
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @The12Signs: If you live with #Sagittarius, they'll be your endless source of comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@LHFMagazine Hi, how do we get our comedy night listed in your magazine?
https://t.co/6xeHRrtgLy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I like Sappy Comedy English movies. #HellYeh.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @THlNK2: Life is a tragedy when seen in close-up, but a comedy in long-shot. - Charlie Chaplin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @The12Signs: If you live with #Sagittarius, they'll be your endless source of comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stand up comedy is hilarious, but standing during the whole show gets tiresome for me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@QuinntonTMC Titus is comedy lmao
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@fortunemaker1 Check me out in InAPP COMEDY playing in theaters RIGHT NOW !! Go see the movie dammit ;-) Watch.. http://t.co/PCf1RacMyv RT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I love watching stand up comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sydneyisfunny great show tonight, awesome style of comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This niggah john comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This is pure comedy!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Inspire_Us: Life is a tragedy when seen in close-up, but a comedy in long-shot. - Charlie Chaplin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@theyoungdread Check me out in InAPP COMEDY playing in theaters RIGHT NOW !! Go see the movie dammit ;-) Watch.. http://t.co/PCf1RacMyv RT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Arnold pumps you up for YouTube Comedy Week - Join in May 19-25 http://t.co/ThFBbDJUxy via @youtube
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@FitTeresaNicole Check me out in InAPP COMEDY playing in theaters RIGHT NOW !! Go see the movie dammit ;-) Watch.. http://t.co/PCf1RacMyv RT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Really looking forward to seeing some live comedy tomorrow - loves a good laugh #goodforthesoul and easier than sit-ups. What a cheat hehe ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AnsuyaNathan: Another Aussie in LA talks to the effervescent @CeliaPacquola about comedy and what not. Check it! 
https://t.co/vTTrZ56V…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WeAreDN: Raw passion takes an unexpected breather in @jmjfilm's comedy short RECEIVE BACON http://t.co/Sb8A9rVMq0
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@eddieizzard reaches new heights in his comedy career with the biggest jokers of all....politicians!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@richardthewatts In a row, separated by a comma?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	rodger on american dad is to comedy tho
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@amych_ @jimmy_colts finally, someone who appreciates comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BalhamComedy: Tickets are on sale from TODAY - it's a great line-up #balhamcomedyfestival #balham #comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WANTED: For Bad Comedy- Seth MacFarlane/ Seth Green
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yea cuz we're comedy geniuses
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Marc Savard's Comedy Hypnosis at PH is funny. Must go see it if you're in Vegas!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My last 2 RTs are comedy man
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ouch! The only thing worse than a painful tattoo, is a painfully mis-spelled tattoo! #10 is just hilarious. http://t.co/Gf3OCUqTXL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AdamSargant: I strongly recommend @exchangearts weekly Monday night comedy night. Free, funny and good beer :-) Why did it take me so l…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Please Don't Ignore

Type YES if you ask
Jesus to bless you! http://t.co/hgjqEl1qG5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Nonton Stand Up Comedy dulu bray di psbb~
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DalstonDin we've been busy tweeting about our new comedy night in Stokey https://t.co/6xeHRrtgLy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is a tragedy when seen in close-up, but a comedy in long-shot. - Charlie Chaplin: Inspire_Us: Life is a tragedy when seen in clo...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stand up comedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Jokoy I think it's awesome you reach out to your fans. Shows that your a real genuine and good dude. Keep up the awesome comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JasonStutter: Comedy 'Edwin: My Life as a Koont' goes off at Hollywood premiere. Actor Bryce Campbell gives thoughts on Hollywood http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @debrabaker33: @danieljohnsonuk “@THlNK2: Life is a tragedy when seen in close-up, but a comedy in long-shot. - Charlie Chaplin”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Melvynhayes Good your supporting all this. One of my Comedy sketches i am recording today is the Meet the Gang cos the boys are here.......
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stand Up Comedy Season 1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lmao he is comedy for that
</tweet>
