<tweet>
	Happy happy happy happy happy day <3 doing what we love isn't a crime but an entitlement to love ourselves a bit more.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We ain't doing crime for the sake of doing crimeWe movin' dimes cause we ain't doin' fine
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Criminal bumblebees! - The Economist explains: How can bumblebees commit crime? | The Economist http://t.co/kqnjaHePsV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Demanding excellence and striving for superior work is not a crime.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @danielkemp6: Seventeen Years. A free to read gritty crime story in three parts published in Female First Celebrity magazine.  http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Happy Birthday 2 my Partner in Crime..Whereva she is ,Fun is always beside her....life of the party @Que_lyk ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"IT'S NOT A CRIME RIGHT?"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	goddess-of-trickery: awkwardstandinglewiskennedy: Doctor Who: The only show that has inter-species crime... http://t.co/n0XkguPwuc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Anth3aG I generally prefer things darker tho #LikeSVU ..comedy/light crime doesn't sit too well
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Freedom is not a crime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	DTN Turkey: Dink murder committed by crime gang, says high court: Turkey's High Court of Appeals have overturn... http://t.co/xjCE1ZVa8k
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Em_ily_S: LOLy GoET headline at Lonestarball:

“Oakland: First in Crime, Last In Our Hearts, Rangers Finally Win At O.Co”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dink murder committed by crime gang, says high court: Turkey's High Court of Appeals have overturned previous ... http://t.co/VrARqwOzlz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It should be a crime to be this weak lmaooooo
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@hazmatt69 
It's all about who screwed who.  Wich famous person is in trouble   Who died 
Bombings, money courts. Crime rate is high, Hello
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MIKLAA Ikr! We were joking around with Connor and she took it like it was a crime! And she told me I had a dirty mouth! Like shutupppp??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @joe90kane: ME medical charities help Murdoch attack disabled ppl & smearing them as anti-social when UK disability hate crime at record…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wait when did josh peck become attractive?...is this a crime?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @umairh: It's not a minor league crime. It's one of history's greatest ripoffs. Bankers should be in prison, and frankly, we all know it.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Police killers should get 'life means life' sentences says Theresa May via @Telegraph http://t.co/HtYkEdrzPp
</tweet>
<tweet>
	International Law & Rape: Nature of the crime *Coercion* Crime of inequality (whether of force, physical power, status or relation)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	There are so many crime programs these days on television, I feel like wiping my fingerprints off the remote, everytime i finish watching TV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I added a video to a @YouTube playlist http://t.co/rgKGHQ2yX3 Kerala's Most Wanted - A real crime story -
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thames Valley Police and Crime Commissioner statement on Bullfinch case http://t.co/NqywgltCFj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Report crime to your local police station! http://t.co/1anjNvVUyY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Financial intelligence helped return app $300M to Govt last yr but agency had forced staff cuts. Get $ back from org crime @JoeHockey
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Crime shows are the reasons I get freaked out all the time yet I still watch them.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ChrisMcAloon21 @STGOFMaguire @Jade_Sparkles  Dont worry im plan on being a military cop so we can fight crime together #BatmanandRobin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@jemmacookx yeah he has
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Killin These Bitches Crime Scene
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The corruption of Michael Henderson is now available from the finest booksellers around the world!! #thriller #romance #crime #win #comp
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DrEvanHarris: @justice4daniel The police can always go to their MP or the opposition crime spokesman or to the IPCC now.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @lukemizon1: What I hate most about Twitter: finishing a good tweet, having -1 characters left, and then having to decide which grammar …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @billmaher: Shit-U-not,Repubs voting to repeal Obamacare for the 37th time! This after another week of Benghazi. Why not just beat an ac…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wife accuses hubby of infecting her with Aids http://t.co/jTdnsCwzwn
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheComedyHumor: What I hate most about Twitter: finishing a good tweet, having -1 characters left, and then having to decide which gram…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @stophateuk: Stop Learning Disability Hate Crime supports anyone in #England or #Wales who is affected by #LD #HateCrime. Open 24/7 on 0…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	?China's Crime Rate;(http://t.co/yrE7Q6pIhr ) According to the report by the United Nation’s Office on Drugs and. http://t.co/7O28SrviD5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SophieBrown401: Happy birthday to my partner in crime, @marniebird123 ???????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@_Alaster @Crime_writer97 At least you only had to put up with the text of it, I pity Alaster's parents
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BUcrimlaw: RACISM ALERT-3 BLACKS beat up white family & NOT charged w/hate crime-let off easy http://t.co/InQF89qJHm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Happy birthday to my partner in crime, @marniebird123 ???????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Prison_Health: Correlates of Serious Violent Crime for Recently Released Parolees w History of Homelessness http://t.co/DISOa9ldaM HT @…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@iScope_Botches: @Lucian_Jay oh you might just have a partner in crime if im off" YESSSS!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @NYPFJBB: Coalition tough on crime tougher on fighters of crime - will HomeSec dispel or confirm this today #fedconf2013 ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Phemii_iamHer: Black Girls can easily get away with murder, cause 'em police gonn find a hair at th crime scene &track it back to a gir…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"cause i really knew my little crime would be cold that's why i got a heater for your tighs"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SAcrimefighters: Fact: Anyone who buys stolen goods supports crime and is as guilty as the criminal.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Apparently not wanting to go out is a crime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	After ATM heist, India's IT sector again in unwelcome spotlight http://t.co/K8bXiLFJqt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AlixAinzuain: "@Dontaemims_20: Didn't know talking to a new girl was such a Crime," get it boy get it ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sacto 911: Driver guilty of second-degree murder in crash near Woodland http://t.co/MFWWooNvvj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @umairh: It's not a minor league crime. It's one of history's greatest ripoffs. Bankers should be in prison, and frankly, we all know it.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i had to pull out the car from the fucking crime scene without police escort. and the hacker still on lose. punyetang pulis sa pilipinas!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BarnsGreg @frogpondsrock sorry to hear Tasmania has joined the "if we make this even MORE illegal surely the crime will stop" meme
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @satyabhashnam: How the 45 million dollar ATM heist poses danger to India's IT industry
http://t.co/KqucQxvV9h
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Crime_writer97 dan's got his right?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@fareedahmed502 Yes I guess his only REAL crime was that he got caught in the act of eating a fellow musliim's heart. Otherwise #warishell
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MelissaMono and the victim is White... It also becomes a pathology when a white person commits the crime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Actually black people don't like crime! They get confused they get confused...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheZako: Only in Syria a stupid savage rebel, who wants to put Assad on trial for war crimes, go and commit a war crime on record. He's…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@justice4daniel The police can always go to their MP or the opposition crime spokesman or to the IPCC now.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@2210kelly @joblo99 @esneet4113 i know the truth of the crime. blood trails blood splatter, M.E. report. PLUS MOTIVE http://t.co/bLd3cLmcCk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@SAcrimefighters: Fact: Anyone who knowingly buys stolen goods supports crime and is as guilty as the criminal.”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Smatkoschmann You fit get belle now, no b crime. It is your choice.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BethAuntSally: Wearing eye makeup is a crime when it rains
</tweet>
