<tweet>
	@MrSteveTaylor @jodiekeeling little satsuma... I like it haha! Jodie will always choose me she's my partner in crime babyyy!!! X
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@iofiv @PFEW_HQ Presenter asked several times "who actually logs the crime" Apparently evasive answer knackered credibility!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Brazil4MPE: What about treason of compromised media that neglects facts and proofs that banking is terminal, a crime against us? #pfmpe…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ChrisDoee_ buck nasty you are so dark when you touch yourself it's like black on black crime HAHAHAHA
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Osaka Mayor: Wartime Sex Slaves Were Necessary: TOKYO -- An outspoken nationalist mayor said the Japanese mili... http://t.co/9ycWmLv7ju
</tweet>
<tweet>
	FROM THE NEWSROOM: Rural crime-fighting event held in Kendal: http://t.co/c3Hn3bCXcj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	. @telliott_UUP - Fully operational National Crime Agency necessary to tackle online exploitation of children #nolan http://t.co/eQ9hSdwp1j
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What I hate most about Twitter: finishing a good tweet, having -1 characters left, and then having to decide which grammar crime to commit.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Happy birthday my dearest partner in crime @ARaharjanto *See U on this Saturday ;)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The partner in crime @rsrikanth05 too is sick. What shall happen of our WikiMafia?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hyper tier: Song 1 is N? CRIME [a]. Song 2 is lower world [h].   these are good songs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@olliecattermole @DorsetRachel @damiangreenmp absolute utter tripe. The key is in the words "reported" crime. 1/2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OhMyGollyGosh_: criminal minds > every other crime show
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RediTlhabi: great that Zuma responded to desperate cry of a mother& community fed up with drugs& crime. Positive step,NOW ACTION pls fr…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @NorthantsPolice: We've just been on @BBCNorthampton talking about how we use Twitter+FB and reminding folks not to report crime on here…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @bellelinde: 'Can you imagine a world without men? Yeah. No crime. Just lots of happy fat women.'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I heard a police car and the 1st thing I thought was "Guess the crime!".
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Venezuela troops target street crime http://t.co/MEo1ITKYeG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	crime shows again! feeling fat lying down and watching tv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Daughter dies from injuries after hotel incident | Herald Scotland http://t.co/ZvcmSFJpQC via @hsnewsbreak
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Racist trolls adore statistics pertaining to blk-on-white crime. To them, numbers tell them who black folks are.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @syedasiftanveer: Nxt tym if some1 robs u steal frm u comits a fraud wid u
Shw sme grace n nt regstr an FIR against the crime cz of sprt…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@enslavednomore I have no stats,but viewing the spike in crime& lack of border controls,leads me to my opinion.not stating facts, my opinion
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RediTlhabi: Remember Eldorado mom whose son is addicted to tik? She wrote letter to pres Zuma complaining about drug& crime. JZ visitin…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Beer mat is secret crime busting tool: A student has designed a beermat which will be distributed to... http://t.co/jDud9RHfkh #beernews
</tweet>
<tweet>
	. @telliott_UUP warns of the effect of no fully operational National Crime Agency in NI #nolan http://t.co/AleTG4sKsD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My Sarcastic jokes should be a crime lmao
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bottom of my road is now a cordoned off crime scene. WHERE DA HOOD  WHERE DA HOOD WHERE DA HOOD AT?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Police conducted a door-to-door search following the shoot-out during a Mother’s Day parade in New Orleans. | http://t.co/4QIxs6Yxp7
</tweet>
<tweet>
	O.J. Simpson back in court http://t.co/GXMRKLjNym #cnn
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Brand new #crime #thriller with a big juicy twist! Pursuit released today on #kindle http://t.co/9BrSdeW0pi
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Marching to the doctors in my Superman PJs. Full time vigilante; fighting crime even in my nighttime attire.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Evening Lovelies!
I'd love for you to meet my partner in crime, I mean, my classmate at Clip Joint, and the gal... http://t.co/H9qzyy1oK5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teenage Crime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RediTlhabi: great that Zuma responded to desperate cry of a mother& community fed up with drugs& crime. Positive step,NOW ACTION pls fr…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	jasmyne forever my partner in crime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Law 27/79 stipulates it is a crime to destroy cultural property: Save & Protect Dhivehi Heritage @UNESCO
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PwettiDuchess: Glo is one Criminal network tho* crime fighters where are thou???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fine let me commit a real crime.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GoodwinMJ: On my reading only 7% of voters see EU as important issue. Behind economy, immigration, unemployment, crime, education, hous…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DavQuinn @rtenews indeed, illegal late-term TOP is wrong. Interesting that he could be murdered by the state for his crime. Eye for eye?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Telegraph: Tia Sharp: Mother wants to ask murderer 'why?': The mother of schoolgirl Tia… http://t.co/u0YTdP4OZZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Tae4_Montana: Eating pussy aint a crime is it
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It seems the recent crime stats aren't all they professed to be then. Who'd have thunk it. Really worth a listen when iPlayer link is up
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RediTlhabi: great that Zuma responded to desperate cry of a mother& community fed up with drugs& crime. Positive step,NOW ACTION pls fr…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I really missed my partner in crime Brittani today ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I think #oomf in twitter jail lol oh well, did the crime do the time
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Stanhopeless Spot on. The man's #vile. It's probably the real reason he doesn't want resources used 2 try & prevent crime. He's a #parasite
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#fedconf2013 the policy of claiming crime figs being suppressed is not helpful without meaningful evidence from all forces involved.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	There's no such thing as perfect crime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RediTlhabi: great that Zuma responded to desperate cry of a mother& community fed up with drugs& crime. Positive step,NOW ACTION pls fr…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tia Sharp: Hazell facing life in prison despite police blunders which meant he almost evaded capture via @Telegraph http://t.co/SIWQSFCLSf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @lekomotion: Well done SA for making effective noise around the Gupta issue on social media, we can do the same against RAPE, CRIME, ABU…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dubai spies from the skies on unruly football fans http://t.co/EQNJfKM385
</tweet>
<tweet>
	On duty till 4pm today. No reports of ASB or crime overnight in Tupton or North Wingfield. Foot patrol planned for today and no meetings
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This book I'm reading is getting interesting! Never thought I wouldve enjoyed a crime fiction novel
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If loving fashion is a crime, Dubs Place plead GUILTY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@THemingford @brigadoonboy Its a punishment for no crime. Pure nasty Tory bullying at its worst.  Beneath contempt.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheStar_news: Shot baby was caught in mob, cop fray http://t.co/LGFotAMjkP
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@metrotrains you guys can't be this shit at running trains... Fare evasion isn't a crime, its called paying the value of the service given
</tweet>
