<tweet>
	Love that The Fear of Things to Come hit #16 on Amazon Best Sellers Top 100 Free ebooks in Suspense! #Thriller #Crime http://t.co/CuI7bJoUwF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@tips2_cantik I keep telling you, Papa, when you sell a fake masterpiece, that is a crime!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It really should be a crime to have a headache as bad as mine right now.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SAPoliceService: #sapsHINT #Drugdealing The Police can't solve this problem alone. Success required community involvement. Report to Cr…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love crime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@lil_chief18 wish u were still my partner in crime! U shacked up lil ol lady hahaha jkn
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Tembo11RG: @JoRichardsKent studies do show some causal links between those committing crime & motoring offences @reviddiver @constablec…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @bbcwm: Further government cuts could lead to 1,000 more jobs going at @WMPolice, its police & crime commissioner warns http://t.co/zrHy…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Both sides condemn convicted Pa. abortion doctor - Seattle Post Intelligencer http://t.co/c1rvSaG1b6 via #NewzSocial
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This information passes to the Interpol as the bill of crime not only journalistic information.I'm still
</tweet>
<tweet>
	So Cooking While Brown is now officially a crime. http://t.co/fgRjyLjq7F We are ruled by geniuses.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheA21Campaign: Human trafficking is a crime with a human cost and we've had enough. Join our fight! http://t.co/uELxHVZ5fh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SaiyidahAisyah saida jakarta x best .okay end of this year ke krabi kita .tix murahh.jommm .i need partner in crime too.hahaha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @crazyfriendsxx: What I hate most about Twitter: finishing a good tweet, having -1 characters left, and then having to decide which gram…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"The crime rate has dropped to 0%...how could that be? Did the Mexicans get money today too?" #ChappellesShow #LAWLZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LongLiveGuapo: "This jus in, the crime rate has fell to zero.....how can that be? Did the Mexicans get money too?" Lmao Chappelle show …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dubai taxi sex couple lose legal battle: http://t.co/O8QV3vdScv - Judges dismisses claims it only lasted 45 seconds so wasnt real sex :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Duhvidzz: @krogey_says It is a good idea for a movie though. You just say "what if crime was legal for a day" and you're practically sh…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @FirstpostBiz: Corruption and crime: How coal mafias fuel India’s power crisis http://t.co/0cwLL3YIrc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Classic Crime: Glass Houses
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Leveson made Officers too scared to contact press to blow whistle on crime-figures manipulation; police-federation bloke to #R4today
</tweet>
<tweet>
	sorry Gus and all crime victims. Top journalist, family attacked and robbed: http://t.co/NNlwMZJtUg via @News24
</tweet>
<tweet>
	is it true that crime rate in Mexico reduces when Chicharitto is playing?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BhawanaSomaaya: Nirbhaya case bus files go missing so crime branch cannot identify the transport comp who chartered pvt bus. R u surpri…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@carolhadinata oreimo 2, kakumeiki valvrave, date a live, dansai bunri no crime edge are a bit interssant, they are from this season
</tweet>
<tweet>
	O.J. Simpson retrial bid opens with Las Vegas attorney raising questions about previous strategy. http://t.co/ST49PIHjAp #vegas #FB #lvrj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@krogey_says It is a good idea for a movie though. You just say "what if crime was legal for a day" and you're practically shitting movies
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_KatieBarrett: mammy just came in and told me that one direction are coming to crime park on a stadium tour OMG the news better be true…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	T I R E D! But working hard. It's a crime, but no one ever said crime didn't pay. Oh wait....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If crime fighters fight crime and fire fighters fight fire, what do freedom fighters fight?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @YeaDonny: @Yarrum_Nairod that I know, you still at the scene of the crime.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Reevesy29 u nightshirt again fucksake. Jus saw ur partner in crime leavin yard there #HatesTheHours
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@UmarCheema1 @Asma_Jahangir I wonder why no one accept the guilty and unlawful acts which has been proved? thats itself a #Crime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TonyKanal: STOP #AgGag !! Please sign @will_potter 's petition to stop criminalizing those trying to stop animal cruelty. I did. http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Corruption and crime: How coal mafias fuel India’s power crisis
http://t.co/hk1JcDe7f1
Deadly Powerful Combination = Corruption + Crime :((
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stamp out crime — abolish the IRS.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Yarrum_Nairod that I know, you still at the scene of the crime.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SAPoliceService: #sapsHINT #Drugdealing The Police can't solve this problem alone. Success required community involvement. Report to Cr…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"This jus in, the crime rate has fell to zero.....how can that be? Did the Mexicans get money too?" Lmao Chappelle show that shit!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@2uMISSbell but still figures don't lie lower crime stats than the UK with assault & rape & burglary. Here they have stabbings & hammers !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @lekomotion: Well done SA for making effective noise around the Gupta issue on social media, we can do the same against RAPE, CRIME, ABU…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stiffer regulations on cannabis cafes in Amsterdam linked to recent 'explosion' in crime. http://t.co/EkpTOQBL8E @the560k
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CriFiLover: New today: Chilled to the Bone - crime fiction set in Iceland, written by a Brit - http://t.co/fSAV9cDjIx reviewed by @Mari…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Enjoyed this post by @MarinaSofia8  at Crime Fiction Lover. com http://t.co/wmpQFshAMn
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ASnarkyNerdette Well, not *all* mutant powers are useful for crime-fighting.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DonnaDiva No, it's an atrocity of mindless fear of creativity. A Crime Against Humanity delivered as self-inflicted torture.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why am I made ugly did I do a heinous crime while I was in my mother's belly i
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TimesCrime: Tia murder: police fear Internet abuse images fuelled killer http://t.co/cXvr91iEZj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JoRichardsKent studies do show some causal links between those committing crime & motoring offences @reviddiver @constablechaos
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I was tryna create a crime scene,i ended up with sumthang else sh!t
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Crime doesn't pay...Does that mean my job is a crime?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @NorthantsPolice: We've just been on @BBCNorthampton talking about how we use Twitter+FB and reminding folks not to report crime on here…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SheldonSaid: What I hate most about Twitter is finishing a good tweet, having -1 characters left and having to decide which grammar cri…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#welsh book of the year nominees announced. No #crime fiction
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Am with @sandralaville on this: it is not 'porn' it is the rape of kids on film. via @timescrime and @fhamiltontimes  http://t.co/ct1fMgSKat
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's not a crime! Caring about your friends is not a crime! (Lucy Heartfilia)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Money makes a man and thats a crime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SAPoliceService: #sapsHINT #Drugdealing The Police can't solve this problem alone. Success required community involvement. Report to Cr…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SAPoliceService: #sapsHINT #Drugdealing The Police can't solve this problem alone. Success required community involvement. Report to Cr…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Reported crimes against Indian women - 228,650 in 2011, the latest figures available from the National Crime Records Bureau
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @EspenBarthEide: Opening #REHC2013 - we must stand up against the rise of right-wing extremism, xenophobia, attacks on minorities and ha…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What I hate most about Twitter: finishing a good tweet, having -1 characters left, and then having to decide which grammar crime to commit.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CEOPUK calling on police to target the growing role of organised crime in child sexual exploitation. GMS @ 0815
</tweet>
<tweet>
	old to be enslaved were----MERELY---beaten to death for the---OUTLANDISH CRIME---of begging the white, CHRISTIANS, God-Fearing folk to
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lmao "the crime rate has fallen to 0%.. How is that possible did the mexicans get their reparations check to?"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Belgrade teen arrested for cellphone weapon charge: A Belgrade man arrested after deputies say he pointed a ce... http://t.co/oKh7s8mlb7
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Belgrade teen arrested for cellphone weapon charge: A Belgrade man arrested after deputies say he pointed a ce... http://t.co/2FxtdFbJRe
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When A lady slap a dude is not a crime.. But when a dude slap a lady problem.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SAPoliceService: #sapsHINT #Drugdealing The Police can't solve this problem alone. Success required community involvement. Report to Cr…
</tweet>
