<tweet>
	Got my test tomorrow ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thekhayalan15: Flipping a big omelet is one of my weaknesses. My omelet will always turn into a disaster every time I try to flip it. T…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	One woman is becoming disaster 
Even though a man is still singing 
I’m tearing up at the thought of break up..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You such a disaster wit that square shit Red Cross couldn't give a coffin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @twowitwowoo: This lorry full of tortoises collided with a van full of terrapins.  It was a turtle disaster.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TotallyHenley and sex and childbirth and disaster, death and destruction slow it down though
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This fool called me asking where the chicken heads at ?? I am done!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Woke up late and now it's raining. I think it's safe to say that today is going to be a disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Crank the Walls Down" by Maylene and the Sons of Disaster #BadassFeelBetterMusic
</tweet>
<tweet>
	So even if disaster strikes , I close my eyes and then I´m next to you, I´m right there with you
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#GNDR 57% say disaster losses are increasing according to a global report #VFL13 to be released today http://t.co/XTcJOcmXb1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'M A FIRE STARTER, I'M A SWEET DISASTER
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sjhumm: I suspect that @JuliaGillard's tears are for herself because inwardly she must realize that as a PM she's been an absolute disa…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sometimes a short cut is just a short cut  to disaster.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sjhumm: I suspect that @JuliaGillard's tears are for herself because inwardly she must realize that as a PM she's been an absolute disa…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thekhayalan15: Flipping a big omelet is one of my weaknesses. My omelet will always turn into a disaster every time I try to flip it. T…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I feel like my whole prom situation is about to be a disaster.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GreatSiteFinder: This book will show you why being prude is a recipe to disaster when it comes to relationships.. http://t.co/LsGo5BXfPJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thekhayalan15: Flipping a big omelet is one of my weaknesses. My omelet will always turn into a disaster every time I try to flip it. T…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sjhumm: I suspect that @JuliaGillard's tears are for herself because inwardly she must realize that as a PM she's been an absolute disa…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@markmcdsnp Have you seen this on @ScotlandshireGB? "Chaos as MSP quits to apply for a job - as an MSP." Ha! http://t.co/l0rCydwbtl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@emaleroland Yes, much cheaper. Also, property taxes funding schools is disaster for inner city kids. It needs to stop.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thekhayalan15: Flipping a big omelet is one of my weaknesses. My omelet will always turn into a disaster every time I try to flip it. T…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	watching disaster date love this show lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thekhayalan15: Flipping a big omelet is one of my weaknesses. My omelet will always turn into a disaster every time I try to flip it. T…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I suspect that @JuliaGillard's tears are for herself because inwardly she must realize that as a PM she's been an absolute disaster #AusPol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AkposWarriboy: EKAETTE: Why u no dey like take my picture.. AKPOS: I hear for News say e no good to take Pictures of any Natural Disast…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When a mother said she disowned you, it's totally a disaster. Dont mess up with mummy. Takutnya.Ma,kalau haja budak baik tau
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We are very concerned that the Comrades who destroyed SA's Railways will spend R300-bn to expand that disaster. From Sig, Randburg @gwawlax
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disaster strikes Rohinghya again as boats fleeing Cyclone Mahasen sink http://t.co/UI3qBXUAQS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	THIS IS A FUCKING DISASTER
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thekhayalan15: Flipping a big omelet is one of my weaknesses. My omelet will always turn into a disaster every time I try to flip it. T…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DDNewsLive: #TamilNadu govt to implement Rs 1,481 crore Coastal Disaster Risk Reduction Project with financial assistance from #WorldBa…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disaster...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Flipping a big omelet is one of my weaknesses. My omelet will always turn into a disaster every time I try to flip it. There goes my life.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	See this is when you need Lebron @Iked_Up29 what a disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	seriously French last assessment before was a disaster~~sigh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Well that was a disaster.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fashion disaster day is just a normal day for me . Lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GreatSiteFinder: This book will show you why being prude is a recipe to disaster when it comes to relationships.. http://t.co/LsGo5BXfPJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Allianz: Low Rates to Keep Earnings Under Pressure: Fewer disasters, higher premiums boosted insurer's profit ... http://t.co/m0MRo0HOVs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just keep thinking, 'but why would he ever choose the emotional disaster that is me?' What if I've messed it up for good. Ah.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We are very concerned that the Comrades who destroyed SA's Railways will spend R300 billion to expand that disaster. From Sig, Randburg
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Full fringe and rain = disaster :(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Deaf & experiencing emotional distress after disaster? Disaster Distress #Helpline offers 24/7 support via SMS: text 'TalkWithUs' to 66746
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Having to break my own rules here, got work jeans on but wearing running trainers with them till I can get my wellies from the van. Disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Overconfident would lead you to a disaster. Believe me!!! :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@fawadchaudhry @RehKhalil One of them Rehman M was an unmitigated disaster.Thamks he is not around otherwise he wd b licking AH shoes now
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @UN: More can be done to reduce disaster impacts. Learn more about #GAR13 http://t.co/eZQfsaVkXZ via @UNISDR
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Photo: I’ll soon forget the color of your eyes & you’ll forget mine. http://t.co/j8hvsXBBzx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#WorldNews Disaster strikes Rohinghya again as boats fleeing Cyclone Mahasen sink - The Independent http://t.co/cr10KLbZnc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yea I would like to drift someday :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Coping with a disaster while living overseas - Your Expat Child http://t.co/4Lk9Qdzqg3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disaster strikes Rohinghya again as boats fleeing cyclone sink - Asia-World-The Independent http://t.co/fwPnVLGbM1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@pinkvilla destroyed the whole look. Disaster. She looks like shez 45 yrs old !!! Such a pretty face made to look like this. I pity her.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GreatSiteFinder: This book will show you why being prude is a recipe to disaster when it comes to relationships.. http://t.co/LsGo5BXfPJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dear Almighty Allah save us from terrible disaster #Mahasen
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BBC news reader repeatedly using phrase "fracking free zone". Stay tuned for news of the inevitable disaster #highriskjournalism
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @jeslynpeiyu: got a feeling presentation will be a disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i could be your perfect disaster
you could be my ever after
</tweet>
<tweet>
	EKAETTE: Why u no dey like take my picture.. AKPOS: I hear for News say e no good to take Pictures of any Natural Disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @as_ox: Today is just going to be a disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Seriously, how complicated is the UMass (Lowell) website! Navigational disaster. I am better than most ppl at it & struggling to find my way
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When you drift with the shopping carts in Walmart and then there's this old guy with mustache looking at you like TF is wrong with him ._.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Two astronauts must fight for survival after disaster strikes during a space mission. Gravity - Trailer http://t.co/fmKwWN3prs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i could be your perfect disaster you could be my ever after
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Today is just going to be a disaster
</tweet>
