<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@shefaly Didn't know that. But if it funded the likes of Monsanto, then it's disaster in another form.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Adamjmargo course he is his treatment and selection of managers has always been a disaster having said that avb needs to improve
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This day is gonna be a disaster. Just know it already
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MaddogsBro is it wrong to miss Trav so much that u put beautiful disaster and Walking Disaster on repeat in ur audio book que?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OCHAAsiaPac: 1/3 Latest from Pacific Disaster Center on #Mahasen #TSOne: The highest impact, surge and rainfall predictions are for the…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@joebicks couldn't think of anything worse..disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@suhzzzz Lol I'm praying for it to come :) it's fun when there is a disaster :D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bloomberg is a real-world environmental disaster http://t.co/Z6omhDwNJo #bearish
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My phone slid out of my pocket in my dads van as I got out. Only realised now I'm on the bus! #disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My pride pushes me to do some crazy ass shit. lmao
#Seriously
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Will Obamacare be a disaster or a success? I wonder!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	what a complete disaster .
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@joespencer10 you missed floral disaster at mine
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MeActually @Mr_DrunkGent are your pubes a disaster?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disaster the heron has had all my Fish.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Already having dreams about districts being a disaster friday ? This is going to happen all week long and i wont be able to sleep ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	people angry at balloon. compare balloon to death of 36 people (admittedly German) http://t.co/ZXfjlfudPc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Awk0Tacoo: Hey, you can't mix business with pleasure, that's just a recipe for disaster. (My first one-liner from when I solve a murder…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My room is a disaster. #moving #illcleanitlater #ineedtogetridofstuff
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What if Anna Kendrick wouldn't be Beca in PP2? That would be a disaster. It's not even Pitch Perfect.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Skywhale branded "Hindenboob'' in ACT Assembly question time
http://t.co/UeEqvr9Dht
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I got trap money.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just finished Week 2 of my @DietBet. Now in 2nd place with a 81% chance of winning. Cheer me on! http://t.co/rMBYPv8d3R
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DacapoSA pretty disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I rarely let people get to me, but when you're someone I considered close and you test me, it's fucking wwIII with a huge natural disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OCHAAsiaPac: 1/3 Latest from Pacific Disaster Center on #Mahasen #TSOne: The highest impact, surge and rainfall predictions are for the…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You natural disaster but this isn't over, catastrophic Casanova you're mine and I love ya
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#SocialMedia Security First Improves Disaster Recovery With New Social Media Technology: Security F... http://t.co/7vHmJz0Zmm #Insurance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Shit like this is exactly why I love seldom and trust never
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Human being to the mob; 
What's a mob to a king? 
What's a king to a god? 
What's a god to a nonbeliever?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Security First Improves Disaster Recovery With New Social Media Technology: Social Media Capture, Control, Com... http://t.co/VScoi1m6P9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	it's coo to be in love in all but love her for her not just the sex that's a recipe for disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @dailystarnews: Children show photographs of their parents who went missing in the Rana Plaza disaster. They are still to know... http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mixed start: home smells lush; chocolate brownies with pretzel taste YUM! They're stuck to the cupcake paper #disaster #AintNoDomesticGodess
</tweet>
<tweet>
	the disaster of yesterday's exams mean I'm going into this exam in self destruct mode..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	dream.love.disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Best practices in business continuity and disaster recovery http://t.co/kbu1d6JJCG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Learn more about the Global Platform for Disaster Risk Reduction in May 2013 http://t.co/UMlCGdniWP #gpdrr13 via @unisdr
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You should never ever take your ipod/iphone to the restroom. That's like asking for a disaster ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How post-disaster therapy is a disaster by @vaughanbell http://t.co/1kbBUlhAMk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm a fire starter, I'm a sweet disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Picassokat This is so sad. Burma has had trouble for a long time and now becoming free and they have this disaster. Just pray for them.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MeActually 

thought your name said "Pubic Disaster", and for that, I'm following you
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@toughtimess77 Like, War in Iraq was a huge disaster completely caused by Bush lying about WMD. Never happened.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fucking disaster on the train! @EleanorJaneR
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This was a shoulder burner after cleans. Time was 9:18 as second set of DU where a disaster #cfwod #CrossFit http://t.co/5jH2F9r10g
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SlushHoleSlasha: but i am stubborn as can be so i will take it to the head before i ever take a knee
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Done it again.. mascara on then sneeze #disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disaster!!!!! RT @abpnewstv PM constitutes GoM to study autonomy to CBI
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ACountryQuote: We'll both play our parts in this disaster. I'll be the bitch and you'll be the bastard.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Some very clear directions that the @americascup should consider when looking @ArtemisRacing disaster http://t.co/LT5m6yivQZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@marthakanama you are right to say so, if they play like on saturday it will be a disaster to u guys
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@rommelvincent06  you will have to survive any disaster-.. you can make... #survive
</tweet>
<tweet>
	SAVAR, Bangladesh (CNN) -- Across from the detritus of Bangladesh's deadliest industrial disaster, up four flights of narrow stairs, and ..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Had a dream I lost my maths formula book and Now i Can't find it anywhere #freaky #disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	END OF DREAM BYE WOKE UP A DISASTER
</tweet>
<tweet>
	MARITIME DISASTER FIVE TIMES MORE DEADLY THAN THE TITANIC http://t.co/jgZISqNGBb #FatalReturn #kindle #thriller #amazon
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iDrZakirNaik: There's a reason Allah created men &women differently but today’s society is demasculinizing men & defeminizing women,a r…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@rebeccacallard is that true? Last year the weather was completely grim. What if S.of France is just cold & wet in may from now on? Disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Myanmar must avert further humanitarian disaster as cyclone approaches | Amnesty International - #Rohingya http://t.co/3Lj8VsghHv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The theme for the 2nd Asia-Pacific Water Summit is “Water Security and Water-related Disaster Challenges: Leadership and Commitment”...
</tweet>
