<tweet>
	Everything changed when I met you.
naging disaster!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Totally, McAlpines points all accurate Browns record an unmitigated disaster, is why hes so butthurt about the article after bigging him up
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Well that BSL exam was a disaster!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@_SarahAston not gonna lie this is a political disaster waiting to happen
</tweet>
<tweet>
	o u shutup @mianadeel its @AliZafarsays right to say anything about his country. Country is in disaster coz of politician not coz of *bache*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wish I had a twin ! But I don't at the same time as two of me would be a disaster !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iDrZakirNaik: There's a reason Allah created men &women differently but today’s society is demasculinizing men & defeminizing women,a r…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@richardbranson Mr Branson how about Virgin bidding for the Thameslink franchise and ridding us of the terrible first Group disaster please!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	bet the house was a disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @innoadage: Supp"@geospatialhub: applied maths was simply a disaster. which is the best word to describe it? #appliedmassacre"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MagsNews Given the utter disaster that banking has been in the last 5-10yrs, I don't think the best and brightest have ever been involved!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JamieMcGuire_ Hi Jamie I love Beautiful disaster and I'm waiting walking disaster in Italy... any news about it? Pleaseeeeeeeee
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"a profound failure of politics... democracy has quietly been supplanted by plutocracy" http://t.co/jcLHH2X7dG #climate
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Your eyes sparkle like the morning dew, looking at them makes me smile even if my day was a disaster @NormanHariss97
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@lif_au: Apocalypse Survival: The Disaster Essentials Every Home Needs - http://t.co/Zth377vy10” Chuck Norris is all you need.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CindyB1017 Lmao i don't know who ended up with it :) it was a disaster though
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Backside Disaster= Anal with an oops poops.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JennyJohnsonHi5: When I see a Twitter page cluttered with nothing but @ replies and RTs, I assume that person's house/apartment is a fu…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MiAmore_lee: @yellah12 lol. When my room is meant for a princess hippie like myself..when it's not a complete disaster. I need to clean…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@richardjh_org "...and they often lead to disaster." My sentiments exactly. Re: Traits. :P (Should really publish my draft blog post... :/)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I know what has happened to your sexual life. This cruel disaster is called impotence.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JGTMKTA lol yeah I mean if there was a natural disaster id be woken up by it lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Proper determined now to do well in the rest of my exams after yesterday's disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ah disaster I forgot to put make up on I can't go out without it on.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iDrZakirNaik: There's a reason Allah created men &women differently but today’s society is demasculinizing men & defeminizing women,a r…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@therunhome @MeganHustwaite This is ridiculous...if it were not for the high standards the players set this game would be a disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Here i'am screams out from the disaster and running faster.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"No matter what sort of difficulties, how painful experience is, if we lose our hope, that's our real disaster." -- Dalai Lama
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SteveBrowney That is very funny, from one disaster too another. Let's  seal the deal and have Mickey Arthur as assistant. Game Over!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AHACentre: We participated in ASEAN Regional Forum Disaster Relief Exercise (#ARFDiREx) in Cha-am, Thailand. Here is our album: https:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@bldstphereee: alphabet cannot be with math cos it is a disaster.”finally something from xueting?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	disaster RT @tonitoni48 wishing well.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If I go on a date & its bad, Im just going to stand up and say, "Im an actor, they're all actors, & you're on MTVs disaster date" & run out.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We participated in ASEAN Regional Forum Disaster Relief Exercise (#ARFDiREx) in Cha-am, Thailand. Here is our album: https://t.co/gNzWYQCvYW
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@barryfunite @unitetheunion @UKIP Thought Bangladesh Hindu til natural disaster few yrs ago, US Navy relief ship refused entry by muslim gov
</tweet>
<tweet>
	There's a reason Allah created men &women differently but today’s society is demasculinizing men & defeminizing women,a recipe for disaster.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Should had copied down all of the A2 pure maths notes. crap laa complete disaster man now.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HenchAsPossible: And may those that want you to fail be obese with disappointment, demotivation and disaster.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@yellah12 lol. When my room is meant for a princess hippie like myself..when it's not a complete disaster. I need to clean!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	alphabet cannot be with math cos it is a disaster.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Freshwater #fish contaminated by #Fukushima nuclear disaster quicker & further (400km) due interconnected water ways http://t.co/Iu6Tgw5XL8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JennyJohnsonHi5: When I see a Twitter page cluttered with nothing but @ replies and RTs, I assume that person's house/apartment is a fu…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	working for the master. preventing a disaster. building giant robots from aluminum and plaster. faster i have to build a blaster.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Feel sorry for city fans.Players ruling a club leads to one thing DISASTER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Saddlebag Biscuit Disaster!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	disaster - an event that causes much suffering or loss; a great misfortune;
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@GulPanag Intent good but jump from earlier deliverymodel without learning a thing is sure disaster @iswets @rajivWORLD @gsurya @marutijha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Euroshambles: Cameron uses draft bill to try and stem disaster: David Cameron desperately tried to draw a line under the chaos hittin...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @dublonothing: #ThankJesusFor poverty, starvation, natural disaster, disease, corruption, sexual abuse, and all the other stuff he could…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@jimbologos Personal loan is a disaster waiting to happen. May I suggest prudent spending instead.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Disaster waiting to happen' is also used.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MercuryZelda So misinformation, poor support and lack of communication by the police? What a disaster. :(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Riley is throwing beans and scrambled egg everywhere, its a disaster
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AileenGilsenan @ninoreido Yeah Im free then, whenever you're about! 2in, 2 to go, ydays was a disaster, but my assignment should save me!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This is a bloody disaster today. I have the choice of decaf tea or Yorkshire tea. Akin to having to decide to die by fire or water.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	FEMA Announces Community Resilience Innovation Challenge Recipients http://t.co/4U2CtyyaOb #hsem
</tweet>
