<tweet>
	RT @_ItsMeLucy: ChasingTheSats has been dropped bc AMERICA didn't like it (as there was no drama). I think they should do the documentary o…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_ItsMeLucy: ChasingTheSats has been dropped bc AMERICA didn't like it (as there was no drama). I think they should do the documentary o…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching a documentary on the White House... Yup
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Brilliant Oddie on the Banker species http://t.co/lB8Ghi9bm5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@fatxzach: documentary time” my favorite time of the week.. what are you gonna watch?!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Vague thought of a self produced documentary where we kiss endlessly & that is the climax & that is the only important thing that happens.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching this BMF documentary and the first city Meech names of is Milwaukee... HYPE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	ChasingTheSats has been dropped bc AMERICA didn't like it (as there was no drama). I think they should do the documentary on itv2 for the UK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotherJones: In a Paraguay slum, a children's orchestra makes do with what it's got—with inspiring results: http://t.co/omShjNRCpb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oddie protests against HSBC illegal logging in spoof documentary video http://t.co/zLL7PCczUV via @guardian | Not me, but worth watching...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotherJones: In a Paraguay slum, a children's orchestra makes do with what it's got—with inspiring results: http://t.co/omShjNRCpb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	documentary time
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/fzfD72ikOD Force Quit: Episode 11 - The Inside Gaming Documentary
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Every indie film maker should find time to indulge in the documentary "EDGE OF OUTSIDE"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kanye West – Where The Lonely Kids Go When The Bell Rings (Fan-Made Documentary) http://t.co/6GQgZcZF7Y @TheeRealChino @MichelleKadir sett?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JeremyClarkson Just read yr bit in 12/5 ST. Spot on. Line in Doors' documentary last night, "artists" need to push boundaries. Push on Jez
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Very much enjoyed 'The fantastic Mr Feynman' documentary on the iPlayer. What an extraordinary chap.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotherJones: In a Paraguay slum, a children's orchestra makes do with what it's got—with inspiring results: http://t.co/omShjNRCpb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Oddie protests against HSBC illegal logging in spoof documentary - video http://t.co/cmwvGB49L1 via @guardian
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotherJones: In a Paraguay slum, a children's orchestra makes do with what it's got—with inspiring results: http://t.co/omShjNRCpb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watch an exclusive clip from Hey Bartender, which delves into the minds of cocktail-makers http://t.co/Uw4opMxHbz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Afghanistan War Without End full movie - Afghanistan War Without End documentary See on http://t.co/udw5lqRFZ1 http://t.co/2GtwO7PVGa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ismaalmas: The superb BBC2 documentary Bradford City of dreams, is back on iplayer! Please re-tweet. Thanks. #bradfordcityofdreams #Bra…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Amazing story of an orchestra with instruments their families made with recycled rubbish. 

 http://t.co/bJr4RIWmCL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching this documentary on Harvard Business school
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That documentary makes me wanna live on the edge again
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@thatsteez maybe I just need to watch that Kanye documentary again. Life made more sense this morning
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When your professor starts to put on a black and white documentary. Your class is ruined
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching a porn documentary show on HBO Latino w/a Spanish VoiceOver since it was originally in English. This shit is hilarious #latenight
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@A3Queen thank you for sharing the Parlotones documentary on vimeo - it's so awesome :) hope they'll get to the very top in the US soon!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	John the Baptist documentary on
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Story of Korean War in Colour (Documentary) - Best way to understand what’s the fuzz going in Korea right... http://t.co/wwd9cF54Fk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Story of Korean War in Colour (Documentary) - Best way to understand what’s the fuzz going in Korea right... http://t.co/49w17M4ccx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@tictoctoy Welcome to our TL! Please, check out the progress of the documentary: http://t.co/W8IDuZW9Y7 #anartisandesignertoy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A pleasant Pablo Escobar documentary on the Bio channel right now. Don't tell me how it ends.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @themoceanvibe: HSBC: Helping Sarawak Based Corruption - Good on ya Bill: http://t.co/SPHp59qYlk do bankers have a conscience?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm really watching this documentary about the 80's.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Speaking of terrifying, guess I won't be sleeping: http://t.co/znApja9iL7
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bridging the Bering Strait - Extreme Engineering-Discovery Channel Documentary - http://t.co/y8k0fTERuZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @likeeabosss_: When guys say 'u can read 50 shades of grey but not read the bible?' HYPOCRITES! You can watch porn but not a religion ba…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @kevinbridges86: Documentary on Nat Geo+1 sounds good. A dentist/drug lord. Great idea for a TV series, a respectable professional that'…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching this anti smoking educational documentary is really making want a new port. So I'm gunna pause it for now
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotherJones: In a Paraguay slum, a children's orchestra makes do with what it's got—with inspiring results: http://t.co/omShjNRCpb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotherJones: In a Paraguay slum, a children's orchestra makes do with what it's got—with inspiring results: http://t.co/omShjNRCpb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	30 Brilliant Examples Of Documentary Photography http://t.co/Q0ZUATWVut via @zite
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RaulZepeda_: WHAT A FUCKING MOVIE/DOCUMENTARY! THAT'S WHY YOU'RE ONE OF MY HEROES JUAN MANUEL MARQUEZ!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I recommend, everyone to take the time out to watch this documentary film about bullies!! Watch this… http://t.co/2jhVD6ptsS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Arte documentary "Wilde Wurzeln des WWW" claims: DARPA employees who worked on the first #internet in late 60s were hippies on LSD. Yeey!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Bridge is a documentary about people who jump off the Golden Gate Bridge in San Francisco.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotherJones: In a Paraguay slum, a children's orchestra makes do with what it's got—with inspiring results: http://t.co/omShjNRCpb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotherJones: In a Paraguay slum, a children's orchestra makes do with what it's got—with inspiring results: http://t.co/omShjNRCpb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Been mulling around an idea for a documentary. Hoping we can get the ok to pursue it more.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Prevalent in S.V.! Filmmaker Debbie Lum sets off to make a documentary about men with Asian fetishes and unexpected… http://t.co/79pSYF2b5f
</tweet>
<tweet>
	no I am not watching the jaSon derulo DOCUMENTARY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@_PRlNCE i think you are libyan desert glass <3 http://t.co/b6wG8VAG9x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watched a documentary called Whores Glory...soooooooo Horrible!!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HavensLtd: @southendEcho thanks for article on @HavensLtd TV documentary. shame re photo of @NigelHavens,not flattering!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The #DoubleFine bundle now has 8 game prototypes & a documentary for Windows users if you pay more than the average: http://t.co/AA0jckpkOV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WHAT A FUCKING MOVIE/DOCUMENTARY! THAT'S WHY YOU'RE ONE OF MY HEROES JUAN MANUEL MARQUEZ!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In a Paraguay slum, a children's orchestra makes do with what it's got—with inspiring results: http://t.co/omShjNRCpb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OfficialSting: Check out the trailer for documentary @20FtFromStardom, featuring interviews with Sting, Bruce Springsteen & more! http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/7kt0O6ClPQ Star Wars vs. Star Trek Made Simple ("Documentary" style)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Oddie protests against HSBC illegal logging in spoof documentary - video http://t.co/DhTborFKmV via @guardian
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Exploring @rabite, the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act N what happens when the law and Internet culture collide  http://t.co/oP3880L7bs Support
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just watched a 45 minute documentary on a man who owns his own lion resort and I want nothing more than a pet lion now.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ABC7Courts: Some of the scenes in the documentary are with the body double, Payne testified.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Time to watch a documentary of Jeffrey Dahmer! Hell yes I get pumped on serial killers
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I can't recommend PBS's documentary Johnny Carson: King of Late Night highly enough. http://t.co/GkF81BSuOh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NoCosign Those lyrics mean so much after watching the documentary "Marley."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Everyone loves David Attenborough but let's never forget about Bill Oddie! http://t.co/SSDb5vTDtS via @guardian
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Killermime93 @Matt_LRR I watched a documentary about 9/11 so now I know everything there is to know about 9/11 ever #WakeUpMan! #SadReality
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This Pablo Escobar documentary is pretty interesting.
</tweet>
