<tweet>
	RT @marcuschown: Thanks. I'm so lucky to have been taught by Feynman @scawdery watched documentary on iplayer yesterday remarkable. Enjoyed…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If Planet Earth of some other badass documentary like that was on Netflix right now...damn #discoveygoeshard
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching this Mayweather documentary sippin on that 4
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@really_there Hey great to hear from you! Working on this http://t.co/l9r0Pga43y it's a big one. Will take a year or so full time.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@humanrightsfest @jonathancaouett @sbsfilm on our way, looking forward to the film and forum. #hraff #hraff2013 #filmfestival #documentary
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We're making a #documentary about #babyloss. Pls follow us here & support us. Help us break the silence. Thanks
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I wanted to watch something soothing before bed so I chose a documentary on meth.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The New Shock of The New (2004) - Art Documentary - Robert Hughes: http://t.co/QXOvZhcq4r via @YouTube
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm not sure what Im more upset about, my insomnia or the fact that my wireless Internet decided to cut out halfway thru a vice documentary
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Making a documentary with @WillOfSCIENCE_. This is our elaborate plan! http://t.co/baY60u8x72
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just backed this Zelda documentary, you should too! http://t.co/JRnSw0kot3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Something from the @IdeasMag archive... How to make a radio documentary: http://t.co/AZIhu9Cmn9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BroTonyMuhammad: I am so PROUD of the Brothers from Mosque 27 who put together this Divine documentary on the Acts of our leaders life.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mr_sidebottom: Hey, have you seen they're making a documentary about my fantastic showbiz career? http://t.co/mxQ8OXlzap
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bob Marley Estate Partners With Hyundai For Rare Ad Campaign, Documentary http://t.co/BtwW0hPJLi http://t.co/8hRxrJn61u
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Women equality on one hand, and this behaviour on the other. Pat on the back to those who manage to make a documentary on #india.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@lolixhunter van , pny link download [AIDOL] DOCUMENTARY OF AKB48 NO FLOWER WITHOUT RAIN gk ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Denise_Foth: @NP_20 Good luck today to all final year Documentary Photography and Photo Art students who are handing in their final pro…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Oddie protests against HSBC illegal logging in spoof documentary - video http://t.co/Vxy4oJhAm6 via @guardian
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@georgemonkz8 @mricco99 
Lol 
Forget her !! 
Sky plus national geo 
527 
10 am 11am 12am 
Jesus documentary
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mr_sidebottom: Hey, have you seen they're making a documentary about my fantastic showbiz career? http://t.co/mxQ8OXlzap
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Oddie protests against HSBC illegal logging in spoof documentary - video
http://t.co/xD53KeheVJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	south african history if understood will move you and put ur  mindset in  places it hasn't been #documentary @Scottie_smith7
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Documentary Photographer Boogie about his journey of self-discovery while photographing on the streets in NY. http://t.co/rtuCLGFuTH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MEWshop: Our #documentary #filmmaking #intensive is one that you won't want to miss. It's going to be such a fun week! http://t.co/89iq…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Should i go to sleep or should i stay up and watch this yeezy documentary
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mr_sidebottom: Hey, have you seen they're making a documentary about my fantastic showbiz career? http://t.co/mxQ8OXlzap
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just watched the "Backstage: The Hard Knock Life Tour 1999" documentary. If I could I would go back and get tickets. #legendary #respect
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watched a documentary on Richard Ramirez the serial killer who killed like 13 people the freak
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nickkharris: This Snow On Tha Bluff Documentary Is Very Interesting.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@cbukhelp Great work you are doing. Please stay in touch regarding our documentary. Thanks.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	America Civil War Grant vs Lee - History Channel War Documentary: @YouTube arac?l???yla http://t.co/7nZxTXLT6e
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This documentary is really deep
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This documentary makes me wanna live in the Netherlands
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Premiere & review of freestyle documentary GAME, Only One Can Win (2013) by Polly Green http://t.co/BA5huxxc1Y
</tweet>
<tweet>
	this BTK documentary is really good
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Lost Kingdoms of the Maya Documentary: @YouTube arac?l???yla http://t.co/QE4UNexatl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @espn_nfcnblog: If someone wanted to make a documentary on how to destroy a career, Titus Young has provided all the elements.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LabourHistory: Jonathan Powell interviews 5 of the 9 surviving ex-Foreign Secretaries for a @BBCRadio4 documentary tonight: http://t.co…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mr_sidebottom: Hey, have you seen they're making a documentary about my fantastic showbiz career? http://t.co/mxQ8OXlzap
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Game's 'Documentary' album was such a classic best production on it with orgasmic verses
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hey, have you seen they're making a documentary about my fantastic showbiz career? http://t.co/mxQ8OXlzap
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm in history watching a documentary on WW2. Such fun
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@tinytyyy most likely. I'm just bitter. I'm not trynna watch this documentary ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Designers Republic is raising Kickstarter funding to produce a documentary film about its work! http://t.co/5swTwmqMW9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That was a sad documentary
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @brit_newsman: Inside the 'bunga bunga' party villa as Italian prosecutors demand Berlusconi is jailed for 6 years http://t.co/RGQF8j8Zp…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AbergavennyVice @helenspiteri That documentary's a scam.  He never goes to the loo!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	John Otway, Rock 'n' Roll's greatest failure, flies to Cannes this week for the Film Festival premiere of the... http://t.co/5TlzLAMzcx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Damn it kaylee. I really wanna watch that zombie documentary. ??? lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"The banker is the most self destructive creature that has ever lived"@billoddie's spoof doc lampoons #HSBC http://t.co/Si7hHEG8ro #logging
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tube History documentary on BBC2 this week. http://t.co/OemqnozEIu
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheFoxProblem: Fox @gemcairn just WON A SONY AWARD!!!! For her super personal and heartfelt Radio 1 documentary Bruising Silence.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Netflix watching some documentary... Gotta stay up to date!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	GTFO documentary reaches Kickstarter goals http://t.co/X7jkkaOHMC Production continues on film about female gamers
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ThatIanGilbert: Have you seen this yet? The Paraguayan slum children's orchestra with instruments made of rubbish http://t.co/2JntTJogl…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@theoelliott watched a documentary on it last night. Classic Albums on Sky Arts.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Oddie protests against HSBC illegal logging in spoof documentary - video: In this spoof documentary the n... http://t.co/hvXjMqpZmF
</tweet>
