<tweet>
	@kaisoobaek it was cool tho and we watched a 2hr documentary about attractiveness
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MrParkerBenton Im watching a documentary about PTSD. This stuff is crazy. Us soldiers do some unthinkable stuff.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	AND the JB documentary.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	ocean documentary at 2 am, yeah, #lounging
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Documentary
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Big congrats to @gemcairn & @snappint for @ the BBCR1 documentary 'Bruising Silence' which has just won a Sony Gold- proud to work with you!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching @WWE Hart Dynasty documentary on @netflix. Young Stampede @jneidhart looks like @JackBlack42. -E
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@lenardizag didn't you watch that documentary on plastic Len!!!!! You should know better
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@nitabhalla tht film is documentary film or wht
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Oddie protests against #HSBC illegal logging in spoof documentary - video
http://t.co/sQZ5v9RwrF
via @guardian No spoof consequences !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @pocketoflies: Watching a riri documentary with @joselynpeaches but not paying one bit of attention
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @notwaving: The #skint documentary is having exactly the desired effect: everyone is shitting on the poor, instead of aiming hate at the…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Get_Headspace: From the author of Pay It Forward comes a feel good documentary about the power of being nice @goodvirusdotorg http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Red Bull Music Academy have put together the doco the DFA label, home to LCD Soundsystem and Hot Chip http://t.co/JXZ9DL5l3f
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@vizzymasters I've been bumping game before the documentary niggga !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DynamicAfrica: Incredible 10-minute documentary on African-Americans who emigrated to Stalinist Russia http://t.co/YzCvrZphg2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SnoopDogg reincarnated is an amazing documentary! I'm glad I watched it!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Studio Space for Documentary Interview (Brooklyn or Manhattan)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	3am and i can't sleep so i'm watching a documentary called The War on Weed
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/HdcMQLWd57 The YouTube Documentary is HERE!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching a burlesque documentary and getting really upset that I wasn't born in the 20's.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HuffPostWomen: WATCH: the girls who will actually run the world. http://t.co/0ClR724NH2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That lowrider documentary was sick!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching documentary on Malaysian cuisine. Tummy grumbles. I want food! Better change the channel.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@boringgbetty well documentary I mean HAHAHA
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@danmackey87 It’s awesome. Weirdly, was listening to it whilst also listening to the Giorgio Moroder documentary on Radio 2. Kinda weird.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	For now, it's time to open the window, turn on the TV, and watch some soccer or random documentary (whichever is on lol) till I fall asleep.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sbilliald: #prisoners a good series but remember twice as many people get a community order each year as a prison sentence. Next docume…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/J0oWhckT3c Batman Unmasked - The Psychology of the Dark Knight [Documentary]
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ziggy Marley Talks Road Trip Documentary | Watch the video Yahoo ...  http://t.co/w3QWTUlBXX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	tonight 7 PM "Jihad on Terrorism" documentary will be screened in the mosque of Louvain la neuve & discussion
http://t.co/e86swwAM3h
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BBC documentary celebrates 150 years of the Tube http://t.co/LlzDSqZGPN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Oddie protests against HSBC illegal logging in spoof documentary - video http://t.co/gmIzwexCEl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@rustymk2 I like that documentary.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A very impressing photo documentary of low priced slaves. http://t.co/YpAJUPbgNJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sitting on my couch, eating ramen and watching a documentary about the Salem Witch Trials. Pretty content.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @jack_welch: To me Lincoln the winner tonight..Loved the movie..Argo documentary better than Hollywood version
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This #documentary is going to be amazing.  Finally seem to be getting past all the road blocks we've hit. #crossingmyfingers
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Oddie protests against HSBC & illegal logging in spoof Banker Watch documentary video
http://t.co/f37OY58TxL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Craigslist joe is a great documentary. It gives me faith in people again.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Don't know what I'm angrier with. The fact the movie Idiocracy is more like a "coming of age documentary" or @HJBenjamin no longer has a van
</tweet>
<tweet>
	http://t.co/45Wii2VPDl is giving away a complete cinematic wedding documentary package valued up to $8000.http://t.co/Us4GorwkNr
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I could watch Bo Jackson's documentary "Bo Know's" so many times!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching a riri documentary with @joselynpeaches but not paying one bit of attention
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @char2611: @sausage1820 I hope they make another chicken shop documentary #WHATMAKESFINANCIALSENSE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tired of making money, am on to making history, so ama keep it realer than a documentary .. Ralph
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@emilysNOTmanley: Currently watching a documentary on soap” 1 million uses
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video from @domingo0022iway http://t.co/oIexUYq52Y The YouTube Documentary Coming on May 18th
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sausage1820 I hope they make another chicken shop documentary #WHATMAKESFINANCIALSENSE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	For those who watched Today Tonight, at the end they mentioned a documentary to find what happend to Sammy Salma, airs Saturday ABC2 8:30pm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A compelling documentary on one woman's search for her family years after Vietnam's Operation Babylift http://t.co/9ksvNafhTl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Super Size Me(2004)documentary/Morgan personally explores the consequences on his health of a diet of solely McDonald's food for one month.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VibeMagazine: #MustWatch: One Of The Best Fan-Made @KanyeWest Documentaries: "Where the Lonely Kids Go When The Bell Rings" http://t.co…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DrMichaelChick This one is fine. uncle, I'm looking forward to your documentary 'The Right To Live'.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JakeShimabukuro: Thanks for all the wonderful comments about the documentary "Life On Four Strings." Thanks for watching! I'm playing i…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LAFF_Utrecht: And of course Hivos Audience Award winner for best documentary Gimme the Power by Olallo Rubio will also play @MelkwegCin…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Jay Z   Reasonable Doubt The Documentary: http://t.co/IjaUHDDXdB via @youtube
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @NUPeopleMagUK: Please watch this inspirational documentary by Daniel Mbaku, about African Caribbean Achievers in the U.K  http://t.co/W…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@LouiEv_ yeah I like Tyson too. You've seen his documentary?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	if ur a Programme Producer & is looking for a new long running new documentary inbox me your number 2 talk about a meeting
</tweet>
