<tweet>
	Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while they don't know me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while they don't know me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	All the drama is uncalled for tho... Like calm the fuck down
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Good on Gai-Singo drama and some insights into Brisbane drug culture http://t.co/sNTT7h7zu9 …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MyNameIsYusuf_ English isn't so hard I have drama and it's shit ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have to do a warm up for drama today, pray for me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I look like such a mong with my hair done for my drama exam today
</tweet>
<tweet>
	why pledis didn't release any info about Juyeon's participation in this drama >_< ugh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Giving a career talk this evening @Gaietyschool. Getting into and out of drama school. 01-6799277 to reserve a seat. http://t.co/WZBR6mgMZg
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have my drama practical exam today, eeeekkkk..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And the Summer drama begins
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while they don't know me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	omg why are all the producers producing new shows? Even the producers from Revenge is producing a new drama called Betrayal. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Some people are so drama-queens..oooff the #publicitystunts they perform time and again ..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @baabyJackee: If your boyfriend is someone else's babydaddy your gonna have drama. Be prepared .
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ADSkingofbeer Because it's kind of an old drama I understand if it's not available, but here's to holding hope in my hand. <-- hehe JOJ...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	drama revision or bed? hmm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Whatevs though ?drama is for dumb bitches!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RealityTvBlogr I feel ya! It seems that no matter what, I will never live a drama-free life. Ive considered cutting all ties & moving to AZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@mightypalace have to get ticket first drama's
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @YourAwayMessage: i cannot wait to get out of high school and be an adult with 0 fucking drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stop making drama fuck
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Luyanda__ then drama will come out
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Drama exam today :/
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@blobyblo which one do you prefer.. drama or music?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Drama and music today! Rest is a skive easy!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bitches and there drama <<
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@torib88 you aint the only one..drama is just childish
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ferallike @SherrieGG If the entirety of the Bush admin was somehow worked into an award-winning sitcom or drama, ppl might pay attention.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @premierleague: Drama at the Madejski as Carlos Tevez clears an Adrian Mariappa header off the Man City line after 78 mins. #BPL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DjHustlenomics: Gotta Couple Niggas Thats Down To Ride For A Homicide When It's Drama Time.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	well honey, my life my drama my mess. u dont like it... keep ur shittalk away from me. MIND UR OWN BUSINESS.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NathPowley @ryramsden22 @AnthonyTognola fuck me, god help my little girl! She'll be a nun... Although I would prefer a boy! Less drama x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AIwaysRemember: I never gave you a reason to hate me. You're just creating your own little drama out of pure insecurity.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Twitter is the place to go when you get too much satisfaction from reading drama on Facebook.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My mom doesn't believe that I'm ill, and I have p.e and drama today. Kill me now
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GodsFighter_: God, You are stronger then all this drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @IndiaToday: Sad how handful of families control Indian politics: Another family drama unveiling as @lalupra... Read more at http://t.co…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	There's less drama when they are on tour I like it
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lose weight then all your underwear doesn't fit. Hayi. Hahaha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Damn, cant remember the last time i tweeted!! Any twitter drama tonight?!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Im getting annoyed by all those enchancer's drama (im an enchancer too) but damn its too much already.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	All these lessons SUCK today. Only Drama is good.
</tweet>
