<tweet>
	RT @affxtionINA: [INFO] Krystal is being strongly considered for the female lead role in new drama ‘Heirs‘ along with Lee Min Ho and Park S…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@GetNailedFakeIt @roll87jonathan @chiccabello @lianna1310 @Tantrumhairx better service, No stress, No ego, No drama, No BAD batch of hair
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@EmilyHoneymanX we are watching it in drama at the moment! ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @paris89k: Made in Chelsea is the best and I don't care if its set up! Still good drama
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MsMickJagger dat drama there aint worth it
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ltsTyga: Best thing about being single? No drama, no fighting, no crying, no feeling, no confusion, no worries, no problem.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TeamBieberGasm: Justin is releasing new music = new videos, interviews, new live performances. No drama. Happy Beliebers. http://t.co/E…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The second teaser of the new drama series Shark is revealed:  On May 14, the second teaser of Shark was releas... http://t.co/OiDNaJ4vW8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	[kpop] The second teaser of the new drama series Shark is revealed http://t.co/pzM9sY5eWi
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @moonjunka: A producer should try make a drama and hire all the members of ZE:A to cast in the drama because most of them have acting ex…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	All any1 can hear is you talking about the amount of drama @ your 9 person party Im sure all that happened is some year10 slipped over #ugh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @missgerrard88: i seriously think the phillipine drama on tv3 is the only great thing in it. seriously. THE ONLY THING
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Political Incorrectness In All Its Splendour. follow @LifeOfIRC it will be your little window  into IRC life and drama. #Anonymous #OWS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	so not in the mood for drama
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Uganda football drama my TL is heavy with. God help this nation. Minister reading a statement they've only met 4 the 1st time @ the presser?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	To sum up. He doesn't want to go to India. He doesn't mind if you do. Where is the Fucky drama?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GirIFacts: #50ThingsAboutMe I'm a girl I dont smoke drink or party every weekend I dont sleep around or start drama to get attention Ye…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NikkiMcLeodFoto i know, have kept them on sky + so may have an appointment with the duvet and some drama x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kein Tag ohne Twitter-Drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wasted about half an hour of my life listening to Sharon banging on #again #drama #boring #killme #please
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Group assignments and the drama they carry along with em O_o :""""""""""D yaaa ne!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	so wanna start the drama again and then leave ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ThatDopeBlasian: #IfOnlyPeopleWould realize that life is too short to be starting unnecessary drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sitting in drama doing the actions that our starbursts tell us to do
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Definitely almost corrected a grammar error but I don't want to get involved in the drama. Haha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chem over already. Drama is a chill today.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AsherWest: All this Twitter drama is infecting my feed #goaway #children
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Bristol_Culture: Frankie, a new six-part drama starting tonight on BBC One, is the latest television show to be filmed in Bristol: http…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	So glad there is no drama at college now, load off my back :D now let's boss this exam
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's always drama drama drama!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I would hate to know what it feels like to have baby mamma drama lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ShinieEsther: i don't actually hate facebook i just hate those certain people and all their drama in it..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tell me who's win on this drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sitting in drama with Cerys,liv&pat jut doing
</tweet>
<tweet>
	rice wreath in support of #Sora's new drama @reveramess @TSL1001 via daum http://t.co/WQvAYgF2Aw
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It pulls you away from all the drama of today's generation
</tweet>
