<tweet>
	RT @GarryDCollier: Some people's lives are just such a drama.. Don't get how people enjoy it.. It drives my insane being caught up in stupi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	looks like all the drama is set to continue http://t.co/lp2jI895ml
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm too short to stand in the way for drama, imma let it pass #be_gone
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_ItsMeLucy: ChasingTheSats has been dropped bc AMERICA didn't like it (as there was no drama). I think they should do the documentary o…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	She did not know herself whom she loved.. Real stupid when women acting like this.. She should make her choice faster then less drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dreading my drama gcse exam next thursday so scared:'(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Nayeli_____: Im not even about the drama, I just wanna have a good time
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm tired of drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Drama On Twitter Is So Weakkk >>>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@babershafiq There is nothing to tell sure, as you know we have several Drama Politicions
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just get this one drama exam done today and then I've no more work to do until September
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_ItsMeLucy: ChasingTheSats has been dropped bc AMERICA didn't like it (as there was no drama). I think they should do the documentary o…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while they don't know me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	chaotic longest day in years i swear, hella drama & i dislike it.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	School and drama exam will be shown today yay -.-
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@KreAtin_Drama: Lucy said her life will be ruined” dude she wont even wanna come out the house
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I feel like every time I get on Twitter I get drama why?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The gays that are in the scene of Atlanta's drama are pathetic to me. and I can talk because no one really knows me. #PREACH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wow if you're gonna not talk to me because drama with someone else, that doesn't involve you, you're ridiculous.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	TNT: WE KNOW DRAMA
</tweet>
<tweet>
	is the drama over?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Final drama exam of year 12 today!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @justinemorleyy: After biology i only have a drama exam then im completely done.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	u know when your otp is starred in the same drama and them being the main character of where they're gonna end up together
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @UnstableByNarry: "louis pooped on a fan" i know u guys want some drama and all but srsly
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@ThtBIGBootyGirl: it will be ! & I'm the one to blame lol” naw whoever said it first . Go to IG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	IZ U BOUT WHAT I'M BOUT IF U BOUT WHAT I'M BOUT U BOUT DRAMA THUGGIN IN BROAD DAY WIT 4 GLOCKZ A KNIFE&A CHOPPER #LILWAYNE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wish I knew why everything has to be such a big drama
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@TheBossGirls: Petty drama is not worth acting out of character for & simple-minded chicks who start shit are not worth your time" #;)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Breaking bad used to be my fave drama but now its homeland. Show is just too good!!! And Sgt Brody is just... Too good
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You're just too selfish , that's why we hate you . Our drama group broke in about just two weeks .
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheKidGotSwagge: We just want to make greyson happy, right? So stop the drama and stop fight!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	[Info] Juyeon is participating in the drama “Monstar” where she got a kiss scene with BEAST’s Junhyung http://t.co/gpbnGZ0SAG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PandoDaily: Say what you will about bitcoin: It's disruptive in the most raw sense of the word. http://t.co/3FPDrRd77t
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheKidGotSwagge: We just want to make greyson happy, right? So stop the drama and stop fight!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Drama performance today!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In all honesty, you're a really pretty girl, but the drama...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	ChasingTheSats has been dropped bc AMERICA didn't like it (as there was no drama). I think they should do the documentary on itv2 for the UK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Science,maths, history,drama = what a crap day me and my mates have ahead !! of us today ...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	in drama I'm an anorexic girl named catherine who dies at the end awh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Sahoyah @LilEdieMonsoon But PLEASE, young Sir, enjoy the drama. When you are apparently the center of a poonany throwdown, you may as well.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Eh quinton friend is so loud, drama queen of note
</tweet>
<tweet>
	good luck in your drama girls @ARichardson25 @JBAbbieR xxxx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i shit u not we have the scariest teacher ever for drama today i
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CuteLoveMsgs: Things That Irritate Me:
- When people lie to me
- Drama
- Monday
- Being compared to others
- When people judge me while…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@HasanJawwad I actually want a recount so that this drama can be done and over with.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@katprescott77 @Meg_Prescott This is the drama we can see?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Too. Much. Drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Nayeli_____: Im not even about the drama, I just wanna have a good time
</tweet>
