<tweet>
	Why am I even going in for drama revision
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@Jolie_Juliaa: Starting twitter drama with my boyfriend >>" fags
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rin's favorite manga genres
are: action, comedy, and
emotional drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I hear there was major drama at the Justin Bieber concert sunday night - apparently they stole 19 BMX's and 41 Tricycles.???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The feeling you just finished watching your favorite Korean drama of the week. TTT____TTT #MissingYou #Bogosipda ???? ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Final GCSE drama performance tomorrow and I only went and got the main character. So scared :S
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Is it wrong to be slightly fangirling over Ben Stephenson? He was so passionate about TV Drama at @rocliffeforum that it was inspiring.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SouthLondonGirl: Interesting to see so many women saying they can't/won't watch 'dead women' dramas. I'm sick of murder being the mains…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Betta find female friends that dont cause drama
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Drama that was embarrassing
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Flashowns idk what all the drama is but we've done a lot for u jay its not right for u too disrespect @_brig_  regardless of the situation
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @imWilISmith: Life becomes so much better when you decide not to care. Just live for the moment and don't let the drama bring you down.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#TRASH! RT @Trxton If u dnt ff Revenge, I dnt know what u're watching. Drama series don't come bigger than Revenge. Best at the moment. End.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Starting twitter drama with my boyfriend >>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OnlyForSwift: 3 things Miley Cyrus wanted and she got it.
1- More hate
2- More attention
3- More drama
Lets hear the applaus for Miley …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	All this drama made me mis the bear put scene on GoT. Fudge.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pooing myself for this drama exam, ahh?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BenSaadna @djcharlottes I'm not really sure if there's a show for that... Like comedy, drama, romance? Can I get a genre lawl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	full day of drama now this is why jesus died on the cross
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Gilo drama korea aku hah
</tweet>
<tweet>
	But you can't never go anywhere with drama ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @imWilISmith: Life becomes so much better when you decide not to care. Just live for the moment and don't let the drama bring you down.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LaurenGoodger: “@courtoneillx: The thought of drama 1st is making me want to cry”don't cry Drama was my favourite lesson!!! Enjoy it ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I dont understand all the dan drama on tumblr yesterday.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @itinamarie: FACT : DARA PLAYED A JAPANESE ROLE IN A KOREAN DRAMA~ SHE WAS A NINJA~ (iljimae)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"dont do this or that itll cause too much drama" ok im sorry but stfu
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CauseWereSexual: Everybody’s all “drama this and drama that”

I’m over here like “Hey boo, you wanna cuddle?”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	drama queen
</tweet>
<tweet>
	people still do drama? wot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	People who creat their own drama deserve their own karma
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Snooki is having contractions every 5 min and is only one cm? This doesnt even make sense. Tv is so fake. Or snooki is a little drama bitch
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hey"@Weza_Solange: Good Morning Twitterville! Have a positive Drama Free Tuesday y'all... I know its hard on these twitter streets, just try
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ah drama practice now , laziness
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @imWilISmith: Life becomes so much better when you decide not to care. Just live for the moment and don't let the drama bring you down.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	-Ms. Drama was drunk when she left the building...lOl.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@Essy_Jhay: I feel like tucson is just so full of drama & bullshit."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just want to be friends with a chill group of real people that don't care for drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	CONTROL YO HOES
YOU LET EM TALK TO YOU CRAZY
YOU GOT BABY MAMA DRAMA
YOU AIN'T EVEN GOT YOU NO BABY!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@semadivad David Ames, the Demi Moore of continuing drama
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@imWilISmith: Life becomes so much better when you decide not to care. Just live for the moment and don't let the drama bring you down."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I hate how everyone speaks on my family's drama and makes my mom look like the bad one. SHUT UP! YOU DON'T KNOW A DAMN THING!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BezCore looks good fingers crossed mate I'll do mine and show you them I got paid for it straight into my account no drama's
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lmao Ms. Drama is funny.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	plus I have 3 exams and a face rash so my life is basically a drama series in itself.
</tweet>
