<tweet>
	RT @InjusticeFacts: The United States sells an average of $68 Billion in weapons each year to Middle Eastern dictators and 'kings'.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Heat nadert finale in Eastern Conference http://t.co/HZnAeCendY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Plane_Talking: Turkish fighter jet crashes near Syrian border: A Turkish F-16 fighter jet crashed in south-eastern Turkey on ... http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In #Brussels at a #democracy & #humanrights working group meeting of the #EU Eastern Partnership Civil Society Forum @eapcsf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @tichophil_: @Eyes_Quin #HataUwe na Kiingereza Kama ya Eastern Europe,Tina tunajua  umetoka Eastern Kenya (Meru) where the worst English…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Top 5 video games from Eastern Europe http://t.co/NmP11KNdaH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Drake looks middle eastern
</tweet>
<tweet>
	check out Bear Woznick live interview 10:30 am Eastern Catholic TV “@kroro43: On This is the Day tomorrow @BearsWave http://t.co/AjMHSzfhXF”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	No Wait at 3:11 AM Eastern Daylight Time #PHX ^0 ^1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The next solar eclipse will be a hybrid eclipse on Nov. 3. 2013. It will be visible from eastern North America, southern Europe and Africa.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Holts170 appreciate the eastern conference quarterfinal win tonight #nyr
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JackBauer__24: I am just ahead of cancer as the leading cause of death in Middle Eastern men.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @uptightcommuter: @ed11e it's a football landmark I agree but it should compared with Marathon becoming Snickers not the liberation of t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SydneyUniLibs: a free day to the Will & Grace campaign? They're currently chatting to voters on Eastern Avenue. #usudecides http://t.co…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This eastern standard time is messing me up big time I'm not use to this at all
</tweet>
<tweet>
	the highest sublimest eastern view of_tru death _is_when u physically _dont die in your_deepest vision u see/watch/experience
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dear God, it is 2am central, 3am eastern.  Let Andrew Wiggins go to UK for basketball.  Or curse wherever else he goes.  I'm cool with both.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Eyes_Quin #HataUwe na Kiingereza Kama ya Eastern Europe,Tina tunajua  umetoka Eastern Kenya (Meru) where the worst English is spoken Hides!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ahead  of the naming of DCEs and MCEs, NDC party leaders in the Eastern Region are said to be taking monies from candidates #citinews
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Urbanization and surface warming in eastern China: Urbanization is one of the most significant processes in land... http://t.co/Acd53lvf1V
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ahead  of the naming of DCEs and MCEs, NDC party leaders in the Eastern Region are said to be taking monies from candidates #citinews
</tweet>
<tweet>
	South eastern is just getting worse
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Dan_Mac94 consequences of the peace and the eastern bloc for me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Online entry is open until midnight tonight! U12/9 race has a full entry!! Follow the link to enter:... http://t.co/WSADtQlhx5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Im guaranteeing #miamiheat advance to eastern conf finals #nbaplayoffs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @abscbnsports: ABS-CBN Sports will air ALL the NBA Eastern Conf. Finals and Western Conf. Finals games starting next week and the entire…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I always find eastern europeans are much better than the English, much better work ethic. No wonder they always find work!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @abscbnsports: ABS-CBN Sports will air ALL the NBA Eastern Conf. Finals and Western Conf. Finals games starting next week and the entire…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ed11e it's a football landmark I agree but it should compared with Marathon becoming Snickers not the liberation of the eastern block.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CarolaAnkar @CheerfulKiwi @Spemki_Molsen @dawkinsassange @haloefekti i don need a lecture on hatred for wolves. I'm in eastern finland.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tours of North America Capitals of Eastern Canada Spend 7  days touring  Capitals of Eastern Canada  #travel #deals http://t.co/zp9BwQzT8k
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Eastern Freeway can seriously go fuck itself #melbournetraffic
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Reform Of Middle Eastern Militaries: Lessons From Indonesia – Analysis http://t.co/Yy80AUPvf2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	From Nations to Provinces: The Demographic Collapse of Southern and Eastern Europe < Share @CraigJWilly's concerns http://t.co/9QMlkTj3UW
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cant wait to see the new @bmayzee video ICE CREAM SHOOTER  today at 8pm eastern on youtube! BMayzee spits str8 no hook one of my favorites
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@__laurenhart go clean up you eastern European slave haha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Eastern Band of Cherokee Indians (EBCI) Council: Rescue bears at Chief Saunooke Bear Park  http://t.co/KdGNLXO9lL via @change
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @manekshaws: UPA has managed 2 turn India Shining into India Begging. Get ready 4 massive power cuts this summer.
http://t.co/ATpDypnTBc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just 131500'd how to get somewhere, without realising it's only 1.3kms away. I don't know the eastern suburbs at all.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Tribal Chief/Council of Cherokee Indians: Stop the Inhumane Treatment of Bears in Cherokee, NC https://t.co/9stXDtThRQ via @change
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The only type of turtle you can eat UN the eastern parts is a turtle that people from the south call "Coots" or "cooters"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	EPIC bottlenecks awaited at both ends of the Chembur Santacruz link road and the Eastern Freeway too! @SerenaMenon @tajmahalfoxtrot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotolifeMusic: New B Mayzee video  ICE CREAM SHOOTER goes online Tuesday14th at 8pm eastern time on youtube/twitter/facebook etc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Japan to make a nuclear push in Eastern Europe: http://t.co/uOMDCpUY7B | There were no takers just six months ago...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @IAmTheWiseOwl: @JennifLawrences Vote for Jennifer's hometown school Louisville Eastern High School in the Southeast Region for vans! ht…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Freaks be up at this time especially if they're in the eastern time zone
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Middle Eastern Hackers Attacking U.S. Power Companies http://t.co/LGS3zwSyYc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PabloEscobird: Clowns to the left of me, jokers to the right, here I am, stuck on a shitty south eastern train....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Plane_Talking: Turkish fighter jet crashes near Syrian border: A Turkish F-16 fighter jet crashed in south-eastern Turkey on ... http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @abscbnsports: ABS-CBN Sports will air ALL the NBA Eastern Conf. Finals and Western Conf. Finals games starting next week and the entire…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Off to Vienna today to run the second compliance workshop with the Eastern Europe groups - via Zurich
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New B Mayzee video  ICE CREAM SHOOTER goes online Tuesday14th at 8pm eastern time on youtube/twitter/facebook etc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @abscbnsports: ABS-CBN Sports will air ALL the NBA Eastern Conf. Finals and Western Conf. Finals games starting next week and the entire…
</tweet>
