<tweet>
	RT @Redpeter99: #Cameron met Obama on Monday.  Visited Boston and Eastern Seaboard on Tuesday. What's he doing today apart from hiding from…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oi Sherece, send us some if that middle eastern weather please...

sharing is caring
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pacers though. With Wade’s knee, the Eastern Conference championship could be very interesting.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Redpeter99: #Cameron met Obama on Monday.  Visited Boston and Eastern Seaboard on Tuesday. What's he doing today apart from hiding from…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I will pay someone $7 (that's all I have) to type up my summer TV schedule (premiere dates & eastern daylight times) and tape it to my wall.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	With effect from April 01, 2013, a maximum wage of Rs 214 has been fixed for Haryana and minimum of Rs 135 for North Eastern States. #NREGA
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RSJCheam Haha not that I saw. It's a bit worrying as the roads around mine all lead to the Eastern Avenue :S
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PrepSchoolBtch: Every time a Middle-Eastern man gets up from his seat on an airplane, my heart jumps to my throat. #prepschoolbitch
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@burbagea I recall an Eastern European film about trains & bath&razor suicide :/ Did enjoy the Graham Greene film though.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tangina. Pacers in the Eastern Conference Finals?? This is gonna be one boring match up
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why do eastern Europeans have to shake hands everytime they see there mates at work? Why not a true English mate to mate hello #alr8youprick
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Redpeter99: #Cameron met Obama on Monday.  Visited Boston and Eastern Seaboard on Tuesday. What's he doing today apart from hiding from…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Looking forward to @the_CIEH Eastern Region Spring Forum today with @JigsawPSPH & @sarejames3 at the Wood Green Animal Shelter #CIEHSF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Have fun while you strengthen and tone your body with Pilates!  http://t.co/TH4ylCzIZ4 #exercise
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@m23congordc  it's  MAI MAI of eastern drc general kombi hillaire  who seized beni town
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @J_Yanez_305: Heat end the bulls season tomorrow. 1 game away from returning to the Eastern Conference Finals. #heatfamily #heatnation #…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Praying the KNICKS get this 3 game win streak and move on to the eastern conference finals! Leggoooooo!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Photo: In May of 1995 Paris-based Tunisian designer Azzedine Alaïa created a Middle Eastern inspired hooded... http://t.co/a5cku4jCgP
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why is Great Eastern not picking up my calls and why other companies bugging me to join them!? Annoyinggg~
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Birds of prey still #migrating above the eastern desert of #Egypt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Prep softball roundup: Waupun clinches Eastern Wisconsin title; Beaver Dam downs West Bend East http://t.co/2xGeL7UhLf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The sorts of things that happen in Eastern Nigeria is Bizarre
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Off to @The_CIEH Eastern Region Spring Forum today with @sarejames3 & @stanleystats1 Will be tweeting throughout the day using #CIEHSF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	THIS IS FITNESS
THE HEALTH BENEFITS OF SKIPPING

Skipping is a serious form of exercise training in Eastern... http://t.co/RcNFzHBiyL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Nav News: SE Coast, Solent, Cowes:
Small Craft Channel
The eastern pair of yellow lateral buoys marking the small... http://t.co/uohpfmNkoc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@m23congordc  whatever  drc gov, sadc  and UN  can do people of eastern  drc have the right to fight 4 good governance in their country
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@cantyanty just got in from an unexpected shoot all day. I'm gonna hit ya tmrw at around 7-8...eastern standard time.?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sydney Traffic HAZARD Metal - EASTERN CREEK M4 Mwy at Service Centres #sydtraffic #trafficnetwork
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mcDarke the guy actually said don't worry about it...I tried I failed I don't get paid...eastern European work ethic < ? love that! ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	YAKKUM Bali field trials in remote Eastern Indonesia continued last week in West Sumba, a remote and dry island... http://t.co/6iqHjtEuLo
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The eastern star is the most beautiful flower in the world.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Redpeter99: #Cameron met Obama on Monday.  Visited Boston and Eastern Seaboard on Tuesday. What's he doing today apart from hiding from…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@FiosArmy @stunplxy so you'll take advice from the middle eastern kid, right?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	.@Nunawading_sc tops National Swimming Championships for the fourth time in five years. @swimvic Via @twr_eastern http://t.co/3ptAXX43ku
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Pacers: With the possibility of hosting the Eastern Conference Finals, registration is open for priority presale access: http://t.co/HI…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Does anyone stay in the Eastern Cape for their whole life by choice...?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@noodlemage spellcasting methods that would technically count as eastern-influenced? I have positional, seal and tag/charm casting sorted...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Caraway extraction is used to soothe muscle sores and clear the cold. #SpicyFacts
</tweet>
<tweet>
	For a tournament being held in the Eastern Time Zone, there sure isn't a lot of EST representation: 1 of 8 teams left (Liberty) in EST
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@hastr0 from one middle eastern to another, happy birthday, stro
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Climate Action: Public debate in Southern and Eastern Europe #climate #SEE http://t.co/x0uzEA9Ebg
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AmelTerzic: I'm an outsider on twitter. Everbody is from eastern Bosnia and I'm from the western
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @moggda: @star_pumpkin  As Nigel Farage quoted "the cabbages got picked for generations before Eastern Europeans arrived."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm an outsider on twitter. Everbody is from eastern Bosnia and I'm from the western
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pacers close in on final: The Indiana Pacers are just one win away from reaching the Eastern Conference finals... http://t.co/cPElG1VuAF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RupiPANAICH w'a into nursery & primary shl edu presently in the Eastern/Niger delta area of Nigeria. Fees are subsidized, std very high.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pacers close in on final: The Indiana Pacers are just one win away from reaching the Eastern Conference finals... http://t.co/eucMhrY1UL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What timezone + coast are you from? — Eastern Time and I'm from the East Coast :) http://t.co/vtKWwyHVkH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Saamic @kaseeyyex sorry I'm not the right middle eastern
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Gunmen kill 12, injure 3 in Iraq: A group of unknown gunmen have attacked a line of stores in eastern Baghdad in... http://t.co/vZXBlbZuQU
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PiltonVillage: "As grey traces of dawn tinge the Eastern sky.." remember Rush? That's what it looks like today. Mist fog or fine precip…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ebecirovicc I feel like everyone's from eastern Bosnia on here lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Redpeter99: #Cameron met Obama on Monday.  Visited Boston and Eastern Seaboard on Tuesday. What's he doing today apart from hiding from…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pacers close in on final - The Indiana Pacers are just one win away from reaching the Eastern Conference finals fo... http://t.co/qCdPFIcLQu
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oh eastern Ohio I know nothing about you, except Athens. Charting new territory, there's nothing here #MyrtleVacation
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Cameron met Obama on Monday.  Visited Boston and Eastern Seaboard on Tuesday. What's he doing today apart from hiding from #pmqs?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BakerGeorgeT: The eastern half of BC goes BC Liberal. The west coast goes NDP. Can anyone say pipeline standoffs? http://t.co/vbVF8Z5Y6…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Move to close Eastern Cape schools criticized
http://t.co/4a5fdMViaM
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GiovanniTorre: @SenatorLudlam is on something called the "reddit" tonight doing an "Ask Me Anything" at 7.30pm eastern.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Where is your manifesto la? #Bhutan2013 RT @bhutanpdp: PDP has a specific plan to develop eastern Bhutan http://t.co/E0iK2cMZQz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The @Pacers are taking Care of @Knicks,just wondering if we heading for Last year Quarter final as Eastern Finals this Year @NBA @espn
</tweet>
<tweet>
	, suffering Eastern sweats and Tangerian bone-grindings and migraines of  China under junk-withdrawal in Newark’s bleak furnished room,
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Alternative Health Care 4 Dogs Facing Cancer - Apollo's Story: a combination of Western & Eastern treatments-best of http://t.co/SKtvPHgldd
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lol a no bullshit all middle eastern people are UGLY AF like the arabs the ppl who  work at 7eleven are all ugly
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BakerGeorgeT: The eastern half of BC goes BC Liberal. The west coast goes NDP. Can anyone say pipeline standoffs? http://t.co/vbVF8Z5Y6…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	(Featured Eastern Orthdox feast) Today is the Feast day of St. Achillius of Larissa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Shout out to all the Eastern grads that are somewhere slumped lol
</tweet>
