<tweet>
	Eastern Fwy, Balwyn North - Traffic Alert, Left-hand lane blocked inbound before the Chandler Highway… http://t.co/BceZGWALVC #victraffic
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CallumKirkwood Eastern conference final bruins v rangers. #biggame
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Amateur Radio - Solar activity surges: Space Weather report a sunspot on the sun's eastern limb is crackling w... http://t.co/ETqnguFV8f
</tweet>
<tweet>
	But the competition is sad! The eastern conference finals will be more of a challenge then the playoff finals.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	EASTERN EUROPE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	FUCK YOU SOUTH EASTERN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Imo state use to be d most peaceful state in the Eastern part of Nigeria. Wht really went wrong???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A place all our own http://t.co/RRrJblzEVm via @TheMarke
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BiH Minister at Forum on Cultural Cooperation of China and Countries of Central and Eastern Europe http://t.co/q7c6AZe05h #bosnia #politics
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A mature understanding of the role of the internet in the Middle Eastern revolutions http://t.co/2n2DTyexnM vía @P2P_Foundation
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@__DigDeep what bout middle eastern bitch?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TrippyTaylor23 Eastern Washington territory. You?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Vote4Squash: #Squash is growing in emerging markets such as Malaysia, Egypt, India, the Americas & Eastern Europe. #vote4squash http://…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Heat-Pacers Eastern Conference Finals...My thought. Memphis is in WCF..SAS-GSW is open series..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Reunion Island lies off the eastern coast of Madagascar. At 970 square miles,its the largest of the Mascarene islands.I live in a lost place
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @diplo: This bar is so eastern european.. Just cigarettes and heavy metal and wu tang shirts
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Maroush Middle Eastern Signature Sweets, Cookies and Chocolate available  all year around in 1kg & ½ kg boxes . For Orders Call 52892431
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Eastern Night Wasp
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VenturaBusWatch: Eastern Freeway especially slow going this evening. @Vic_Premier your EastWest Link will just put more cars on the fre…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@Dook3_: @DeezHeavy_M1 My Co-Worker Thought You Were Persian Or Middle Eastern Cuz Of Your Name Lol” But i am... http://t.co/nK4XMqYM0Q
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Anatolia Turkish Restaurant at Far East Plaza is gone. No more affordable, good middle Eastern food :( Anyone know if they've moved?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Active_UK: Enjoy the atmosphere at Great Perkins Eastern #Run and fundraise for charity on 13th October: http://t.co/kOoWTX28UQ @Perkin…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DeezHeavy_M1 My Co-Worker Thought You Were Persian Or Middle Eastern Cuz Of Your Name Lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Shit the NBA prolly asked Miami to lose 1 so they can make money before they just sweep the whole Eastern Conference LOL 7 down 9 to go!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bill Browder: my father was the biggest communist in America, so I said I'm gonna become the biggest capitalist in eastern Europe #osloff
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cancel pavi . Now im at Great Eastern Mall .
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A mature understanding of the role of the internet in the Middle Eastern revolutions http://t.co/qrRamUqWqe
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Really chuffed to have 3 new dates in the diary for Autumn/Winter Persian & Middle Eastern Cookery classes @Divertimenti cookery school!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A mature understanding of the role of the internet in the Middle Eastern revolutions - http://t.co/V4af2EsPQx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Plane_Talking: Turkish fighter jet crashes near Syrian border: A Turkish F-16 fighter jet crashed in south-eastern Turkey on ... http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Christ was a middle-eastern Rasta man who ate grapes in the company of prostitutes and he drank more wine than he drank water.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JamjoomCNN: #Saudi Health Ministry announces 4 new coronavirus cases in Eastern Province, says 3 still being treated, 1 released from h…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LadyRosabell: For Hummus Day today, a recipe with a few unexpected ingredients keep this Middle Eastern staple interesting.... http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Vote4Squash: #Squash is growing in emerging markets such as Malaysia, Egypt, India, the Americas & Eastern Europe. #vote4squash http://…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Jaba_Hoot: TORONTO - Both the Toronto Maple Leafs and Boston Bruins are without key players for Sunday night's Game 6 of their Eastern …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Saudi Health Ministry announces 4 new coronavirus cases in Eastern Province, says 3 still being treated, 1 released from hospital
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have not seen safaricom awarding promotions to people from North Eastern. What critaria do use
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HackneyAbbott: Tories claiming Eastern Europeans overwhelming the health service #demented
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @si_vault: Nathan Horton scores the game-winning goal during Game 7 of the 2011 Eastern Conference Finals: http://t.co/JWJRLQi8Uk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VenturaBusWatch: Eastern Freeway especially slow going this evening. @Vic_Premier your EastWest Link will just put more cars on the fre…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Middle Eastern countries are presently being torn apart by extremists who'd like to see either Iranian or Taliban style regimes in place!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NicoleGennette Not much to push it off the US list at 4 am Eastern. If nothing else is rising it can coast awhile. #RedEye
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DrilonGashi30: Follow @VostokCable from Oxford University students for a unique perspective, in depth and up-to-date analysis on #Russi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Saudi Arabia reporting 4 new coronavirus cases in Eastern Province via @JamjoomCNN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	No Wait at 4:05 AM Eastern Daylight Time #ILM ^1 ^1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Its name was changed 2 Cross River State in d 1976 state creation exercise by d then General Murtala Mohammed regime frm South Eastern State
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@KennethWarner4 @Stormbeard Here it's 1 of these: Helsinki slang, Souther/Eastern/Western/Northern accent. The last 3 sound the same IMO.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Six season HBO show where Wario becomes leader of a volatile eastern-bloc country
</tweet>
<tweet>
	provocative project of history was realized over the Palestinian state of the pearl of eastern Mediterranean in 14 May 1948... "NAKBA"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BiH Minister at Forum on Cultural Cooperation of China and Countries of Central and Eastern Europe --> http://t.co/sT7YEA54up
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TheHalalSlut @umrptl Then you would know that "your people" we're the second next 2 the Greeks that sailed up the eastern coastline
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Leads Traget - Eastern Europe by emilykoenig: Hey,  We promote an online lottery tickets agency that sell lott... http://t.co/O3lluFm9vg
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DerrickSwerve: I hate all you middle eastern Arab niggas for not incorporating good hygiene practices into your life
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Rnagila: Boko Haram now said to control at least 10 of out of 27 local council areas in Borno state, Nort Eastern Nigeria
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Get your weekend a unique twist, with The Big Brunch of Eastern Mangroves Hotel & Spa by @Anantara_Hotels. For reservation, call: 02-6561000
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Unusual behavior detected for vessel EASTERN EXPRESS on route to CHINA CJK
Ref: 4233628-272
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Madame de Pompadour, became a famous chocolate addict and used it as a treatment for her sexual dysfunctions. #ThatsAFoodFact
</tweet>
