<tweet>
	Bout to watch "Erotic Karma" im try'na see wut dat b like
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SexFactsOfLife: In Jamaica there is an erotic dance known as “Daggering” that was banned from TV after causing broken penises.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pfffttt.Seriously?This wasn't too sexy or obscenely erotic at all!Some people need to stop (@YouTube http://t.co/0lyS525sB2)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RealCliveBarker: We're doing an exhibit at Erotic City for West Hollywood Gay Pride Month! We have all the pieces framed and ready!... …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	EROTIC SHOOT (Wtchtr)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Jeremy Laszlo #Fantasy and #Aubrianna Hunter #Erotic mix it up 4 your delight! Give this mix a try and buy your copy today! http://www.amaz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Inviting Gaze Erotic http://t.co/iZrrw4VVBo
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@jginge thanks for the homo erotic photo. Gotta love 90's hair.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @handbagcom: Doncaster buys more erotic fiction than any other city in the country. You saucy Yorkshire folk you. http://t.co/nNt3uDDOI1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Doncaster buys more erotic fiction than any other city in the country. You saucy Yorkshire folk you. http://t.co/IkOp0HHz39" @LornaWebble!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@seattle_erotic When will tickets be available? We only have about a month till the festival.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SexFactsOfLife: In Jamaica there is an erotic dance known as “Daggering” that was banned from TV after causing broken penises.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I want a McGriddle and a Cinnamon melt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @handbagcom: Doncaster buys more erotic fiction than any other city in the country. You saucy Yorkshire folk you. http://t.co/nNt3uDDOI1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's soooooo hot in here
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SexFactsOfLife: In Jamaica there is an erotic dance known as “Daggering” that was banned from TV after causing broken penises.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Doncaster buys more erotic fiction than any other city in the country. You saucy Yorkshire folk you. http://t.co/nNt3uDDOI1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Strangely erotic..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	never thought drinking water could be so erotic http://t.co/HktRjWiVik
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Karolline: Visit my very erotic and lustful world where all of Your fantasies will come true… http://t.co/CNqwNL1LnI
</tweet>
<tweet>
	From the erotic horror story I'm working on. Someone is gonna get fucked to damn death. http://t.co/ZXNnLsQZj4
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RealCliveBarker: We're doing an exhibit at Erotic City for West Hollywood Gay Pride Month! We have all the pieces framed and ready!... …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	5 StarReview ~ loved it! These stories are amazing! Erotic and thrilling, you get pulled into the story.' BRIDES#2   http://t.co/lLusQt2FOh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @supposedlycaleb: just wanna be the star of my own erotic fanfic
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RealCliveBarker: We're doing an exhibit at Erotic City for West Hollywood Gay Pride Month! We have all the pieces framed and ready!... …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	? Nature Touch
? Lea la Bouche
? Babes Network
? Automotive Porn
? Shades of Erotic   
? The Billionaires' Club http://t.co/VQAyCfP5ih
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We're doing an exhibit at Erotic City for West Hollywood Gay Pride Month! We have all the pieces framed and ready!... http://t.co/3aUwuqzQ4j
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Q: Whats the difference between erotic and kinky? A: Erotic is when you use a feather. Kinky is when you use the whole chicken.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Looking for the most erotic massage in Phoenix, AZ?? http://t.co/N3Do0f93PU
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New book arrived today. A collection of erotic stories from @cleispress edited by @mitziszereto http://t.co/oc1hffFMdL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pin-Up Girls: 100 Years Of Erotic Photos From Mark Rotenberg http://t.co/M7KTQpJ3xB via @HuffPostArts
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Erections occur during normal, nightly sleeping. These erections are not related to erotic dreams.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @frilaif: Some people underestimate how erotic it is to be understood. Mary Rakow
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Some people underestimate how erotic it is to be understood. Mary Rakow
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Edmonton 
  
  female models required   Edmonton 
  
Female models necessary for an erotic film, professiona... http://t.co/KpJHlYJNk7
</tweet>
<tweet>
	? Nature Touch
? Lea la Bouche
? Babes Network
? Automotive Porn
? Shades of Erotic   
? The Billionaires' Club http://t.co/UmyGJ0pBt5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Welp, so much for caring ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Follow @boutique_erotic and RT this for a chance to win a #kiterotico #contest #giveaway http://t.co/VRJTwOyjxE
</tweet>
