<tweet>
	'Feeling weightless, semi erotic, you need someone to take you there. Why can't we just look the other… http://t.co/heFe80polJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hey Everyone... Just A quick Question....
 Would You like adult erotic novels???
 any one interested just pm..::):)
 They r REALLY HOTTTT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @m_kopas: if i could get unlimited candy out of having an erotic selfie tumblr that would be enough for me tbh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	if i could get unlimited candy out of having an erotic selfie tumblr that would be enough for me tbh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Inspiration for Breathe You In by Lily Harlem, an erotic romance #erotic #kindle #mustread http://t.co/LaXskvtwsY via @lily_harlem
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iSexstrology: Just below #Taurus cool, businesslike exterior lies a sensuous erotic nature that emerges behind closed doors.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @kswag93: The things I would do to you ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I really didn't need a whole speech about u needing 2 replace UR underwear #humor #erotic http://t.co/IluCpKY41s
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JoeRogersAFC: #possibleWheraboutsOfJamesGrainger death in an erotic sex game involving a noose
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @briasucks: Had to look up synonyms for "erotic" just now (don't ask), and one of them was "bootylicious." I really am done this time.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Had to look up synonyms for "erotic" just now (don't ask), and one of them was "bootylicious." I really am done this time.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hypnotic Seduction & Erotic Hypnosis Using Hypnotic Poetry http://t.co/xPvQGPmQZa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Savy sex maniacs read erotic copy as well as look at pictures. Let us write for you & perk yours up. http://t.co/PMvrxcBgGN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	High Class Independent Escort Lisbon -  I offer an erotic girlfriend experience to discerning gentlemen. I'm... http://t.co/GE4X42bUZd
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ooh give the man a helping hand, it's a sizeable task ahead!
Loves Anna #sexy #wank #erotic http://t.co/7IvZwiEJQZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@__Erotic lol trust I'm in that thing! Haha. I'm about to apply. What exactly do you do (if you don't mind lol)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Still up tho
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@demlips that's right! and that i'm some sorta erotic hottie, too, i think *smirk* x he's so full of it, eh! lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Beautys Punishment: second of the Classic Erotic Trilogy of Sleeping Beauty Reviews http://t.co/IIH5tkc8XR
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@__Erotic ayyyy! Let me get an app! For real tho! Lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@annieplayer is this replacing erotic meet? Is it suitable for me to contribute do you think?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ruggighund den, i would die 4 u och erotic city typ.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@88Keys_No_Locks lmao! Yeah I need another job. How much do yall get paid an hour if you don't mind me asking? And yeah we always are too!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Epiphora EROTIC SHEETS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SuzyAyers: FINALLY I HAVE A WEBSITE: Check out my first post a #FREE #erotic short RUNNING LATE http://t.co/6pccitPtqr … via @weebly
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MIKEcheck_101 lol okay good!!! Well we will def figure it out!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@zeldawilliams @maebirdwing @nickjfrost sounds painful and erotic. Sounds painfully erotic.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm reading schoolgirl nihongi erotic grotesque nonsense and lolita #ellylifestyle
</tweet>
<tweet>
	http://t.co/BRrrJXxSoZ
A gallery of mostly black, white and erotic photography... good morning!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@88Keys_No_Locks are they hiring? Lol and yeah.. It's right by union hospital... I work with mentally I'll people ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Backstage Pass http://t.co/W2Cie2JRPz - over 300 copies sold! Thanks to all who chose this sweet lightly erotic romance :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	$$ Immediate Need for Fetish & Erotic Models for Print Work PAID $$  http://t.co/8cXVDspItO
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@__Erotic i know! my phones off so i have no way to contact you besides via twitter. However, i think my messaging still work!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#possibleWheraboutsOfJamesGrainger death in an erotic sex game involving a noose
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#perksofdatingme i've beaten the elite four a fair few times
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@wtfraech erotic asphyxiation
</tweet>
<tweet>
	5pm-1am: armani brooklyn claudia elle harley lara loretta monique natasha ryder shakira tamara #erotic #massage
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@__Erotic yes ma'am. Bunch of different houses where we work with people with disabilities. Are You in TH?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MIKEcheck_101 ehhhh I gotta find out! We gotta hang!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Balls, didnt charge phone overnight
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@__Erotic today. then i work the next 4 days
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MIKEcheck_101 Jesus knows lol. I have to look at my schedule! Wbu?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@__Erotic idk if you've ever heard of it but it's called ResCare lol. How about you?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@__Erotic im about to make mines now lol. when the next time you off?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MaraMaccabee "Erotic Innocence: The Culture of Child Molesting" by James R. Kincaid. I think that'd  delve into what you're talking about.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MIKEcheck_101 lmao! I need to make a bed and go to sleep!!
</tweet>
