<tweet>
	@kyle_engel @sommerfaye being country is either in your heart or in your family.. A love for hard work, the land, animals and the outdoors ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Parents start as the leaders of the tribe but when us siblings grow up we become the pack & pick off our parents as weakest members! #family
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@IAmEBOI Thanks heaps for the retweet dude! means alot not only to me but to Carlos & his family!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@_lis_sy_ that's what they did, reduced amount and added to means tested family tax benefit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Loyalty makes u family
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Deemmm_: Family over friends, because real friends are family.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I could deal with living in a friendship family
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SoAnnehz: Someone told me growing up is hard.
I told him. Dude, try growing up in an indian family.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Reconnected with some family members! I'm blessed!! I never hold grudges!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SmallTwnProbs: Friends become family and family are friends. #smalltownpride
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @B5sNadiaBuari: EachDay,I am thankful for Nyts tht turned into Mrngs,Friends tht turned into Family,Dreams tht turned into Reality&Likes…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Robert Randolph & The Family Band Set New Album Release - http://t.co/JFrfO4Q1GW
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Ptriezty: I've to be strong just for the sake of my family. This illness will recover, Soon. Dengan izin Allah.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Happy Holidays from the Caber Family!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Truth!!! RT "@MiserableMadge: At the end of the day only three people have your back: Friends, Family and Jack Daniel's."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Silver0_123: "Your Lord has rights over you, your soul has rights over you & your family has rights over you so give each of them their…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AaronMyles3: Fitness testing today :( the bright side I'm home next week buzzing :D #family
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@hannahstrawbery Hannah all my best wishes to him and your family <3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheseDamnQuote: Dear family, just because I'm laughing when I'm reading a text, does not mean I'm flirting with someone.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ChouhanShivraj: My heartfelt condolence to the grieving family of Shri Harvansh singh ,senior congress leader and Dy Speaker of MP Vidh…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	and i love my family
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@thekatvond I woke up with family affair by family stone I think. It's on repeat!  #innerdj. ???argh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My cousin @rwotoruk looks like Kayne West......or Kevin Hart. You decide, I got famous people as family members lol.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just three set of people in ma life, friends,family and fuck mate
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @lifeisatrailer: I fake sleep when my family members come in my room so they don’t talk to me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @msleamichele: Such an amazing day today! So nice to see my Glee family and everyone in the Fox family as well!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	One in three children say swimming is their favourite family activity #swimbritain http://t.co/PqojeEE6O0
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Has your family got the Zoflora habit? RT @ajw_photo: my mum and my gran used it. sweetpea is the family favourite :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LittleMixOffic: Thanks so much to the fabulously talented @MusicHallTavern for a fun night with all the family!#mustseeshow xxjadexx ht…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SanityOrBust It's sad but maybe it is for the best. If they cannot see you and your family's worth then they don't need to be in your life
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Massive respect as far as I'm concerned! @KirstyBisset It's hardcore but a small price price to pay for a lifetime with family and kids
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@kj_nash so so hard. Hanging on to this little family because we seem to have been cast adrift from all the rest.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And her family
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#perksofdatingme my family is awesomeee
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WTFLifeFacts: When South Park aired its “Anti-Family Guy” episode, the producers received flowers from the crew of The Simpsons.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@Ngugievuti: Polygamy (N)" Marrying more than one wife is one of the most pragmatic solutions to keep both the family & society going good!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Summer Open Day, Sat 22 June 1- 5pm. Loads of FREE activities for all the family. Please retweet http://t.co/BzKSGQcONw
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LovestruckBook: “I'm not lonely, I have amazing God, lovely family and wonderful friends.”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Here I was surrounded by my family and my so-called mates and I've never felt so alone.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#DareToDreams Have 1 million USD and give 50% to charity, 50% to my family.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@TmagicT: Looks like there may be another magician in the family http://t.co/NlVNZw1dgQ” yay! #femalemagicians ?????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have a great support group family & friends, what they do for me or advise me on..I try to do the same for my friends & fam
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Blood makes you related, loyalty makes you family..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WELL I KNOW THAT IT DOESN'T MEAN "YOU CAN DO IT AT HOME AND HAVE GOOGLE OR FAMILY TO HELP YOU?????"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Everytime I check http://t.co/EYB1IDntTI I get a bit more frustrated.Come on family & friends.Even £1 is appreciated for such a worthy cause
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@StilldasameGrip Thanks heaps for the retweet dude! means alot not only to me but to Carlos & his family!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ArianaGrande: Family is the most important thing in life  :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Family is the most important thing in life  :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We're getting ready for another family coffee morning today. Just drop in to Teen Talk, 10am-12pm to join in and we'll get the kettle on.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @gym4all: Come on ladies try out our classes and free trial at Gym4all Basildon make sure you bring friends and family members!!!
</tweet>
