<tweet>
	@rachelburden @bbc5live Coincidence or what? I'm off to a Genetic Medicine clinic this morning about Braca testing because of family history
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Eegee's and Family Guy is my comfort right now.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@RelatableKowts: Dear GOD thank you for today, yesterday and tomorrow. My family, my joys, my sorrows, for all that made me stronger."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"The bullies have been so busy, they're outsourcing their bullying to India." Hahahaha, where the hell do Family Guy get these ideas from!?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@cassiecasss oh man!! I got family out there! I hardly see em! Hahaha!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @unfflouis: " one time i got in the shower and came out and no one was home and the lights were off, my entire family went bowling and f…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BrendaNixon tells how to put #family first and still run a successful #career http://t.co/K29PfY5ixH #Homeoffice #FamilyBiz #mombiz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @skate14: @LUISSG_G yeah not until they become your family
</tweet>
<tweet>
	why does Family Guy trend almost every night around this time?!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	EVERYBODY IS ON IS OWN .. THERE IS NOTHING LIKE EXTENDED FAMILY ..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If you're a real homie, you're considered to be part of my family.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @NotCommonFacts: When South Park aired its “Anti-Family Guy” episode, the producers received flowers from the crew of The Simpsons.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @scolari157: Good Day out yesterday for the #mufc family. Got Evra on the mic to say "KA KA KA KAGAWA" as printed on my shirt with smile…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	anybody tries to fuck with my family I will cut off their balls with a butter knife
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I know I can still make my family proud
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Free Tempo Buddha's Family  Free Tempo Buddha's Family http://t.co/fUvUeuuhJc on #SoundCloud
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'll fight for my family any day.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This school are seriously going to think my family belongs to the Mafia. Paying for things with £100/50 notes...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Father of slain corrections officer talks of family's loss http://t.co/Qs8vom8ucH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Str8_no_Chazer: #Indeed RT @LakeShOwQueen: Family Guy is better than most shows on tv that star humans
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @B5sNadiaBuari: EachDay,I am thankful for Nyts tht turned into Mrngs,Friends tht turned into Family,Dreams tht turned into Reality&Likes…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheseDamnQuote: Dear family, just because I'm laughing when I'm reading a text, does not mean I'm flirting with someone.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thinking about crying because hockey is like my family (':
</tweet>
<tweet>
	whose long blond hair is on my leg......my whole family is shorthaired brunettes SOS we have an intruderr
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Family Guy
Peter: Lois, look what I spelled with my alphabet soup
Lois: lol oh mayb ltr u want the real thng?
Peter: lol I prefer the soup
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@THAREAL_ARTHUR one of the homies?! These hoes be opening up to the team and they family. Lmfao #DEAD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KristinePetsAdv: Family Fights to Save The Beagle That Bit Their Child http://t.co/S3VCd9U0gc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	•R.I.P Black Mask of Wu Watchmen•
Sending out LightLovePeace&Blessing to his family, friends and immortal Soul.... http://t.co/4RohWWN3EL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	my family must hate me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Family Guy is funny AF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Great food, candid talks and my family... Really makes my day @YatraHolidays #BeingTogether
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Some people just missed this lesson...your family is the greatest you have on earth
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thanks to Sophie burrow who has bought 4 tickets for some of her family to go to the boxing on 17 August @lifeforakid @Kippaxjuniorsrl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @kev_INyourpants: family over everything, your friends, your loves, everyone will leave you, except your family
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @abcnews: RT @ABCNews24: Baby bonus will be abolished in tonight’s federal budget, parents to receive increase in Family Tax Benefit A t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Rickykhan Course hunni! Wouldn't miss it for the world, it will be a lovely family day.xx Can't believe he is 1 already! #ProudAunty #Zak
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@VOAHilleary I have family in Syria and the consensus is that the MB along with foreign interests are trying the destabilize the country.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Laying down smoking this blunt while watching family guy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @abcnews: RT @ABCNews24: Baby bonus will be abolished in tonight’s federal budget, parents to receive increase in Family Tax Benefit A t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sharon_yamin Happy be-lated Mothers Day, Hope you and the family are well.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_kylielewis: WHY do i have to be the youngest in my family oh my god no
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I hate my father-mom-bro or sis. They're not my family. My family is here. I Love Y'All.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My condolences to the cast of #Y&R and the family of #JeanneCooper What an amazing woman!! She will be missed.
Sending Canuk love
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Michael Jackson’s family want legal ban on kids’ paternity test http://t.co/WZf4d7sQRa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @trev4prez: All I count on is my family flock and my bad bitch who else do I need tho?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What is the strangest dream you've ever had? — I dreamt that my family got run over by a giant rock http://t.co/Bt6eRmk8j2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@moephistopheles a little but I'm lost on the road with my family I still wanna vent tho unu
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Nothing pisses me off more than when I'm trying to watch Hawaii five o and my family will not stop talking. #PleaseShutUp
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm really excited to see my Valley family this weekend! @Lucy_m209 I can't waiiiitttt! ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @abcnews: RT @ABCNews24: Baby bonus will be abolished in tonight’s federal budget, parents to receive increase in Family Tax Benefit A t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Discounts, Special offers and Cashback on Shopping for NHS STAFF + Friends & Family http://t.co/RBoZskLuDO
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Give “PEEPLES” a chance. A family-friendly movie packed with stars http://t.co/RskpzkWz0T
</tweet>
<tweet>
	bitch please, you can judges me but not my mum, my family, my BFF, my Bf, and My GOD !
</tweet>
