<tweet>
	RT @Righteous_RAAM: Almost once in a week we hear Akshay Kumar signing a new film. This man works nonstop. Blessed to be a fan of such guy …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	not a ryan gosling fan really but the place beyond the pines was an amazing film. go and see it!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	sir i am ajith fan please avara vachu 1 film panunga he is my god
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Perhaps you're more of a film fan? You could own or train Harry Trotter, Ham Solo, Donnie Porko or Fat Boy (as in Run Fat Boy Run!)...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@natebuzz Bonjour Nate ! Have a good day ! I love you so much !  From a french fan <3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@simonsherry It's some rolled gold fan film genius. Watch the full series for MAXIMUM chuckles. Do it!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @hamtarospear: After a long, long wait (too long, if you ask any fan) Star Trek Into Darkness is finally here. And, as it usually goes w…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DreadCentral: Emanuel and the Truth About Fishes Lands Distro with Tribeca Film and Well Go USA http://t.co/BDfftmiL3M #horror
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @indiewire: Sundance premiere EMANUEL AND THE TRUTH ABOUT FISHES has found US distribution: http://t.co/hXB2kmkITJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Hetookapull20 huge fan of the film 127 hours...........Only spent 5 pathetic drunk hours outside but gonna watch this morning. Recommend if
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Colinwebsite plss Colin should not be the of Merlin. Watching this film, takes me beautiful dreams. Turkey fan. ?efika  K?cal?.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Has Star Wars fan JJ Abrams missed the point of Star Trek? Thoughtful film blog by David Cox. http://t.co/bAbKLsKL9O
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Colinwebsite plss Colin should not be the end of Merlin. Watching this film, takes me beautiful dreams.Turkey fan. My name's ?efika K?cal?.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If you are a fan of Tamil film songs then please youtube the track Madhivadhani by the super talent Vijay Prakash from #kanpesumvarthaigal!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JoetheJuicer I'm a big fan of your wk, love the film. I'm a journo at the ABC in sydney Can u follow me pls so can DM you. cheers, Whitney
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MrDDyer just want to say I'm a big fan. I just wish they'd give you a fucking decent film to be in! Sack off your agent.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Right now the @MMPRfilm has reached $22,056! All I can say is that you fans ROCK!!! http://t.co/Da3WbDnxAE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#lordsofsalem Cult Horror Film! Congratulations! Zombie's Fan, I Love his movie...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Woodsy245: @Boogie2988 I'm an aspiring film maker/ long term fan! I was hoping you'd RT this so people can see my film? Thanks! http://…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@iamaneek Yar bt as a fan i am waiting for d trailer. Like so badly. It should come with YJHD man. Perfect platform n a prfect film fr reach
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @dredduniverse: Here it is dredd fans, the trailer for the fan made film cursed edge by @Directoroli Tell us your thoughts http://t.co/f…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Righteous_RAAM: Almost once in a week we hear Akshay Kumar signing a new film. This man works nonstop. Blessed to be a fan of such guy …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sugarscape:LittleMix's Wings gets covered on Glee.Lord Tubbington is naturally a massive fan. http://t.co/7Hi2Xz2pKq @LittleMixOffic look(:
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I added a video to a @YouTube playlist http://t.co/u7QOmxZIMX Thor Promo Video (The Mighty Thor Fan Film Trailer)-Coming Soon...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Righteous_RAAM: Almost once in a week we hear Akshay Kumar signing a new film. This man works nonstop. Blessed to be a fan of such guy …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Here it is dredd fans, the trailer for the fan made film cursed edge by @Directoroli Tell us your thoughts http://t.co/fp5Vri75yL Enjoy!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Cubbycake @sarahm132 @iRuthie It's a good film. Some of his best acting. It actually made me like him. I wasn't a fan before that movie lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RangerCrew As a rangers fan, this is very exciting. Hopefully Saban will be able to film more episodes than their 20 limit for this season.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TomFelton You said one time to a fan that you miss HP so much. So I was curious what do you miss: The film or the actor/friends?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Totally awesome: #StarWars, completely remade, by hundreds of fan videos: http://t.co/7sXNnEF9Gw
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Real_Liam_Payne hi Liam!
I'm a big fan of yours and thank you for the film "This Is Us" in Poland!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm going to lose points as a film fan, but I couldn't finish Birth of a Nation on the basis of it being too "quaint."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WHAT OTHER BAND WOULD GET A RECORDER AND FILM THEMSELVES SINGING WHILE PERFORMING DURING THEIR CONCERT FOR A FAN? ASDFGHJKL;.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Rangerboard: Remember, they may have reached their goal, but you can still contribute to @MMPRfilm's Kickstarter funds! http://t.co/4To…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Righteous_RAAM: Almost once in a week we hear Akshay Kumar signing a new film. This man works nonstop. Blessed to be a fan of such guy …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Righteous_RAAM: Almost once in a week we hear Akshay Kumar signing a new film. This man works nonstop. Blessed to be a fan of such guy …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Righteous_RAAM: Almost once in a week we hear Akshay Kumar signing a new film. This man works nonstop. Blessed to be a fan of such guy …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Almost once in a week we hear Akshay Kumar signing a new film. This man works nonstop. Blessed to be a fan of such guy :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching cabin the woods. A must see film if you are a fan of horror!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@optibotimus pardon poor choose of word. My point is for a new fan the film is fantastic and that's how I see it #agreetodisagree
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Perhaps I live in a film fan bubble in LA. I've only talked to one person (that rascal @BrianLynch) who's admitted to anim. star-tracking.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Do yourself a favour and catch the awesome SPN fan film "The Other Side" http://t.co/G2hYEl1aYF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Not that I was a huge fan of the movie. As a specimen of film making, it would be a good fit in this day and age.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	TIL this Power Ranger fan-film Kickstarter surpassed its $19K goal in the first week. It doesn't sound half bad! http://t.co/WW6BdVHsd2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bethlovesbolly thought it works as a genre film evn though I am not a fan of zombie films.2nd half cld hv been smarter w/ better set pieces
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Rangerboard: Remember, they may have reached their goal, but you can still contribute to @MMPRfilm's Kickstarter funds! http://t.co/4To…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Remember, they may have reached their goal, but you can still contribute to @MMPRfilm's Kickstarter funds! http://t.co/4ToswWvhgV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Interview Magazine - Winona Ryder http://t.co/eUUnpQUPMq
I luv her and wish her the best. As a huge Oldman fan I luv what she said about him
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Live Action "BioShock" Fan-Film is Surprisingly Well Done (Video) http://t.co/fsmDOLCA8i
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm not the biggest Metallica fan, but their film, "Metallica Through the Never" sounds quite interesting...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CassieSchwarz @amellywood yes because wherever you film/work you must automatically become a bandwagon fan for that city. #getoverit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JamesFrancoTV I'm a fan and glad you were in a Gus Van Sant film!  :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_AmandaWyss: Thanks to Luca, a fan from Italy for letting me know Nightmare on Elm Street made this list of 10 Best Horror... http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	like i've never been a die hard leo fan but i just... like... he is so fUCKING attractive in this film i cannot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#BioShock fans ought to appreciate this amazing looking fan film called The Brothers Rapture! http://t.co/ZKWzFgPDwQ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@C__Robertson @heartbr3akah my man, hope you doin your film study.  I need you to stuff runs as well as you pass cover.  Big fan Craig
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sugarscape: Little Mix's Wings gets covered on Glee. Lord Tubbington is naturally a massive fan. http://t.co/Uo01hXorZU
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A new breed of fan film from my uber-talented pal @ShawnBaichoo (and other uber-talented folk, too many to mention)  https://t.co/JghJHYuq2d
</tweet>
<tweet>
	PUNISHER: NO MERCY Fan-Film Trailer is now up.
Check out their Facebook page:... http://t.co/5ZJdnr3H0M
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@HaroldItz I suspected you did, since you're a classic film fan too. Louis Armstrong for the win!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If I'm ever at Wrigley this year, I hope they never film me during the fan-cam. Probably be pickin' my nose or something. #costanza-ing
</tweet>
