<tweet>
	RT @BarrakTony: If I was just a fragment of your imagination, a fantasy in your dream, would I prefer you'd wake up, over choosing to stay?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@HelenRazer Funny, Helen, but I think Swanny's fantasy #budget tonight might top you for amusement value. @crikey_news @MichaelTunn #auspol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Woohoo! A PB in fantasy league on the weekend - Ranked 2,071 for the round! Ok, there still lots that are better but it was good for me!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	reality is too difficult to handle, thats why we need a little bit of fantasy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That was a battle of extraordinary magnitude! (Yang ~ Final Fantasy IV)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pellegrini's a bit of a Ricardo Montalblan, he should team up with Zola and form a Fantasy Island tribute act.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Final Fantasy V ##Cory #Bot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	IS THIS THE REAL LIFE, OR IS THIS FANTASY?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#IDnetR session 7, paradox of choice, boundary crossing, fantasy of 'orgasmic' privileged and perfect birth
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Indie_BookStore: Robert Bevan writes fantasy novels. Please take a look at his work.  http://t.co/GB2AXQ7u5t  @robertbevan77
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fox readies its next volley into fantastic modern urban fantasy: Sleepy Hollow: http://t.co/q16l54ZK1L #fantasy #apocalypse #stunning
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VogueDurban: Prepare to be dazzled in a fantasy world of golden glitz & glamour like never before this Friday night (17 May)... http://…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Jeremy Laszlo #Fantasy and #Aubrianna Hunter #Erotic mix it up 4 your delight! Give this mix a try and buy your copy today! http://www.amaz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Read the first chapter of THE PUPPET SPELL here! http://t.co/Qj81XUVrcE #fantasy #yalit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"I always live half way between reality and fantasy" -A
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fantasy Photo Manipulations By Zavgo-Spb - Click Small Images For Larger Image Or Links Below Gallery Tales... http://t.co/s8mpiNh3W3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Final Fantasy XIII-2 Re-Releasing With Ultimate Hits, DLC Collection Versions http://t.co/RKXcMKsf4u
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fast paced, action packed fantasy 
House Of Secrets 
Chris Columbus&  @Ned_vizzini 
http://t.co/zAMQnfkaM9
@HarperCollinsCh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Time Team is on, and I am so happy.  In my head, my fantasy of being Indiana Jones has resumed. http://t.co/5naGo05v8t
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@WarnieDT @Fantasy_FC What is a better trade?
D.Pearce>Ibbotson and Heath>Thurlow 
or
D.Pearce>Thurlow and Kommer>Hutchings
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Final Fantasy 14 gets a torrent of enemy, Primals and location details & images http://t.co/CCK8nQSJQX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Prepare to be dazzled in a fantasy world of golden glitz & glamour like never before this Friday night (17 May)... http://t.co/6vGdipsmN1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@satsu_nyan yes he’s coming for the Final Fantasy concert
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm about to go in on Final Fantasy VII.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Fantasy_FC Yep - DT.. will be looking at SC soon for my Gold article. Priddis is very interesting.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @StudentRushNYC: Fantasy is hardly an escape from reality. It's a way of understanding it. - Lloyd Alexander
</tweet>
<tweet>
	take me up up up and away till the music fills my fantasy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ACarp22: Talking fantasy football in the #afterhours
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Playing final fantasy - under the apple tree with GEETAH!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tell me your fantasy. I'm curious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@WarnieDT Is that in DT? Priddis is an interesting one.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Final Fantasy 7 is the only game I have played on my PS3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @xMELIKEF00D: life doesn't always turn out to be your fantasy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MekanicGaming No problem, I'm glad you found it useful. Also, "shadow corruption" sounds like a really generic fantasy trope
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“Fantasy is hardly an escape from reality. It's a way of understanding it.” ? Lloyd Alexander
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Talking fantasy football in the #afterhours
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @pulpfictionbks: I recently read Brian McClellan's flintlock-fantasy debut, PROMISE OF BLOOD. It is excellent. So good, in fact, that we…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You were my fantasy boy and this, it was my dream come true... But it's nothing like I expected #imdone #moveingon
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Vill ha en beautiful dark twisted fantasy??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @high_on_glitter: Some people say that fairies are the stuff of fantasy, they think the world is just what you can touch and hear and se…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@VictoriasSecret do you have any idea who will get te fantasy bra??! I'm thinking either @angelcandice or @Doutzen they've been brilliant
</tweet>
