<tweet>
	RT @helesialuke: You know that fantasy? Winning lottery? That is feeling @christyclarkbc ads want you to have. Reality: growing income ineq…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Indie_BookStore: Robert Bevan writes fantasy novels. Please take a look at his work.  http://t.co/GB2AXQ7u5t  @robertbevan77
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JAIMEBOOMBOX I THOUGHT IT WAS A FANTASY OF YOURS TO GET YOUR TITTY BIT IN A CONTINUATION SCHOOL HALLWAY DX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Anak perempuan kebakaran ~('.'~) (~'.')~ RT"@rahayu_putri2: She's just a girl, and she's on fire Hotter than a fantasy, like a highway l
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I’m sorry that you didn’t notice me because you were chasing the unattainable fantasy on your ‘Must Have/Must Be’ list. ~Your Soulmate
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Gotta train Ona at work 2mm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The only place where I broke into A.I.R. 100 is the IPL Fantasy League. 

My parents must be so proud!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Giveaway Time frostcosmetics will be giving one of my Fantasy Dolls a Whole Collection Kit (1lipgloss,… http://t.co/43HcSyTWId
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @rojdafenty_: Hi I'd just like to say that this perfume by Britney Spears called fantasy is my fav ? oh and my birthdays in a month http…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	No worries no worries
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I am halfway through Endless Fantasy who wants to go back and forth between getting baked and fcking until we can no longer function
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fugitive Fantasy Fear. #namethattvshow
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bellabendz @kaceyparkerxxx If my threesome fantasy with you two becomes a reality, you'd be saying it even before we get started :P
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Check P out she doing her damn thang lol, ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Life1andQuotes: Reality killed my soul thats full of fantasy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Remember to tune in to Live at Five at 4 in less than 30 minutes. Broadcast LIVE from Fantasy of Trees!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Nick keeps trying to trade me iwakuma for my best players in fantasy at 3 in the morning i dont give a flying fuck and Im in last place stfu
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Carelessness, the novel suggests, is one of the costs of fantasy. Often, to dream up a new life, you have to destroy the old one." #hhmhmm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Original Surreal Art, Dark Landscape Painting, Whimsical Fantasy Art, Tree Wall Art, Purple Sk… #EtsyFu #DarkLandscape
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @torbooks: Over on @bookchickcity, a review of Esperanza, a book that “pushes the limits between fantasy and reality” http://t.co/uVKRwN…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You don't have to live in reality, just acknowledge it from time to time to remind yourself of what your fantasy is. @_Tom_Park9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Life1andQuotes: Reality killed my soul thats full of fantasy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	http://t.co/31tuin8uUt i want to buy this shirt but im a bit skeptical about buying printed shirts from off-brand sources nowadays
</tweet>
<tweet>
	FOT
Need to walk a little after that big Thanksgiving meal? Stroll down to Fantasy of Trees- show is open until 9:00 tonight! FOT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Where is these so called vamps at?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@poetrileharia Fantasy Land
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Reality killed my soul thats full of fantasy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hi I'd just like to say that this perfume by Britney Spears called fantasy is my fav ? oh and my birthdays in a month http://t.co/Pgz8WydJBN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	final fantasy xiii , i think so
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@Fantasy_FC: Chaz Dixon set to miss one more week for GCS” Played 40 minutes of football for my fantasy team. Not one of my best trades.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	She's just a girl, and she's on fire Hotter than a fantasy, like a highway longer @windawijayaa2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	fantasy
steampunk
In Darkfell, a half elven seer raised by ogres holds the fate of the world in his hands. fantasy steampunk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ireland_rhain or is this just fantasy?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Don't let your fantasy world eat up your reality world.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BlindVeil New Fantasy - In Post-Apocolyptic earth,humanity stands only one chance.   Tolomay is the first to... http://t.co/a72mxNPO9w
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@DOPEPICS: People have dreams, but it stays a fantasy forever because they don’t lock in and take the first step.”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The pleasure of a dream is that it is a fantasy, if it happens it was never a dream
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My fantasy baseball team licks?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"It’s through fantasy that we edit out the parts of our lives that make us uncomfortable" hmmMMMmmMm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Honestly I mostly watch cartoons, anime, superheroes, and anything to do with science fiction/fantasy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I love the LawAntilaw and Judge system in Final Fantasy Tactics Advance, and was upset it changed in #FFTA2. #FFTA #UnpopularGamingOpinions
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The sun is at last setting on Britain's imperial myth | Pankaj Mishra http://t.co/OsG62m8qkk via @guardian
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@prestontowers @Brocklesnitch nerds like fantasy and daft punk. Simples. I am a geek, therefore like fantasy....and extreme metal
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dark fantasy !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just 24 hours to the end of the campaign. Lets all the creatures be posible.... http://t.co/1kOCRi7EHH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bonniegrrl @bad_robot So excited for this! Urban just needs to keep making Sci-Fi fantasy flicks forever.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I can make your fantasy a reality
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'his universe is an ideological paranoid fantasy realm hatched in his own mind and the minds of others just like him' http://t.co/CXM3PJyCGK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I may not be a final boss but mother fuck I am a final FANTASY boss. OHHHHHHH~
</tweet>
