<tweet>
	FB profile pics would have been amazing in the 20s - 30s with all that Film Noir lighting everywhere.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Posted FILM NOIR album on Creative Photo Academy page
ENJOY!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Terrific film noir episode. Here's looking at you, #warehouse13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @redchapCREATIVE: I just submitted my short film-noir, sci-fi, drama-thriller script "Thirty-Two Seconds" to SHORT FILM SCRIPT CONTEST h…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nitsirk64: This is a fun episode. Very Maltese Falcon.  It's like Eddie & Joanne were made for film noir. #warehouse13 @EddieMcClintock
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This is a fun episode. Very Maltese Falcon.  It's like Eddie & Joanne were made for film noir. #warehouse13 @EddieMcClintock
</tweet>
<tweet>
	what if who framed roger rabbit is my fav film noir
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Loving film noir #warehouse13 & Missi Pyle? It's like Christmas! Joanne Kelly is so gorgeous I'd love to see her do a pinup set after this!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Scott_Pigman Double Indemnity, I love Film Noir. You?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Film Noir used to frighten me as a child. So did Bob Barker.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@PrincetonHolt Its definitely full of life. I guess I'm so sucked into film noir it's tough to appreciate good ol' Fellini (in color).
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DickJonesBurlyQ that's a good topic, my adviser would have loved you, he wrote his doctorate on Film Noir, I compared Superman returns...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SyfyPR can't get much more "greater" than this ep of #Warehouse13 #Warehouse13 Film noir for the win! amazing writers, actors, everyone!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why have they only just made this episode?!? Film noir = best idea ever #warehouse13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I need more film noir Myka in my life!! Trow H.G. in there and I'd be set! #warehouse13 #nerdsbians
</tweet>
<tweet>
	super loving this film noir ep of #Warehouse13 #Warehouse13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@syfy #Warehouse13 Film Noir? I really like the hat
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I am enjoying this film noir style episode.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @scifistorm: Why does every film noir have to have the oversized guy in the white suit? #Warehouse13 @Syfy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @1girlvaudeville: @laurenspieller There are different classes of Goth. @Leannarenee is Old School goth. I think I'm more Film Noir Goth.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I think this is prepping me for my film noir class next semester (Unless I dropped that)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tonight's #WAREHOUSE13 episode brings to life classic film noir after the fashion of the Maltese Falcon. @EddieMcClintock great job!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why does every film noir have to have the oversized guy in the white suit? #Warehouse13 @Syfy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	how fun was it to shoot a film noir? @Syfy #warehouse13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Loving this new title sequence for the black and white show. Film noir really suit #Warehouse13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	after another not so happy #downtonabbey, just tuned into #warehouse13 and am liking the black and white/film noir theme
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First I took a walk, second I got some whiskey up in mah blood, fourth I'm writing a paper on teen film noir. What's the third thing?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Film noir was a great genre, but can anyone say it wouldn't have been better if the women had force lightning? #WH13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This feels like the intro to a film-noir. Someone think of a gritty soliloquy. @ Woodside, NY http://t.co/3Awrbnfkuq
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New short film proyect @TheBlindNight 40s Classic noir film
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Warehouse 13 goes Film Noir in what Eddie McClintock say is his funnest episode yet! http://t.co/JNPpoDyKXK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Warehouse 13 meets Galaxy Quest for black and white film noir ep tonight. http://t.co/kSua72NtF3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Can't wait for some epic film noir tonight :) #warehouse13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My life is classic film noir, black and white, moody and melancholy, standing on a bridge in the rain smoking a roll up
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@_ChloePower_ Fritz Lang's masterpiece 'M' (his first sound film) starring Peter Lorre is often cited as the basis for the film noir genre.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@tobyhyde @tpgMets Someone will make a film noir about the 2012 Mets someday and call it "Two Franks Too Many".
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Iron man yesterday and film noir marathon today #moviebuff
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RedPandaGamer Sounds like the title of a sweet film noir.
</tweet>
