<tweet>
	In the drip drip, lick lick, like a lolly, or left from Jamaica going Foreign Couture.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Che_ranna: Foreign hair give y'all basic bitches pride.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#NewSingle EVERYONE SUPPORT ME IM TRYING TO DEVELOP A FAN BASE  Zayy  "FOREIGN" FT. JAY RICH by RealLilZay  http://t.co/VrNLPkwqDx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Manouchehr Mottaki, #Iran's Foreign Minister at the time, flew into #Abuja, had a few words wt #Nigeria's FM & the Al-Quds chap was let off.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	?? wtf is so funny foreign fuck ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@brimouzon_bri: I heard white boys do they bitches right” bahaha bitch you are too funny. You goin into foreign territory there lmao
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@VOAHilleary I have family in Syria and the consensus is that the MB along with foreign interests are trying the destabilize the country.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DigiDiplomats: #DipNote lists engaging on social media as a way individuals can be involved in foreign affairs - http://t.co/CsgGUI5MJz…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Tadlette: Bishop whinging about Labor not able 2 retain foreign aid promise is breathtaking hypocrisy. Howard FAILED UN http://t.co/PfG…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @UpikTips: Worried about multiculturalism in TV soaps? Simply watch Coronation Street in reverse and eventually all the foreign characte…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@annamanson21 is off to class and I haven't even gone to sleep haha I love having foreign friends ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Foreign hair give y'all basic bitches pride.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If real recognize real, y'all foreign
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lets be real .. If you ever ate not only my ass , but ANYONE'S ass for that matter .. I will not take you serious . U won't win any argument
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @rihanna: 2 day shoot for my upcoming Autumn/Winter collections with River Island was flawless! My models looked so damn good! Foreign c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Azyvotersmo: http://t.co/e4rOaPCJke
Australia has become known as an haute intention for the foreign country students....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have to get a girlfriend if nights gonna be like this
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I used to go to Korea Kent Foreign School before go to Hanlim High School majoring Entertainment and Arts.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm stomach making all types of foreign noises .
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @danhilbert_: Can't wait to never have to read/write about US Foreign Policy ever again after this morning
</tweet>
<tweet>
	if you are in a foreign, dope & new country & all you're going is instagramming.. come home, you're not drunk enough
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nrfd_: Changing to LoL NA servers, Foreign Europeans are literally the worst human beings alive.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @wamathai: Why do we preach local content but consume foreign content? http://t.co/8pZjEwz7qv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Azyvotersmo: http://t.co/e4rOaPCJke
Australia has become known as an haute intention for the foreign country students....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @najamsethi: All local and foreign observers have declared Punjab elections as the most neutral, fair and non-violent in Pakistani histo…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @najamsethi: All local and foreign observers have declared Punjab elections as the most neutral, fair and non-violent in Pakistani histo…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sepamu right. i haven't touched it in years -- that said, for many, old habits die hard & google docs + cloud feels foreign.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@__KatieDoes: Can I get a bed fulla nekkit foreign bitches with tennis ball titties and volleyball asses?”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Samsung Group said it would invest.. in the foundation ... While noting that the foundation would accept foreign researchers.."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Foreign_Bavina "Chill"?? What does that word mean?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Turkey bombed itself, Syrian foreign minister charges - Washington Times: http://t.co/tESqra1cBu via @washtimes
</tweet>
<tweet>
	So Man City have given Mancini the boot, so the idea of a manager staying at a team for two or more yrs is now a foreign concept
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @rihanna: 2 day shoot for my upcoming Autumn/Winter collections with River Island was flawless! My models looked so damn good! Foreign c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	u over there using emojis that shit is foreign to Android, u might as well type in Spanish
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Changing to LoL NA servers, Foreign Europeans are literally the worst human beings alive.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Can't wait to never have to read/write about US Foreign Policy ever again after this morning
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ALNAFS_ALZAKIA: @MubasherLucman foreign powers like India,Israel and US never wanted IK to form a govt .they helped NS financially so h…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Can I get a bed fulla nekkit foreign bitches with tennis ball titties and volleyball asses?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Jon_Boone: "Foreign journalists have profiled Imran Khan more than they have profiled any living thing in this part of the world http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @rihanna: 2 day shoot for my upcoming Autumn/Winter collections with River Island was flawless! My models looked so damn good! Foreign c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Azyvotersmo: http://t.co/e4rOaPCJke
Australia has become known as an haute intention for the foreign country students....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I love my foreign friends!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BBC News - What does it take to be a great foreign secretary? http://t.co/Dbm9O5EB0T
</tweet>
<tweet>
	4. Teach Avon a new trick. 5.Plant something. 6.Throw/donate stuff I don't need. 7. Learn words in a foreign language and sign language. :O
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @kunalmajumder: Former Foreign Minister Jaswant Singh supports Manmohan Singh's step in inviting Sharif and says extension of Vajpayee's…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	ready to go foreign tho
</tweet>
<tweet>
	All I know is Foreign, but my bitch red, idk what that bitch sayin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@amir_alrahab nih >> PETITION FROM AUSTRALIAN ACADEMICS TO MINISTER FOR FOREIGN AFFAIRS http://t.co/9bDxfeTee7 via @victorcmambor
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @moaningmaskell: LOL @ dopey ungrateful foreign owners sacking a manager within 12 months of him winning the league.....oh #readingfc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Foreign car my roof missing, white on white I'm a fool with it
White on white I’m a fool with it. In that spotlight I’m a fool with it
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KlasraRauf: V didnt hear 4m foreign observers who used to monitor Pak elections&report ab8 rigging or no rigging.Where r they r didnt c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Foreign Service
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That foreign exchange teacher is from Seattle. I should have thrown away my anxiety and just talk with her. I could have known many things.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @rihanna: 2 day shoot for my upcoming Autumn/Winter collections with River Island was flawless! My models looked so damn good! Foreign c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Naval Open Source INTelligence: Foreign sub spotted near Japan's territorial water... http://t.co/PFyulbkuEF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@quotedojo: A man who does not know foreign language is ignorant of his own. ~Johann Wolfgang von Goethe #quote"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	So #ManCity have given #Mancini the boot. So the idea of a manager staying at a team for 2 or more yrs is now a foreign concept! ;-)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @deanhepburn: Julie Bishop whinges about Labor not able 2 retain foreign aid promise is breathtaking in hypocrisy. Howard FAILED UN http…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ImranKhanPTI sm of foreign srnds r dshearted by how pti iz bhavng,if v lose 1 dat iz a big loss:(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@klainttana adam and mia and some foreign website called her a female hooker
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @larsonchristina: China's Premier Li Keqiang to visit India, Pakistan, Switzerland & Germany next week on first official foreign trip: h…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Lion_for_Truth Curious investigation. No mention of one shooting range or a single shot fired. No foreign nationals aside from Malawians.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Remembering My Teacher, IR Giant Kenneth Waltz, Foreign Policy http://t.co/9suztYL5kw
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @najamsethi: All local and foreign observers have declared Punjab elections as the most neutral, fair and non-violent in Pakistani histo…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Kevin_Maguire Andrew Pierce brought in as Foreign Secretary
</tweet>
<tweet>
	POSTED WIT DEM RACKS YALL SLEEPIN WIT DA RATS & DA ROACHES IM JUST HOPIN I DONT SLIP UP ON MY FOCUS WE RIDIN FOREIGN YALL RIDIN FORD FOCUS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @deanhepburn: Julie Bishop whinges about Labor not able 2 retain foreign aid promise is breathtaking in hypocrisy. Howard FAILED UN http…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Top Chinese Official Warns of U.S.-China Trust Deficit, Foreign Policy   http://t.co/Kk1Gs0SCGy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @jake_whitt13: These rich foreign owners know fuck all about building a football club, they expect immediate success. I don't support ci…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	She said she never drove foreign, so introduced her to my red Ferrari.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @rihanna: 2 day shoot for my upcoming Autumn/Winter collections with River Island was flawless! My models looked so damn good! Foreign c…
</tweet>
