<tweet>
	RT @rihanna: 2 day shoot for my upcoming Autumn/Winter collections with River Island was flawless! My models looked so damn good! Foreign c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @APMESA_Outlook: @TulinDaloglu @AlMonitor sensational article, outlining how simplistic foreign policy based on imposed moral superiorit…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dear government, I guess ur private jets were delayed. See,if there were any foreign casualties I bet u wud hv been here in an instant!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I scored 7 out of 10 on the BBC News Quiz http://t.co/093QrmLkgD My grammar needs work but not too shabby for a foreign born englishman!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ammarakh  that would be ideal not to rely on foreign aid
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wish Harley didn't know how to get YouTube up on the tv.. Foreign Ben 10 videos it is then.. AGAIN! ? #Meh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I got foreign dreams #fuckamerican cars
</tweet>
<tweet>
	foreign journalists have profiled Imran Khan more than they have profiled any living thing in this part of the world. http://t.co/nAEBC3rZz6
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WorldVisionAus: World Vision Head of Policy Nancy Waites shares her #budget thoughts over at @WomensWeeklyMag: http://t.co/UMJAmo1nXe #…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @dickmezarry: i told my foreign grandma im marrying 5 men and shes like KURVA KURVA AND STARTED SCREAMING AT MY DAD AND MY GRANDMA CALLE…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The case for Britain staying in Europe - made by the Dutch Foreign Minister http://t.co/SbeAfPia85
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Chellaney: Former Foreign Secretary Kanwal Sibal's op-ed on how the Indian foreign minister is lending China a helping hand: http://t.c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	France sees snags in plans for Syria peace talks PARIS (Reuters) - France 's foreign minister warned on Tuesday a planned Syrian peace co
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MelissaTweets: RT @DanRiehl: About the only ppl this administration doesn't spy on is our frickin' foreign enemies.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just a reminder, do not to talk to strangers. Especially old foreign male ones that repeatedly call you 'very nice' and try and hug you. Run
</tweet>
<tweet>
	smh this king soulja shit ain't half as good as Foreign 1 or 2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pakistan's current situation is quite similar to Shah of Iran who was installed with foreign interference & was removed thru revolution.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Chellaney: Former Foreign Secretary Kanwal Sibal's op-ed on how the Indian foreign minister is lending China a helping hand: http://t.c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@spoiledleftie The foreign fandom is literally a handful of people.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ariel_silvera: If media covered American culture the way they cover foreign cultures - Yet another massacre has occurred in... http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Find out about the newest foreign exchange rewards http://t.co/dCRhFEnZLc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Egypt’s foreign reserves received a boost with inflows of $3.4 billion; $3 billion from #Qatar & the 1st installment of OCI tax settlement
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This is proof that foreign scouts aren't the only ones whose "timezones" are affected by @cmtcinc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@lionsdenkxip Azhar mahmood Shaun marsh Miller and Hussey should be 4 foreign players..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#SecStateKerry meets with @carlbildt at the Swedish Foreign Ministry http://t.co/V1hI2fgF6H
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have a football perversion for players with names akin to foreign translations of a British players name, and just found a beauty.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Sezdw see i just got a tweet about getting loads of followers sent to me. Then in a foreign language...Blocked!! :)
Yes need a draw atleast
</tweet>
<tweet>
	auto message : I wanna make foreign friends so if you interest, follow meI got facebook
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The first condition of understanding a foreign country is to smell it. - Rudyard Kipling
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ridin ina foreign whip diddy boppin when i drive!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	lol ok umpire motto ass
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Chellaney: Former Foreign Secretary Kanwal Sibal's op-ed on how the Indian foreign minister is lending China a helping hand: http://t.c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MelissaTweets: RT @DanRiehl: About the only ppl this administration doesn't spy on is our frickin' foreign enemies.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dear foreign bloggers or just followers. As i just asked my Greek friends, please send me ANY link worth reading-watching about the F4!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I need a Doctor to write the Forensic Medicine part of my exam. How must I remember all these foreign words
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Can't wait to grab keys to a foreign car
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MelissaTweets: RT @DanRiehl: About the only ppl this administration doesn't spy on is our frickin' foreign enemies.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Palestine Ministry of Foreign Affairs Breached, Confidential Documents  Leaked: http://t.co/MBT1T0tFUA … More  to come, stand by! #Anonymous
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Morning statement: @SerenaFalz "You brush your teeth like a foreign person" .... Well, I guess it's time to head to the library then... #LEL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Excellent mtg this morn w/ Qatari Minister of State for Foreign Affairs, Dr Khalid Al-Attiyah. Covered many issues. Now off to the airport.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @aria_ahrary: If people were as passionate about sports, reality T.V, and holidays as they were about foreign policy (drones...) We'd ha…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AHogan35 wow I didn't get this tho :( no foreign probs tho ;) ill be there soon!! #countdown @LozM10 is coming too right?!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	NEWS: Foreign Secretary William Hague reacts to Angelina Jolie's double mastectomy saying she's a 'brave lady' & an 'inspiration to many'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	NEWS: Foreign Secretary William Hague reacts to Angelina Jolie's double mastectomy saying she's a 'brave lady' & an 'inspiration to many'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	NEWS: Foreign Secretary William Hague reacts to Angelina Jolie's double mastectomy saying she's a 'brave lady' & an 'inspiration to many'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	this is the very first time I talk to my boyfriend wif foreign language...what the unforgettable experience!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BancoCapo: I just love foreign women and mixed women frfr ???????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JCJJMB Michu and Laudrup to Real, new foreign invester and a new tier for the stadium currently flying in by 6 helicopters.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BancoCapo: I just love foreign women and mixed women frfr ???????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	who gone tap out first
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Assoc7: 7 Tech firms spend $13.8M - Campaign Contributions to Senators for Cheap foreign IT Labor instead of Hiring CITIZENS
 http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When home feels foreign
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BlingKingSA: The more I see of tourism & the focus on foreign visitors the more I realise domestic tourism both business & leisure need…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just love foreign women and mixed women frfr ???????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	5 months ago I  had predicted Maryam  Nawaz  to be the next foreign minister.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	V much like @benedictbrogan take on EU row. An African coup. Leader abroad, forced to seek support of foreign govt http://t.co/xmAu7NdPY9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MelissaTweets: RT @DanRiehl: About the only ppl this administration doesn't spy on is our frickin' foreign enemies.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Foreign Secretary William Hague reacts to Angelina Jolie's double mastectomy saying she's a 'very brave lady' & an 'inspiration to many'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Donghae loves to watch movies, especially foreign movies. He likes to try to speak English #Haefact
</tweet>
<tweet>
	my Recent piece: FM Davuto?lu's Horizon On Foreign Policy and Endless Syrian Issue http://t.co/VHZoDSMjdE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's a must that I hit that millionaire mark!!!!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LAsThePlace: I don't get how such a powerful country can get to the point where a foreign born hack & puppet has this country by the ba…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	French Foreign Minister Laurent Fabius tries to weed out the terrorists from the Syrian opposition #Syria #UN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MelissaTweets: RT @DanRiehl: About the only ppl this administration doesn't spy on is our frickin' foreign enemies.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Najam Sethi: Domestic & foreign commentators say Punjab CT Govt has conducted fairest,freest & most neutral elections in #Pakistan's history
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cause unlike you I got nothin' to hide
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Cebr_uk claims UK GDP could be as much as 5% higher if the country's infrastructure was same standard as foreign competitors #business #UK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What Nigerian Women Really Think About Penis Size: No doubt, we have all been bombarded by foreign statistics ... http://t.co/KkzoDKNHJZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @russiaexpress: ?????????????????????????????????????Procedures for foreign citizens taking part in international sports http://t.co/Xet…
</tweet>
