<tweet>
	@GrantleeKieza @anthony_mundine I don't doubt he is a good bloke. Just a problem his fans don't know history and theory of boxing.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mattpep15: Take a look at the great comebacks in Boston sports history: http://t.co/AuXc0h7sVk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@thehistoryguy Not forgetting us oldies that have gone back to education with their history exam in 4 weeks time on Stalin and Russian Rev
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History was yeah... I'm fine with that. Maybe.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	theres so much to remember for history I feel like my head is gonna explode if I take in anymore facts or  key dates
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love me some Daft Punk. History of their collaborations. http://t.co/SqBhEMJyYF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Starting History revision at exactly 4.30.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HuffingtonPost: Latino activist to Texas lawmakers: "If you attack our History, our Culture, or our books, we will defy you"      http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @cosby_laura: @redhotsquirrel Rewriting of History again. If you went  sch now you wlld begin 2 believe that Germany was trying 2 save u…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	More events from This Day in History: May 14 (Infoplease): Share With Friends:  |  | Fun Stuff - This Day In H... http://t.co/yB6FgLLpPt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History will be kind to me, for I intend to write it. Winston Churchill
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @tenderlove: Game of Thrones has taught me so much about the rich history of the United Kingdom.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Twitlertwit: The history books will NOT be very kind to @SpeakerBoehner, worst failure EVER in history.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@UEA_History Good Luck to you all! Do good!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@FranMorrisx goodluck for your history exam, text me to tell me how it went xxx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Future of the Past at BBC TV History - do join in twittercast with BBC History Commissioner Q&A #bbcpast Wed 5pm http://t.co/tFF8Yi1N5s
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fender make a history....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Nancy Pelosi: If John Boehner Were A Woman, People Would Call Him 'The Weakest Speaker In History' http://t.co/A1g0TSHkmx via @HuffPostPol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chelsea v Benfica: History will be made in Europa final - http://t.co/khh73XGEIv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Vintage Nude Male On Leopard Skin Throw | @scoopit http://t.co/Emg9Rsc9ru
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wish I was doing higher history, so wish I was...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	cant believe i need to do credit history i cannot do it at all
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History here i comeeee ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Daily Telegraph repeats verbatim Daily Mail's false claim. Lazy journalism. @stwater cooperating w @RoyalAirForceUK
 http://t.co/rvm7wqNOWq
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm a sick girl, filming thrilling killer film & presenting on how officials tortured the suspects in China's history.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In revising on my own cause everyone in the world seems to be doing history.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Isn't it unbelievably arrogant to assume the Twitter title of 'The History Guy'? Maybe other disciplines have them too...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	abortion
tcot
Do u know every 3 days, more blacks r killed by abortion than have been killed by the KKK in its entire history tcot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History's Door by Husky from Forever So #NowPlaying
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If it wasn't for my stomach issues I wouldn't be behind so many essays and missing an exam from history. What to do... I don't wanna drop.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Did my social studies test today... AND I DIDN'T DIE!!! yea not doing history or geography next year -_-
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @cosby_laura: @redhotsquirrel Rewriting of History again. If you went 2 sch now you wlld begin 2 believe that Germany was trying 2 save …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @dunyanews: Chelsea, Benfica chase history in Europa final
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Sashmac72: Lets all raise a glass to @SwannyDPM at 7 30 to bid good riddance to the most dysfunctional g'ment in our history #Fudget201…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HuffingtonPost: Latino activist to Texas lawmakers: "If you attack our History, our Culture, or our books, we will defy you"      http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	?Abe1;Nation Image="Beauty";PrimeMinister Shinzo Abe says,"1;Japan is the Nation which cherishes culture, tradition, nature, and history._ ^
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Art? Or history with mr Sissons? I think my choice is obvious :3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	2 niggas doin the slow grind and holding each other. Goddamn. Sad day in Dark Skin History
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LesMisDVD: 'It's a dream...This is going to go down in history'. The Independent. Order your copy of #LesMis now! http://t.co/73H21xxoH…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ivanF1: #Pirelli didn’t have the right info about tires because the lack of test they only extrapolate winter data and we know the hist…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	To bad we can't rewrite our own history.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The history of dirty words http://t.co/It4b8rMZzj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ashleighmackie_ good luck with your history exam! ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ItsM1tchRL @EastsFan And thats ok because between 00 and now we've been runners up more times than you've been in GF in your History #Boom
</tweet>
<tweet>
	buildng bec those little, how about its for history, second i dont have anything about listing the negotiation the wise pple had+
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @El_In_Charge: Zaha hasn't pulled on a United shirt yet but he's alrdy part of the history as Fergie's last signing
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @acmrs_org: On this day in history: May 13, 1568 – Battle of Langside: the forces of Mary, Queen of Scots, are defeated by a... http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	First history exams an hour and a half long.. then my second ones an hour and 45 minutes long... KILL ME NOW.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @janreiMueki: mataasnakahoy is definitely making a history.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History come at me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_geek_: a first in iloilo city's history: one group swept the elections. from congressman, to mayor, the vice mayor and 12 sangguniang …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Making history
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dun feel like studying for history unlike my two best friend kevan n yinci all quai quai study
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Little Known Black History Fact: Church Bombing Victims Honored http://t.co/tJRikliKX5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JackMcAllister6 jack do you do history?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I want to go to #TattooAvicii with @nicoalzona because I want to be a part of this awesome party which will make a history!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT "@comradeazhari: History spoil my exam mood. Someone cheer me up.."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History and dnt paper left
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm bout 2 retweet all the lightskin jokes on twitter u gon see the darkest Avi's in history
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DrManishKumar1: MMS wil go down in history as weakest PM,failed economist,foolish diplomat,worst administrator,dumb politician&Head of …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The genesis and emergence of Troodos and Cyprus constitute a miracle of nature geosciences, history and myth!... http://t.co/hlzCz3sluG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CameronAtfield: Well keep it then #killthepaddlepoplion MT @brisbanelions Lions have a pretty good history in games they've worn a spec…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why does this man still have a job? BBC News - Hunt doubts Gove on history evidence http://t.co/SSZdyAJQEl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Doing nothing in History
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Regretting picking history next year with all these tweets
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @wired: Star Trek was one of the most forward-thinking franchises in TV and film history but it faltered on LGBT crew members http://t.c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That there are wonderful stories in our Irish ancient history is no reason to doubt the whole. We have Harry Potter books in our times!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And Mrs Anders history lessons are up to their usual standard, absolutely nothing
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History will be kind to me, for I intend to write it. Winston Churchill
</tweet>
<tweet>
	black history,black freedomwe made it first,,,danm what a nation,haitians,what a country,haiti
</tweet>
<tweet>
	any group of pple free in their belives as long as their practicing tht not taking others rights, so non will give syrianc same history +
</tweet>
<tweet>
	good luck to everyone with History! ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	GOOD LUCK HISTORY PEOPLE.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	good luck to everyone with their history exams today
</tweet>
