<tweet>
	RT @SciencePorn: If Earth’s entire history was viewed as a 24 hour period, humans would only represent 1 minute and 17 seconds.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chelsea, Benfica chase history in Europa final: AMSTERDAM AFP) - After a turbulent season, history beckons for... http://t.co/PpgRnbMjmJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History will be the death of me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ETohJiaLe: Can remember all the lyrics of my songs cannot remember 1 page of history._.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History exam today ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	might just write 'their all dead' on my history paper
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chelsea, Benfica chase history in Europa final: AMSTERDAM AFP) - After a turbulent season, history beckons for... http://t.co/ICyc0ojSoN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@rachelburden @bbc5live Coincidence or what? I'm off to a Genetic Medicine clinic this morning about Braca testing because of family history
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@graham_cpfc have you a booking history with Palace if any left on Saturday go public.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chelsea, Benfica chase history in Europa final: AMSTERDAM AFP) - After a turbulent season, history beckons for... http://t.co/xA08UKn7Qc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have a really important history exam today and I know about a quarter of what I should this should be fun
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I receive none of your love, dear History.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @liamstack: Note to @BuzzFeed: if s'one in #Syria mutilates a corpse its not a shout out to 7th century Arab history #orientalism http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is a history tomorrow is a mestry
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @aku_jujur: The past is history the future is a mystery  this moment you have now is a gift :) #AJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BlieEou: Hats off to hank; most influential shit in tv history. You da man.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Most epic NAM history project ever http://t.co/eQxCHgpQcB #httpgdatayoutubecomschemas2007video
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In pandemonium about choosing the hilarious Russia history option, kill me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	history exam this morning.... actually pooping myself
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In class working on history! Probably close to favorite subject ????????????????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	‘I studied History for 5 years, but there was not a single chapter on the history of the Northeast’ http://t.co/nu9YiIrz32
</tweet>
<tweet>
	& history paper for tomorrow wooooooooooooiiiiiii
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Can't be bothered with history today but what makes it even worse I have fucking biology tomorrow!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kris's fly was down in the beginning of EXO M's 'History' MV.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Teen swimmer makes history with national selection http://t.co/UldEqcateq
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Kellyy_Lo yah in now for history x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chelsea, Benfica chase history in Europa final: AMSTERDAM AFP) - After a turbulent season, history beckons for... http://t.co/6aiLmVua5E
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Lauren_w_s: HISTORY COME AT ME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @therealMickeyT: “@crystalmais: @therealMickeyT the only history you have is of printing money you prick”yeah but my money was better qu…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@JessyJamJar: this history exam will be the death of me” good luck cxxxx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MARLONLWAYANS: Some people know what they want in and out of life while others just fumble and flail. Be focused be driven make your hi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chelsea, Benfica chase history in Europa final: AMSTERDAM AFP) - After a turbulent season, history beckons for... http://t.co/cUqsgei2ls
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BarbieTash_LDN: Okay Russian history today I pray I get a terror question and one on 1905 rev
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Im entered for the history exam... Should i sit it?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chelsea, Benfica chase history in Europa final: AMSTERDAM AFP) - After a turbulent season, history beckons for... http://t.co/jLjNfOsPzO
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@samallsee is it your real trophy history or your football managed trophy history haha?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The problem about history is they can ask you literally anything
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Read the First Chapter Chauvet, The Dream Unlocked #History by Steve Meads http://t.co/UhXEbXFEaZ caffib
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Should make the History words into a song so can remember better!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	soundtrack of history exam:
panic // the smiths
I started something I couldn't finish // morrissey
no surprises (im gunna fail) //radiohead
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. And Today? Today is a gift. That's why we call it the present.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	yesterday is history tomorrow is mistery~
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Basically, all you need to know for history exam: Lenin=good guy, Stalin=bad guy!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The "religiosity" of a country's law generally tells you more about its history than present day religious feelings http://t.co/G1l8SRMK22
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Is it wrong that I'm excited for this history exam for the pure fact once its finished I'll never have to do half of history again?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KieraCole3: I feel sorry for everyone doing credit history..   I'm freaking about general?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Does #socialmedia bend the arc of history more towards #democracy?" All three Secretaries of State, Powell, Baker, Alb ...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@xiumii @ChazzaB_ 4 questions on anything except british history please
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MARLONLWAYANS: Some people know what they want in and out of life while others just fumble and flail. Be focused be driven make your hi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History is infinite. die soon write
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@alanamccann_xo @elliebaylie I was on a geography one last week & a history one yesterday lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	good luck to everyone doing the history/geography exam today. PLS DON'T KILL YOURSELVES
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WOWFactsOfLife: Native Americans lost their history, their land, their culture, and is one of the least discussed genocides in world hi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_LaurenAngus: HA HA HA HA H H HISTORY HA HA FAILING
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If I could, I'd rewrite history, I'd choose differently. If I could, I would. #TheStory
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History exam fucking come at me u faggot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Its black history month every month "
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If you do law and history my thoughts are with you today ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lies. Any southern state with a fierce history of slavery and classism will have ghosts and demons like no other.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Double history, pls no
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @xmatthewadams: History is fun anyway
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @aosa_aone: In history of havin a crush I don't remember when someone actually got a chance with there's
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sod British history, I'll focus on the Civil Rights Movement.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Already prepared for my fails in history and german. Lol lifes good!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@nicoletanyijing history test what topics ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ron Swanson's medical history form :'D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Law and history... Writing non stop today... My hand is gonna fall off defo
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cannot be fucked with history today.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Ms_cooch_brown: Yo if I hook Chad I will go down in Philly history. That nigga is the most eligible bachelor in Philly????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Good luck to everyone doing History today!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Excited for our history party today #cake #HannahLovesHistory ?@hannahmaher_
</tweet>
<tweet>
	History will be kind to me, for I intend to write it. Winston Churchill
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SupremeGREAM @milonare yes dollar savings is a good point. I can't wait to hear the story, I'm happy for @safaricom they've made history!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Argh so much for history pulling up my combined humans. It actually pulled me down instead :c
</tweet>
<tweet>
	People moaning about a little history paper PFT TRY FURTHER MATHS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Climate Tipping Point? Concentration of Carbon Dioxide Tops 400 ppm for First Time in Human History http://t.co/jPUj3UNoLK @democracynow
</tweet>
