<tweet>
	RT @meganforse_: Can I just go on holiday now please
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Well roll on 4pm then let the holiday begin :-)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CIANMH hahaha u were on the show!? Sorry bro :P parents shouldnt be shocked at what kids do its a holiday lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	At the gate ready for my flight to JFK - next stop Florida. Surreal feeling that I have no work to do! #chillin #holiday
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Who wants to just pack a bag and go europe for bank holiday coming?? Its about time I did something crazy. Dont want to go on my own
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@kizrmudz awww bummer oh wellsss tis holiday its watching every series I have marathon
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Looking to shed some holiday weight? Here are some helpful tips to get you there faster. http://t.co/FmgTmY7WPE - sp
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Lennyjacobson I wholeheartedly agree.. Kilmer as Doc Holiday was magic. #ImYourHuckleberry
</tweet>
<tweet>
	the holiday was just doing homework! It's very annoying!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Ali_Knighty @thewobster great stuff, nutrition obviously spot on! See you at 6pm for a final session before #holiday
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@patrickwintour Tories-so stuck on EU don't realise not major issue 4normal folk-we like Europe,holiday there,world has moved on since 1930s
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@gabriela_gita yes, idk.. i'd rather go somewhere than nothing to do in my home -.- home sweet home is useless when i've a long holiday..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Hoyababy_VIP hahaha poor thing xD heeh all the best lat ! Will and must go out this holiday kay jiayou :*:*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Holiday needs to stop interrupting my summer.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When you at school: I wanna go home and holiday 
When you holiday: stay home and said I wanted to school
</tweet>
<tweet>
	stay blondie or go brownie for my holiday? ?? #decisions #marbs2013
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Nicomadd22 Na plan is to book another holiday when I get back mate. I need the motivation. And I'm finding a boxing club up here too
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Countdown is on till holiday time ? #hatethisrain ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @tae1virgil: J holiday - put you to bed
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@stuartfergus he also wants him hung! Life should mean life in jail not 10 years. It shouldn't be a glorified holiday camp as well in prison
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That Blue Cross ad ???... why wouldn't they take there nan on the Holiday too?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Back at work for three days. Time needs to hurry up as i don't know if I can wait all these days to my holiday!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	everybody in MPLS talking like its a holiday "What are you doing for 90 degree day?"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @amberlawley: Just rememebered the time me + @rebeccadousey had an arguement on holiday at 3 in the morning and my mum was telling us to…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ForeverPeazer: Danielle loves shopping, going to concerts, going on holiday and fangirling. She's one of us :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	J holiday - put you to bed
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@LittleTalmo @ThatsEarth Is it too late to change our holiday booking??!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fun Affordable Pet Friendly Holiday #Wales Camping Pods! by Red Dragon Holidays http://t.co/Gi5i5IMNh1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SentrimCastle: For Best Holiday Deals in Nairobi, Kenya.
do visit http://t.co/Ff9GOQG8sW
</tweet>
<tweet>
	?Now taking appointments for week beginning 3rd June......Mink Lashes are ideal for going on holiday!!! http://t.co/QtCUZU5M9M
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I beg to dream and differ from the hollow lies, this is the dawning of the rest of our lives! ? #HOLIDAY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Maybe go on a holiday for 3-4 months and just RELAX..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@StillerDesigns Not for another month - hotels and a train to review, plus a weeks holiday in the Kalahari desert...no internet
</tweet>
<tweet>
	the holiday was very boring!!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SophieEddy29: Can I just go on holiday ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Holiday flights booked! USA here I come! :D #excited #NYC #LA #Vegas See you in June. Open to suggestions on must do things.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sarahburns88: Lovely holiday in @lanzarote with @anneburns27 airport could do better, delayed, no communication, had to google to find …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The only thing getting me through these exams is knowing i have a holiday soon after them. #winning
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hot Natured featuring Anabel Englund - Reverse Skydiving (Shadow Child Remix) Prepares me for my holiday jheeeeze http://t.co/8eEsbyqr5L
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Win A Fantastic Family Holiday To Cornwall With Parkdean | http://t.co/JlrT1sEKyq
</tweet>
<tweet>
	KRW Modern Block Custom Save the Date Petal Invitations: KRW Modern Block Custom Save the Date Petal - Hot Pin... http://t.co/1oa78AJnnJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	KRW Modern Block Custom Save the Date Pomegranate Custom Invitations: KRW Modern Block Custom Save the Date Po... http://t.co/RqOV28BepE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	KRW Modern Block Custom Save the Date Earth Tone Custom Invitations: KRW Modern Block Custom Save the Date Earth Tone http://t.co/8ZI1WQr58T
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @COAChildcare: First Mothers Day was in May 10 1908, Founded by Anna Jarvis; it was made a national holiday by President Wilson in 1914 …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Best Man Holiday Teaser Trailer http://t.co/EDE3IvPodG @102_jamz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Morning everyone! Its nearly Friday which means it's nearly Bank Holiday Weekend! What's everyone up to this weekend?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PoppyHollands: I can tell when I go on holiday with my friends that we would end up staying somewhere like they do on inbetweeners
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@February2102 haha..u really don't know?im actually is that white...ever since I had half year of holiday I had been locking at home
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Got your pre holiday tan booked ?  We are mobile based in #westlothian ,  book in your Nouvatan today x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TheAsplands No, I feel the same! Love my lazy mornings in school holiday time!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Best Man Holiday http://t.co/xAeiWWcwb5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Can't believe I go ok holiday in 25 days :O coming up so quick
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@carleyblythe lol I think you need to go on a crazy holiday then after that it doesn't matter lol. I was going to go to ibiza with my ex but
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Brohatch Hahahaha really? But you were on holiday, no need for moaning, take it you didn't manage to get her pissed?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@EmmaCaseyx what we gonna do about a holiday? #ineedone
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Is today some sort of holiday nobody told me about? Where is everyone?! #work
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@aliceowen_ guessing you know who this is about!! Have an Amazing holiday dear xxx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In the airport, holiday starts now! 
#Cuba ????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@LauraRyan__ I can imagine us both on holiday! #dontspeaktome @_beckymartin knows how much of a crank I am in the morning haha!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Book now to avoid the rush - Bank holiday 4x4 car hire from a name you can trust http://t.co/xu5MreHbxh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WE'RE ALL GOING ON A SUMMER HOLIDAY!!! ?????????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yeah holiday tmr!!!
</tweet>
