<tweet>
	Hey Guys Please do come and bring one and all..... Its Holiday Time Here... :) http://t.co/mlOQjGJ3wU
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@swaggxcanadian have a good holiday we love u ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@chlokells D-D-DROP THE BASS. I start work soon so it's like a little holiday for the moment ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@josh04678858 @vileanimal1993 you will be out in 2 weeks. Bank holiday again
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wish the wee guy that washes the cars was off for the next 3 weeks, washing cars from now till holiday sounds brilliant haha! Love doing it?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mother's Day Cards For Dads: A Sweet Gesture Or Holiday Double-Dipping? http://t.co/GUY7DUHz53 via @consumerist
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @taylerhalfordx: i need to go on holiday, that's final
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@xjessicawalker hahaha omg yeees! Btw i asked dad about holiday thing and he said only 4 (inc me) :(((( idek what to do
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Top 10 Cornish holiday cottages for Spring Half Term http://t.co/x5PXauE8KZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just had a lovely phone call of my mum, looks like she's enjoying her holiday in spain. Miss her loads though. I love you millions mum. <3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fell back asleep and dreamt I was on holiday in what was basically paradise and I went swimming and everything ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Up early going holiday shopping!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I seriously need to go for a vacation on this upcoming holiday. Urgh so stressed
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@rebeccavokins @stevie_wyatt Hi! We see you're looking for a holiday - can we help at all?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Looking out your window and seeing heavy rain is depressing! Need a holiday somewhere sunny and hot! #ifonly
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DanHasALamb @PaulHasALamb OMG was it that long ago? (Feels old). Great memory. I was on holiday in Wales at the time. #sigh #damon
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@nikharjivani its not a holiday its a day off lol like how ppl have weekends?? That supposed to be my weekend haha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	glad that summer holiday starts soon
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ElinorThomas cctv on bank holiday weekend #enoughsaid
</tweet>
<tweet>
	holiday
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Telegraph: What women don't want: "You, on a sailing holiday? Won't you be in the way?" Our weekly team-up with @everydaysexism: http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Check out our website http://t.co/cMDGqnLYoZ for a full list of activities for the June Bank Holiday Wkend! Also see our beautiful queens!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@cheahpeiwei no :( Kay fine. Huh since when today is a public holiday?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@anaispontett: working 55 hour weeks to afford a holiday for your birthday, and then being told you're not serious about it? Yh ok” ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	FYI: China sets aside September 20th as a national holiday known as “Love Your Teeth Day.”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	During the holiday season we want you to be safe.  Be sure to lock your doors and always place gifts in the trunk and out of site.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Taboo2Taboo: 26th of may @magicalcircusuk is back for another bank holiday special #twistedtokyo at circle

#circle… http://t.co/22TI8A…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Need to get a holiday booked! #ineedsomethingtolookforwardto #fedup ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	HOLIDAY..!! I can't wait anymore
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@kazenga25 @I_CALDERON_14 @OfficialBHAFC Chin up boys you have done us proud.  Go on holiday, get ready for next season #keepthefaith #BHAFC
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Still searching for a villa to spend your holiday? Casa de la mar give's great promotions this month! http://t.co/lCh2s5yIv9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Mullies If that was true, and remembering your holiday photos, you're not looking too bad on them! Still running?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Holiday, please come faster!!! I'm so tired of my fuckin' school?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thinking of going back deep red before my holiday! #redhead
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@miss_cathcowan @glennrule If I don't see you or speak to you before, have the best holiday ? ?? xxx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Two weeks today until holiday time!  Can't wait to get away from this place!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	After dreaming about holiday all night I have managed to upset myself it's only may!! #zante2013
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Eh next month holiday hope theres no hwss
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Let' s go to holiday !!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	holiday but still have lessons
</tweet>
<tweet>
	8 weeks and 4 days until holiday yayayay so excited
</tweet>
<tweet>
	24 Holiday . yeah enjoy our holiday but now need to struggle .. still have 9 papers to go ! SC1n2,EKO1n2,ICT,AKAUN1n2,PAI2,M31,
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ScotsCouple awww bless you, I've done a few countries on this holiday. You going follow me?;) x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bank holiday weekend I just wanna party and bullshit!! This month and the next few months to come is gonna be stress
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What's top of your essentials list when it comes to packing for a holiday with b...: What's top of your essent... http://t.co/Iy1fF6Mta7
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i need to go on holiday, that's final
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BarrelHopping My tip always have your next holiday already booked so you can start looking forward to the next one!  http://t.co/3a058nA0cs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @jackstearman: @YorkKnightsRLFC May 1/2 term holiday club coming up!£20 per day or £50 for three days!Includes daily entry to waterworld…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	holiday :P
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Holiday clothes shopping is so much fun #mexico #mexoparty
</tweet>
<tweet>
	6 days till holiday, really should start thinking about what I'm gna take ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@mistryneha: The 2 days at work after a nice holiday are the worst! Dealing with day 1 ?" WORD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Looking to shed some holiday weight? Here are some helpful tips to get you there faster. http://t.co/G1HEE29VLY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Really wish I took an extra 2 weeks off to "prepare" for my holiday. Work is not fun right now.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cryptic half-heard conversation of the morning: 'So we've got pictures of Mrs Holiday-home and the buffalo?'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Holiday in 2 weeks my birthday in 3 weeks #sun #excited #cantwait ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tomorrow marks the last day of paper and here come a month holiday!???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Telegraph: What women don't want: "You, on a sailing holiday? Won't you be in the way?" Our weekly team-up with @everydaysexism: http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@james007barrett so gutted.  Missed last year cos of exams and this year because I can't take holiday for 3 months. Gutted.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I posted a new photo to Facebook http://t.co/AfY9rPdpXn
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DJLEE246 rachy needs a holiday
</tweet>
