<tweet>
	people just dont make good horror movies nowadays.. sigh. the only horror movie that got me a phobia was "chucky doll"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Release Details for Friday The 13th Documentary Crystal Lake Memories - HorrorMovies.ca http://t.co/RTPxZTC4K7 via @horrormovies
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@usnews: We're only beginning to understand the full weight of the growing student loan debt http://t.co/uzCFHweyMp"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BringMeSatan: A drink, for the horror that I'm in, for the good guys and the bad guys, for the monsters that I've passed
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lie still bag of bones.
Lie still bag of bones.
Lie still bag of bones.
Lie still bag of bones.
Lie still bag of bones.
#Horror
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Horror movie niiight. I'm going to vomit and cry and love everything.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SurvivorPenner  I have no idea but it was pretty decent as a horror I thought as well! #BadMoviesGetTooMuchPublicity
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@HQReviews One of the best films ever. Not just horror.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@spacevz that. that was not the response i was expecting i thought you were watching some weird horror movie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A drink, for the horror that I'm in, for the good guys and the bad guys, for the monsters that I've passed
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Baay_Gyalness soon enno! me ago buss a watch offa one horror movie fuss
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @twisted_twins: Photo: American Mary is #22 on the iTunes US store for horror. I really really want to hit top ten by the... http://t.co…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @broadwaycom: Patti LuPone and Angela Bassett will tap into their inner witches for AMERICAN HORROR STORY: COVEN: http://t.co/MJSKciUrDK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bag of Bones is a complete mind fuck. Pretty good though. I give it 7/10. #Horror #Miniseries #StephenKing
</tweet>
<tweet>
	no...es negra eh jajaja q horror
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just bought season 2 of American horror story #adioslife
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @usnews: We're only beginning to understand the full weight of the growing student loan debt http://t.co/ACVw4Qb9kH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @rachelburden: @ladydaventry i agree, i think the horror of her story is how little she had
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ThomasDale5 original horror :D gotta love it
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KevinHearne: Created a monster thingie and kind of scared myself. Probably a good thing that I don't write horror.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tip no.1: Don't invite someone you’ve just met to an abandoned warehouse, or another setting where horror movies take place.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Incog_negro lol, horror movies are hilarious to me.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	http://t.co/p4HqSNCzm6

Are you a zombie fan? If you are, then drop by my Wattpad account and be updated with my horror-packed novel! :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Evan Peters sale no solo en American Horror Story, sino que también lo hizo en An American Crime. Se le ve que le mola America, pues.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Does the family in American Horror Story NOT close their doors? -.-
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@cronsilo You're lucky got covered. Heard horror stories insurance companies make it hard to claim.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Stuff4blackppl: Being killed first in horror movies
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hey! Sen. Pappas is reading from a piece of paper!  The horror. #MNSen
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@NME: The Vaccines' Justin Young says One Direction are 'natural songwriters'" NME hype band that supports manufactured pop? Shock horror!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@goldennsoul aww man they really don't make movies like that anymore, this is why I stick to my horror movies lol no feelings. No tears.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just wasted two hours of my life watching this "horror". . . time for bed!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#tcot #education RT @usnews We're only beginning to understand the full weight of the growing student loan debt http://t.co/nrQ2m1wC0r
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching Americain Horror Story, Waiting for my Work Permit to get faxed back. Wanting to be with my boo #bored #missingyou
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Greenock hotel horror: Mother and daughter overdosed on painkillers before slashing their own arms http://t.co/OhHogfjeEa  via @Daily_Record
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why do people in Horror Movies yell out “Hello?” as if the killer is gonna say “yeah, I’m in the kitchen, want a sandwich?"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I will definitely seize every opportunity to do whatever I want before next week... because that's when the real horror comes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@for_polanco The horror.. I fear for the worst lol.-.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	No black man with a mustache survived an 80s horror movie.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @usnews: We're only beginning to understand the full weight of the growing student loan debt http://t.co/ACVw4Qb9kH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dios mio el q lea los tuits q le escribo a @cejaspobladas y no tenga idea quien es, pensaran q soy la mas pervertida y sucia.. Horror total
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TDHorror: I remember going to the local VIDEO 94 Rental store in the 80a and staring at the #HORROR covers. What's your favorite? #VHS …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Angelina Jolie reduced her Boobs! Oh the horror! The horror!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RixterSm2 Damn it. I need a good horror to scare me shitless. So hard to find these days.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @vicktaaar: I kinda want reindeer girl to write a kinky gothic horror story lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I hope the Kermit Gosnell trial at least awakened SOME people's eyes on the horror of what abortion truly is. #thefive #lnyhbt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Play From 2-Year-Old's POV in 'Among the Sleep' Horror Video Game http://t.co/qahUGcWUVe via Anita Li
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I know I'm late but, I LOVE THE AMERICAN HORROR STORY.?? #bestshowever
</tweet>
