<tweet>
	Ahhhhh I so enjoyed that film I watched yesterday!  I want more Jewish horror stories!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MotherJones: Walnut Grove in Mississippi: "a picture of such horror as should be unrealized anywhere in the civilized world." http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Shall re read some horror stories!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Horror movies always has bitches in their underwear
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @frankieboyle: Of course the real reason that the United States is such a horror story is that they built it on top of an Indian graveya…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	She look like something straight outta horror movie in that avi.......
</tweet>
<tweet>
	why does toby have to be in horror movies ugh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WTF? RT @angryknob: As footage of a "rebel" allegedly eating a soldier's heart emerges from #Syria the "civilised" world recoils in horror.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm freezing. My window doesn't open and if I shut off the aircon it'll be dead air. Oh, the horror of living in beautiful places!  #Austin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Biker loses arms, leg in fatal accident in Perth's south: Source: PerthNow. A MOTORCYCLIST has been killed in ... http://t.co/Yb3yDBBn07
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Horror Thailand
</tweet>
<tweet>
	They cover the black dahlia murder in American horror story
GOODBYE LIFE!!! I'm holding a flashlight for the rest of the night
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What kind of movies do you like? — action one, horror,comedy http://t.co/IXmOGwaAUH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DavidPerryRadio: Boy, did that balcony shake to the Time Warp last night @mayflower - Here's Brad & Janet @rockyhorroruk chatting http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	7u7: My favorite genre is “starts out normal but then turns into really disturbing psychological horror” http://t.co/Zf0yHI9kfU
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Season after season, episode after each fucked up episode, I would love to be on the Real World. BUT, SAME WITH AMERICAN HORROR STORY. So..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Congress Takes Action To Root Out Abortion HOUSES of HORROR, 2 House Committees Issued Letters ALL State Health Depts http://t.co/doWcnoO0Vn
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This Arnisyah eh! ask the show to not scare her when she wanted to watch horror -.-
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video http://t.co/fVA6I4GlfE Batman's Top 3 Horror Films & The Long Halloween Review!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ShaneKPONeill: 5* Best Dracula book since the original. If Goth horror is your thing you will love this http://t.co/3iwL8i63kg #ASMSG #…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Horror movie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dark Skies oh yeah so awesome #aliens #horror #cool #awesome
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@jocelynthesnail IKRRR they do lotsa things then after you go home and wash your hair.... oh de horror ._. Im okay with it now sigh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fuck horror games ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CNNVideo The craftiness of man can't last forever. The backyard gives a detailed story of the horror inside the house
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Help me from that shitty locale horror pls
</tweet>
<tweet>
	like y would u watch this gross shit its like a horror movie this is not real life!????????!!!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@LewEvil i know this. iv had many fun times there. but always nervous. always. the horror stories...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@yelyahwilliams what's your favorite horror movie?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TobyTurner you better make this horror movie available to order overseas for us Oceania folk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Do you sell #horror #books #comics #games #DVD #Bluray & merchandise online? What you need is a banner advert on http://t.co/pM1jtFkEus
</tweet>
