<tweet>
	Arrgh! --- the horror. My son is sending Angry Bird Star Wars tweets using my account. He's only 5.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	08:30 The Ken Dodd Show: The King of Knotty Ash examines black magic and gets a part in a horror movie. Or does he? http://t.co/4c1h2Yin1x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Nice of the team to be so supportive this morning after last nights horror show @sandpithq #bhafc http://t.co/MUHSj5qRYq
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Lulu_Topia I think this should go under the category of horror movie; did u see his face? lol....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @wwhitneyhayss: The whole "if you can't love yourself, no one will" mentality is complete bullshit.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@HalalPORK ya sia. like some horror movie.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SadeCee_143 thats a horror ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BeerOholic: School time horror moment:
1. Science teacher enters the class
2. Declares a surprise oral test
3. Points at u and says, #I…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@tanndell My mom still awaits the day I return to live in Canada. And then she plans to move in, much to my horror. She misses Canada.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HorrorMovies: Arnold Schwarzenegger In Negotiations to Star in The Toxic Avenger Remake! http://t.co/xKn4rg536J
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Horror "@Questionnier: Describe your night in 1 word? #QnA"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Loudwire: What horror movies have inspired hard rock and metal songs? Check out our list here: http://t.co/IwLpZsuKxm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	[AILEE FACTS] She likes romantic comedies and horror movies
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@lotsacatsndogs @sofiagoncalves no worries friend & yes it does help!! We keep bringing awareness +signs, this horror show must end. Tysvm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Of course the blonde girl is always the idiot in a horror movie.
Stereotypical.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If the people in horror movies would listen to me, They'd still be alive right now ;)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	But of course horror movies are the best ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@my_bitz Argh!! If I wasn't awake before I am now. Jeebus!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@chase_horror ah I see. well that changes things!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Imagine the horror of Robert Peston interviewing William Hague. It would be a nightmare of irritating inflections. #BBCbreakfast
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Some barbers, u could sleep off soon as they put the clipper to ur head. Then we have the others... days later, u're still living d horror.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The #FXArtists Behind #Tremors and #Aliens Are Making a CGI-Free Horror Movie and Need Your Help  http://t.co/b8SIjna35c
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ThugBarbiee check it out its a good movie, well that's if you like scary/horror movies lol.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@my_bitz Holy shit, man!! Give a girl some notice! Clowns are freaking scary-assed!! :-P
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dan siank ne kami horror story
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I feel like talking about horror movies without context is something that gets you put on a watchlist.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	these days horror movies aren't really horror, it's just suspense and gore and murder. where's the psychological mind screwing part??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"There is something so humanizing about horror movies-when are we more human than when we are not in control?"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ZEA_leader ahah look like Kevin oppa is running away, like horror movie place hahaha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@netflix Oooo netflix please add the second season of American Horror Story!!! @AHSFX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	watching a horror film
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dear southern hemisphere (north get sleep) this is a love/horror story depending on if you're a romantic or a cynic http://t.co/sN4aYSCA1R
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Shell_568 what the heck is that?! Too early in the morning to look upon such horror
</tweet>
