<tweet>
	Here is a list of my recommended reads for Indie Authors!  Learn the tips and tricks of the published! http://t.co/7r4wXxlrLw #books #indie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Need a professional Book Covers? Allow the @AuthorAlliance team of professionals to help. http://t.co/hAcb7nUO9s
</tweet>
<tweet>
	dictating writer / Indie girlfriend.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Christopher Cain At Helm Of Indie Eco-Thriller ‘Terra Infirma’ http://t.co/S9X6I6YmKw via @nikkifinke
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I asked @sunshinetasneem if we could be indie and this was the response i received....yea shes totally hipster http://t.co/JBQvSVzjV9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Got an #ipad #SAMSUNG #TABLET Support indie authors buy your kindle books here http://t.co/OFxVohTy2W
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SpooderW I don't understand why hardworking indie devs get downvoted while scams and lies get massive upvotes + press :(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NiallOfficial do you listen to indie?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	indie music takes me back two years ago
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Indie House Books contributor @JaniceLanePalko writes - Should You Tamper With a Classic?  http://t.co/qUIiNOlU1p
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ferricide indie RPG that came out 3 months ago. The game itself is nothing special but the plot is really crazy and deep and dark as hell.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Grape_Rape: I'm going to take pictures like this with my boyfriend http://t.co/r4zxX20hdb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@_vroom If it was some indie artist, I wouldn’t care as much. But it makes me think less of Daft Punk as a whole.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We truly support the indie artist, and we are always will too give them a helping hand.#dagrahynd #real-support http://t.co/CNguKNwOGT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @kseniaanske: Be goofy. Run around flapping your arms like wings. Jump and dance and laugh. Ignore those shaking their heads at you, kee…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@indie_visuals How long did it take to get a shooting permit? I’m looking to shoot in CGN Airport
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video from @phedran http://t.co/Q0jEwrSEQL Indie-d || Henry Attacks
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hey @dexbonus , would you still recommend Lucius? It's part of the Indie Royal Mayhem bundle atm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Black Light ft Jesse Evans - The Johnny Walker Experience http://t.co/eLzuV7I6Zv via @indabamusic
</tweet>
<tweet>
	if you're wondering our cover photo is of @BooksActually , Singapore's well loved indie bookstore and a resident of #singaporehouse #gtf13
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Do people still think it's indie to listen to Knife Party? Even I was listening to them last year.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Feel free to post your books on our Facebook Page http://t.co/9AMA8rJwta #KINDLE almost 2,000 likes :-)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	what material things do you want to buy rn — indie merch i guess http://t.co/MZJNt2xxkL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The NEW 2013 Ford Escape with "Ego Boost"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Back to marketing Past Imperfect - penning some press releases re the indie way for local papers where story scenes are set.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This show is so weird and different and crazy! Its like watching and indie tv show instead of an indie film
</tweet>
<tweet>
	LIFE OF THE PARTY, Written on Sept. 29, 2010.My first observation of 'indie' in today's culture. http://t.co/8OsUVFcUne
</tweet>
<tweet>
	INDIE FILM CLUB MIAMI announces a new SCREENWRITERS LAB ...: IFCM's Screenwriters lab is a three month program... http://t.co/zHODvcm3rm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	best tune i heard in a long time from an indie. https://t.co/knQ6K4n0Vt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Trying to update my #pop crate and ended up discovering a gold mine of #indie songs. It's a good day for my collection.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sometimes direct action is a challenge when it comes to tellin... More for Virgo http://t.co/FgrFXXBeu2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PlatformExpos: #Gaming #platform2013 the showcase event for platform in the UK. Be a part of platform and help build a new super cluste…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I think the norther/city indie bands are cool(like the ones in nick and Norah) And their artwork Is something I'll start Incorporating that
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I miss listening to indie music ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Some more indie stuffs for @ColdBlackKitty #nowplaying  fire - kasabian, now bring it I'm on fire or just incredibly hot lmao
</tweet>
<tweet>
	shiiit this indie playlist is awesome as fuck
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why do people feel the need to be indie? You seriously look stupid
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Falling asleep to indie and classical.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I wish there was an 'indie guitar band' A Level
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Acorok: Happy Birthday to epic action ? adventure ? fantasy ? magic ? romance ? The Destiny of Dragons: The Book of Wrath,... http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Indie 100. It's getting close! Are you ready for 100 songs in 100 hours?! Thanks again to all who entered and... http://t.co/sZfbFzi0Mi
</tweet>
