<tweet>
	Katy Perry song, California girls music video doesn't make sense. It should be more beachy instead of candy. Lmfao ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I think people think Im insane because when I listen to my music in public I lip sing and being on my own it looks like Im talking to myself
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@YLA_Music thank you for following meee?xD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@YLA_Music thanks for following me !! I love your New sang $$$ex !! By the way I'm vanessa hudgens look alike ^^ <3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Music_Dreamers @Zaannnnn  KR go hong her uh. Then you can teach her. (Y)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@50cent bro how to get my music to you,, hit me asap
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HeartCapricorn: A #Capricorn's best creativity comes when we are listening to music relaxing.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ok, I'm not a TI hater. I love his music and shit, but this is a made for TV "non-reality" show. We'd never know how he truly rolls. I'm JS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ItsEscapism: I dont like that people only think Music Great when they think MJ.He was more attached to his humanitarian side of helping…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@dlawrence_music I'm glad I don't have to find my key...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Any Music promoters for Malaysia here?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KattWillliams: Smoking weed is illegal... but then again, so is most of the music on your iPod. ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Study music is like the best thing on earth!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Imagine this...sounds of a fountain..children play from far...music...soft sofa big glass of banana shakes oranges dates...yeh still hungry
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@MGKateecaywood: *waits for them to start subtweeting Steph*”grabs music food and patiently waits
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I wish I could make music!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I listen to dope music.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Eliseo Way III hopeless hearts # real music http://t.co/BXIed7efQn
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My phone had crap taste in music this morning!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Skinnywhore84 thanks girl! He has the same bad haircut as the guys I find very sexual in a few edm music videos hahahahahahaha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	On the inside I'm a little gay fairy dancing to disco music
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Trey_G11: Music gets me through so much stuff
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PatrickStump: @beliebsforevs Fair enough. Unnecessary to tell me but I'm happy you have music you can attach to. Have a good one!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DaniellePaynex: Old music is so much better than new music
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tried listening to music to fall asleep to...didn't work.  Might as well go back to studying until I get tired again
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Need some ideas for new music ...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RickDaRula12: A shower without music, just not the same!?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i liked to listen to their music, now that im a selenator, i have to say that i have a really big obsession with selena , like i cant live +
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Damn near if you have music notes tatted your basic too unless your in the music industry
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iTweetFacts: Technically, music becomes medication in terms of insomnia prevention. An hour of music each day relieves insomnia by 70%.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@PerlaGeeMoreno You got some good music taste. :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	've been recently asked about places to stay in london, shop in paris, and music to listen to à la @marilynmanson. feeling like @google
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I really, really, really like listening to music.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@imyopushaaaa the opportunity for music to be heard... I can't refuse, I'm following!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Its bad enough that I'm watching the word network lol high!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iTweetFacts: Technically, music becomes medication in terms of insomnia prevention. An hour of music each day relieves insomnia by 70%.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CHOOSETATTOO I want to go to #TattooAvicii with @keeshiaohh  @ninyuhgee @regbagtas @fatmilley cause he made me realize the beauty of music?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mychonny: red jumpsuit apparatus, all time low, PATD haha music I listened to in high school
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @biskuatt: RT @dailyteenwords: Music is my bestfriend, it knows what to say to make me all okay."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Jordy_sull_69: Its so tempting to sing when listening to music on the bus
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A great George Benson track, How Do You Keep the Music Playing, playing now on Jazz FM's Red Room
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RealSONEindo: And Music Video of "LOVE&GIRLS" to be included in place of "BEEP&BEEP" in the limited edition. For now, they don't mentio…
</tweet>
