<tweet>
	@zacpozin Truly. I even began a screenplay for a high school jukebox musical, á la Moulin Mamma Mia Rouge
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JustFTIsland: [INFO] Minhwan is casted in the musical "Goong" which will be shown from  July 5-21. Minhwan is scheduled to perform from…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	So Cristin Milioti? Star of Once the Musical? Not a bad choice indeed. #wemetthemother
</tweet>
<tweet>
	SPECIAL PRICE for children aged 12 & under! ONLY £5 to watch High School Musical this Saturday 2pm Bishop of Llandaff High School #cardiff
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@acetobacters u mean highschool musical one day theyre gonna start singing "WHAT TIME IS IT? SUMMER TIME"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@cupKAEke She has a Grammy award for Best Musical Theater Album, so she got in bec of the bass player part? :))
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Musical.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Preparations are well underway for Fulham's next contest at the French Open! It was all musical chairs last night... http://t.co/jMGjdqBiz7
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Gimme Your Favorite Song Right Now Tryna Expand My Musical Library
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TristanGarner: Ok guys, this new Daft Punk album is a truly masterpiece. A  musical journey into space disco & retro funk filled with f…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HongKisBiased: [INFO] Minhwan is casted in the musical "Goong" which will be shown from  July 5-21. Minhwan is scheduled to perform fro…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@oxfordtimes @OxfordshireLife Free musical comedy gig @thekillingworth  this Sunday 8pm Spandex Ballet http://t.co/XvLZyaVK08
</tweet>
<tweet>
	To buy tickets to see High School Musical jr at Bishop of Llandaff High School #cardiff this Saturday 2pm or 7pm see http://t.co/UuW1jT747M
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SteveStfler: I bet Rosa Parks killed it in musical chairs.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Me and @Conniekk are like musical twin brothers when it comes to this EDM shit and setting the mood with it
</tweet>
<tweet>
	can someone teleport me to their musical? :(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Am I seriously crying at high school musical 3....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A talented group of local 4-16 years old from are performing HIGH SCHOOL MUSICAL jr this Saturday at Bishop of Llandaff High #cardiff #shine
</tweet>
<tweet>
	[INFO] Minhwan is casted in the musical "Goong" which will be shown from  July 5-21. Minhwan is scheduled to perform from July 17-21.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Random Access Memories" is more than an album ! It's a fuck*ng musical trip to metaphysical !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@eddychemical @Alexmetric AND WHAT'S WRONG WITH AN ANDREW LLOYD WEBER MUSICAL?! #jazzhands
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Which bellend is playing musical chairs again
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@prionadonna musical ticket price?!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thekillingworth: The Social Presents musical comedy from Spandex Ballet this Sunday from 8pm! Not for the faint hearted!! http://t.co/M…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@amycatherineann FIGHT DA WHITEY! Totes need to do it again soon! 
MUSICAL NIGHT!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Only Primary School musical Kids in black Schools will ever know of or Do is "Sarafina!"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My musical taste honestly makes zero sense
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A raunchy musical comedy about a libertine transvestite gardener from outer space - The Rockery Horticulture Picture Show.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @NickSantino: The only music I've listened to the last few days has been Peter Bradley Adams and One Direction. Musical diversity at it'…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@CeriSian did you ever see 'cov market: the musical?'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@stevenRusel Thanks for blessing us with great musical history!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HongKisBiased: [INFO] Minhwan is casted in the musical "Goong" which will be shown from  July 5-21. Minhwan is scheduled to perform fro…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BibleBrat She seems so interesting, do you know if she's recording a new album or taking a break from the musical industry?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Premier League musical chairs? Looks like it with all the coaches and players reshuffling...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	High School Musical 3 - Can I Have This Dance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HongKisBiased: [INFO] Minhwan is casted in the musical "Goong" which will be shown from  July 5-21. Minhwan is scheduled to perform fro…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Phew! No one's ashamed of me that I'm missing the 1st night of the festive season! Well it's for the sake of a musical after all #Eurovision
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Whilst music appreciation is subjective, Coldplay don't exactly push the adventurous musical envelope http://t.co/phvoxqcQ58
</tweet>
<tweet>
	op school net musical
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HongKisBiased: [INFO] Minhwan is casted in the musical "Goong" which will be shown from  July 5-21. Minhwan is scheduled to perform fro…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watch Amazing Musical Movie ~Aashiqui 2~ 2013 & Listen ¤ All these New Upcoming YJHD Movie Songs¤ Awesome, Romantic,Inspiring.............
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HongKisBiased: [INFO] Minhwan is casted in the musical "Goong" which will be shown from  July 5-21. Minhwan is scheduled to perform fro…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's our Musical directors Dave birthday today. Everyone say happy birthday to Dave.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SmokeyComedyy: I hate when I'm singing a song and someone joins in... I'm like "Bitch, this isn't high school musical"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @UnOriginal_Adri: #AddInThatPussyBehindAMovieTitle High School Musical In That Pussy! We're all in this together lookin ass!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching my favorite musical at this time, talking to a nice guy & eating chips ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Support our NUS BBA alumni Meryl Joan Lee (Class of 2011) as she displays her vocal and musical talent on... http://t.co/8pdNFXrGJJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JeTaimeThugg: High school musical used to upset me so much. I couldn't understand how EVERYBODY MAGICALLY KNEW ALL THESE SONGS AND , AL…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HongKisBiased: [INFO] Minhwan is casted in the musical "Goong" which will be shown from  July 5-21. Minhwan is scheduled to perform fro…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	when in doubt listen to high school musical
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PointlessBlogTv: I wish my life was a musical
</tweet>
<tweet>
	High school musical used to upset me so much. I couldn't understand how EVERYBODY MAGICALLY KNEW ALL THESE SONGS AND , ALL STARTED ON TIME!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If your new single doesn't have physically played musical instrm. (Stringed, horns, keys, or at least drums) keep it to yourself!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HongKisBiased: [INFO] Minhwan is casted in the musical "Goong" which will be shown from  July 5-21. Minhwan is scheduled to perform fro…
</tweet>
