<tweet>
	. @yousefg_ is my musical spirit animal
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Bethan_Louise_P: One Direction irritate me they have no original musical talent theyre just the same bland old boy band, nothing origin…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	High school musical luisteren met sinem
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'Holocene' ladies & gents. You're welcome to the bands brand of musical genius, in my mind they're harmonic bandits. **Sips brandy**
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Bombergrl2000 @jrgrimaJulie prepare your ears for a musical gift. The Radio and Left My Heart in NYC are smash hits in my opinion.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	High school was nothing like high school musical ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	bradley nowell was seriously a musical genius. 
#sublime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Like a play. Or musical. Or what eves.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@lingling1307 Yes!! :D Really hope he can do a musical!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Countdown is on for another musical feast @debbie_green19 and @shell_cornwell
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Been introduced to a musical wonder by @its_sycho...we love James Blake?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If you don't like Vampire Weekend....I can't talk you anymore. No joke, you need to appreciate their musical talent and amazingness.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Photo: vintageblackglamour: Happy Birthday to ya Stevie Wonder!!! My favorite musical genius was born 63... http://t.co/avOeRDBbaL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VISHALFASE: PM's and Sonia's relationship is perfect - congress,is it relationship counselling? We want order,not relationships! @Music…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@jaxxxxx58 good thanks Jackie. Doing a new musical at the Arts Theatre this summer, be lovely to see you there. Thanks for your support x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Bethan_Louise_P: One Direction irritate me they have no original musical talent theyre just the same bland old boy band, nothing origin…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Started up this week's #MadMen. That musical chairs scene was poetry in motion. Pete Campbell is such a weasel.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dario Marinelli's indeed a musical genius!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Once The Musical London: One of the remarkable West End venues, Phoenix Theatre is located in… http://t.co/gncQj8nGts
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JanelleMonae: Screaming H A P P Y B I R T h D AY to my musical mentor and spiritual counselor: S T E V I E. WONDER. ?You ha … http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	One Direction irritate me they have no original musical talent theyre just the same bland old boy band, nothing original
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Usher is a musical genius.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Check out this upcoming #Vegas event | 'Billy Elliot the Musical' -- 05/14/13 at Smith Center for the Performing Arts ...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @josiahwise8 RT @PeppermintPatee Check out Zahara from South Africa. She’s quite a musical sensation.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ukiss_intl Yeah! I really hope I can watch this musical show..double casting..wow..ganbatte kudasai vinSoo..<3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@julieplec is it bad that #wildcat made me think of high school musical?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The role of musical training in emergent and event-based timing | #Neuroscience #Music –  http://t.co/RIPcanqbjD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@emclarks i only know one. anthony stewart head.uther from merlin among other sort-of famous roles.he's also in this musical which i ADORE.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	PM's and Sonia's relationship is perfect - congress,is it relationship counselling? We want order,not relationships! @Musical_Patriot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Musical Review Hour #2: Random Access Memories - Daft Punk, much better when played loudly and taken with a pinch of patience. #goodtunes
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I get so bored when I'm ill I find myself watching high school musical 3... Sad life
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TheDoperPeddler Sounds a lot better than watching a musical
</tweet>
<tweet>
	UKISS_intl: [The Memory 2013 musical] Any changes to Hoon's performance schedule will be posted on the U-KISS fancafe. Please take note!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That woman's chromosomes are musical notes! It makes no sense the stuff she does.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	ICIT Spring Concert this Weds, May 15th @ 8pm in Winnifed Smith Hall @UCIrvine @CTSA_UCIrvine! Come for a musical paradigm shattering time!
</tweet>
