<tweet>
	RT @Barbs6794: I need to put some music on
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@zabiatko13 you're more than welcome hun, you know! And thanks :* x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NBCTheVoice if I can't listen 2 the music on our Harley, I won't vote. Country, hip hop or wtevr @shakira @blakeshelton @adamlevine @Usher
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How have I only just found out it's Eurovison on Saturday! Fave music event of the year.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	music is my savoir.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	will get your music played on @SOWESTRIGHTNOW will bang your single 4 times to hundreds of hip hop fans 4 25$ text 4 details 562-208-4455 ,
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Even the soothing voice of #BillieHoliday can't help me go to sleep #pandora #insomnia #music #sleepy… http://t.co/1zznUuf9vL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i must be getting old because i hate all music i see on tv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm here at @KBCS hosting SLOW DIVE RADIO from 1-3 AM PST, right now! Tune in on 91.3 fm Seattle or http://t.co/wQrFE8y9aI! :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I be studying to music like Curren$y ft Dom Kennedy - Hennessy Beach , makes me want to go to just relax and k.o though lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	was just paid two litres of diet coke for my answers to my music textbook from last year
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @1dandjbjanoily: I love them but why are they always in LA? They say they're not a boy band but they're in LA making music. #NotABoyBand…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thinkin back on dem days me, busta , dre & jnice stayed in the studio ... It was nothing but music
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Modern rock legends The Cure are booked to headline the Lollapalooza music festival for the first time, alongside Mumford and Sons, organ..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Jonas brothers have a twerk team in their Pom poms music video.... Oh.?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ChooseTattoo I want to go to #TattooAvicii w/my friends&sis toget goin' and join AVICII for his concert here! We all love music and party!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Music gives a soul to the universe, wings to the mind, flight to the imagination
and life to everything." 
— Plato
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Presley_Radio Guy u can now download music by your favorite artist straight to your phone at  http://t.co/0hgtZ4SS3k absolutely at no cost
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mai Atafo Released A Song Ke! So Desigining Don Tire Am, Na To Entire Music Industry Now? Kai!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mike i Joe o Music for Relief - Linkin Park .pl http://t.co/rmb1TRS6oG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And, I may be wrong, but I'm pretty sure the hold music at City today is an instrumental of 'Not 19 Forever', someone taking the piss.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @xx13z: Can u Please help out a brother with his music and life struggles and retweet http://t.co/F5gbDHZPXA
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Don't miss out on this iTunes Giveaway! WIN a SIGNED #HeartAttack POSTER from #DemiLovato ! Join Now >> http://t.co/8MGJf7eyxk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Taylor swift is my everything. Without her music. I am dead. Real shit.....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @noko82: @robbiewilliams get in there!! Nice to see @grimmers getting knocked down a peg or two! http://t.co/Vo6DL4mmdX via @YahooOmgUK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	CORNETTO SUMMER MUSIC Presents CARLY RAE JEPSEN Live In Jakarta | Mon, 27 May 2013 at Tennis Indoor Senayan | Promoted by @Indikapro
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @supercw: more ppl saying they like the music than making requests la guy bought me shot n loved viceroy aussie gave $ for a cd even tho…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	finished my project for asb yaay i like it :) think i did good ^-^ just putting all this music on my itunes then knocking out
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NathanTheWanted The most favorite music is yours, waiting unusual show
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BITEMENUMB: The vibes I get from certain music >>>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i just want line-ups of music festivals to come out so i can make decisions on where to go god dammit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GlamGeekG: Artists interested in being featured on Haute Chicago please send music in mp3 format to music@hautechicago.com
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MetalB___666 @simonverrill1 @slika68 Sitting on bus home music for sure :) x #BeastKnowsBest
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @dhanushkraja: Hey guys we have decided to launch our own music label soon under the name "wunderbar studio". Will make an official anno…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mpotoae: At least music never sleeps ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Now playing Nobody Compares by One Direction x #music #yay http://t.co/OIHmD8ALXI #lagu
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@KREAYSHAWN: Music soothes the savage beast.” @Sav_Noir
</tweet>
