<tweet>
	Hendra virus still mystery for scientists but not Mark Purdey  http://t.co/XxMvg5jObE via @smh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @aku_jujur: The past is history the future is a mystery  this moment you have now is a gift :) #AJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love that The Fear of Things to Come hit #16 on Amazon Best Sellers Top 100 Free ebooks in Suspense! #Thriller #Crime http://t.co/CuI7bJoUwF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. And Today? Today is a gift. That's why we call it the present.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RebeccaCannon_ did you get over the mystery passport or is me identity being stolen wouldnt blame them ! #IMMASSO
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Martina_Smyth To the nation’s best kept mystery; Your factual age
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm just one entity. 
I'm a mystery. 
I'm a different breed.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love is never planned it always just happens out of nowhere. Thats what makes it so special. You are the detective and love is a mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Having faults is only half the mystery being flawless is only half the fault being mysterious is only half the wonder of my flawless fault!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @theycallmejerry: http://t.co/w3C9aDLSty a link full of mystery. .... So that was a lie but come on, vote for our idol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kahlil Gibran~ When you have solved all the mysteries of life you long for death for it is but another mystery of life.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bestseller MONEY LAND is now available on Nook! http://t.co/Jo4uJJ7Rht Get your fix with the second James Pruett Mystery.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HarveyHough: Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @brigithaangelia: RT @ohteenquotes Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How I made it out the door and on the bus in time is a mystery #iamgod
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love is more than mystery, and romance can survive intimacy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT"@ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	hunting underwater is such a pain, both because of the controls and my lack of depth perception. #MH3U
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm up late watching a murder mystery show.  #wrongwithme
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love comes,love goes,like a journey.Love is like that, full of mystery, full of mischief
</tweet>
<tweet>
	like, i first noticed it when i used to WoW. when i'm underwater in a game, i just cannot tell how near or far away anything is.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is a history, tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift, that's why we call it the present. - SNSD,Sunny.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ahujinator: The last 24 hours without Facebook have given me an unexpected sense of relief. Life suddenly regained its natural level of…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NiallOfficial a mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	does anyone else have a lot of trouble judging distance underwater in video games?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @brigithaangelia: RT @ohteenquotes Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ohteenquotes Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. That's why we call it present. ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm attracted to the mystery.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oh You know you know you know I'd never ask you to change, if perfects what your searching for then just stay the same .xx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	the time will tell the unspeakable truth and the great mystery of fate, but It's depend on us..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TwiSagaQuotes: Theres nothing like an unsolved mystery to keep you up at night. -Bella
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thank you to the mystery person who just ordered some good food to our room. ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is history, tomorrow's a mystery. I can see you lookin' back at me, keep your eyes on me, baby, keep your eyes on me~~ #nowplaying
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#PLL Pretty Little Liars Season 4 Mystery: Who is the Woman in the Black Veil?: Oh Pretty Little Liars. Our be... http://t.co/9QdxJJN9dU
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Another mystery of the miraculous poster: Akpabio denies interest in the Presidency http://t.co/XsMk2woKfO"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. That's why it's called the present.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	'What do you think is a good job fit for me?' 'Mystery shopping?'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	there's mystery milk in the fridge and I think I'm gonna risk it
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TwiSagaQuotes: Theres nothing like an unsolved mystery to keep you up at night. -Bella
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@PME2013 @onawintersnight Boys are always a mystery. Especially when they aren't. *looks sage*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a
mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Evolution is a mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Abstraction is mystery tamed, but not necessarily vanquished.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video from @edmondchee http://t.co/qQeoPRlnKR The Mystery of Time & Space
</tweet>
<tweet>
	THE MYSTERY ADMINS ARE SO STRICT O.O
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Debating whether to text the mystery man who left his number or not ugh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mystery Aircraft Frightens Quincy Residents « CBS Boston http://t.co/DKxWX2oTUL  Okay, this is super creepy.
A bad omen, I believe.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	IM A MYSTERY. PHANTOM OF THE OPERA TYPE. YOULL LOVE ME WITH MY MASK OFF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The mystery of New York's eternal flame: Scientists unsure exactly where the gas produced to keep... http://t.co/oToJSdRCJS via @MailOnline
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iFafaEiger: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MichaelJMcCann1: Can Detective Karen Stainer stay calm in a country club that bans women? The Fregoli Delusion http://t.co/bSw5bmlJEH #…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Disappointed Strong Belwas isn't in the show. He was always fun. Makes Yunkai a mystery though, so YAY! @LMHPhotog
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Louis_Tomlinson: Have to say a huge thank you to everyone @yiannimize for making mine and @zaynmalik 's mystery machine haha !!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@chilldogge thats the mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Day Four, 3am: playing Pokémon Mystery Dungeon and eating Mr. Noodles. I'm such a weeaboo right now; I can hardly stand it! :p
</tweet>
