<tweet>
	RT @DanGlover1: When I lose my direction I look up to the sky. The Mystery: Zen Stories by Dan Glover via @amazon http://t.co/utCXqePmk0
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's day 4 of the magical mystery tour of university visits today for @WhichuniUK and it's brought us to #Oxford! Plenty of updates to come!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lucid's Jacob Jones and the Bigfoot Mystery unravels on Vita, iOS this week http://t.co/Cl3nkLt8Q0 #games
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MollyQuinn93: Loved the mystery in this episode. 
@AndrewWMarlowe is perfection.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How Well Traveled Are You? http://t.co/ifqZr04Bhh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SNSD_FamilyRP: ”Yesterday is a history, tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift, that’s why we call it the present.” – Sunny Lee
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @aku_jujur: The past is history the future is a mystery  this moment you have now is a gift :) #AJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have just reached new 7 level in Mystery Manor! Be my guest! http://t.co/NxIPuat99j #iphone #iphonegames #gameinsight
</tweet>
<tweet>
	”Yesterday is a history, tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift, that’s why we call it the present.” – Sunny Lee
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@indieBerries and some mystery people STILL put flowers on her coffin area in the chapel. It's awesome.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"yesterday is a memory, tomorrow is a mystery and today is a gift, that's why it is called the present"--The Buddha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Jacob Jones and The Mystery Bigfoot hits the US PS Store today, should be here in EU tomorrow. Our review at 14.00pm today @LucidGamesLtd
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love is like a mystery and no one will ever be able to understand or explain it fully.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Share the mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TayMichelle94: What is my purpose on this earth? A mystery..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@KFMarcella hahah the mystery of the disappearing 4th guest hahah we shud get bk at her ... like drink her moet! haha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@TayMichelle94: What is my purpose on this earth? A mystery..” Swear i was jus asking somebody this smh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	thank you :)
ya like Andrew said you can get them from mystery chests from either solo or (@YouTube http://t.co/M9hYhYio1J)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Louis_Tomlinson: Have to say a huge thank you to everyone @yiannimize for making mine and @zaynmalik 's mystery machine haha !!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is a history, Today is a gift, Tomorrow is a mystery.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @itsmovies: "Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. But today is a gift. That’s why its called the present." - Kung Fu Panda
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@LowkeyFluffZz hmmm. Girl with a mystery.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes: Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“It’s a mystery of human chemistry and I don’t understand it, some people, as far as their senses are concerned, just feel like home.”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You're the kind of mystery I wouldn't mind spending the rest of my life trying to unravel.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ePrintedBooks: @ChrisPetersenTX Fresh off the ePress! U R published in the headlines of "ePrintedBooks Mystery Thrillers"  http://t.co/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	*"Yesterday Is History And Tomorrow Is A Mystery !!"*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	There are things I can do that you can't but if you come and have a open mind your ready too embrace the mystery ... http://t.co/RRhUHnS9Ka
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mystery shows are a trap.
Because I can't stop watching until I know who the fuck did it..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	yesterday is history tomorrow a mystery but today is a gift that's why they call it a present #RealTalk #TrulyGifted #GiftedENT #Knowledge
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The mystery of New York's eternal flame: Scientists unsure exactly where the gas produced to keep... http://t.co/kiSmut0jDX via @MailOnline
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Franschhoek_SA: Did you miss out on the first Franschhoek Mystery Weekend? Well here’s the good news! Join us over the weekend of... ht…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ahhhh. Tea break. Leave my desk for ten mins and come back to a pile of paperwork.  Who's giving me all of this. #mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ChrisPetersenTX: ENDLESS SUMMER-A summer vacation goes horribly wrong - A ghost story, a mystery-tear jerker ending. http://t.co/tRex1R…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RictorVeznov Mystery Dungeon : Gates to Infinity
</tweet>
<tweet>
	you,me and all that things and memories we shared are all mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RoboMumBlog great idea, now how to solve the mystery of the missing pens. Especially when I brought them a few hrs ago
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GillianJacobs: New game show: How'd you get that bruise? 

I'm quizzed about various mystery bruises & if I guess correctly win Reese's…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TroyBouwens: And you light me up, when you ring my bell.
You're a mystery, you're from outer space,
You're every minute of my everyday.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The name of the Doctor revealed this saturday?! :O!!! Noooo! This is as bad as calling the Prince of Persia "Dastan". Wheres the mystery?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You're grace, still amazes me. Your love, still a mystery.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @samanthajamison: #VOL4 A LETHAL TIME
“Interference could be lethal”
I got right up in his face, hissing,
“Don’t push me,
I’m hormonal”
…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ill trade a little peace for some suspense. And ill let it fall wherever it will take me, I love a mystery in the making
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have just reached new 6 level in Mystery Manor! Be my guest! http://t.co/NxIPuat99j #iphone #iphonegames #gameinsight
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is HISTORY
Tomorrow is a MYSTERY 
and today is ANOTHER DAY :D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I look so innocent on my pictures which makes it a mystery knowing my personality awe
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And you light me up, when you ring my bell.
You're a mystery, you're from outer space,
You're every minute of my everyday.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes
Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a
mystery. Today is a gift. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@IselfLinda Apparently Nucho is in some shit again. Whats he done this time around, is still a mystery.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	TwinFX (SA) has always been shrouded in mystery, time for you to know who and what we are all about.

Comments... http://t.co/m1lHSbWNwt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hey John... I agree with Michelle - go as yourself! You've got the best retro look I've seen! :-) Now all joking aside... the Mystery...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ImranKhanPTI..It is far beyond our thoughts how we loose..We were the winners till 3pm. We lost after 6pm..Mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yesterday is history, tomorrow's a mystery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pregnancy Weight Gain - The Mystery Solved http://t.co/DPiiFAmERW
</tweet>
