<tweet>
	RT @newbeverly: We've got a John Dahl neo-noir double bill of RED ROCK WEST + KILL ME AGAIN tomorrow (5/14) w/ John Dahl scheduled to appea…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @newbeverly: We've got a John Dahl neo-noir double bill of RED ROCK WEST + KILL ME AGAIN tomorrow (5/14) w/ John Dahl scheduled to appea…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @newbeverly: We've got a John Dahl neo-noir double bill of RED ROCK WEST + KILL ME AGAIN tomorrow (5/14) w/ John Dahl scheduled to appea…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @newbeverly: We've got a John Dahl neo-noir double bill of RED ROCK WEST + KILL ME AGAIN tomorrow (5/14) w/ John Dahl scheduled to appea…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We've got a John Dahl neo-noir double bill of RED ROCK WEST + KILL ME AGAIN tomorrow (5/14) w/ John Dahl scheduled to appear IN PERSON!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	or is it neo-noir? either way...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I will seriously sleep with whoever I have to sleep with in order to get on the writing team for Mike Tyson's Neo Noir Pigeon show.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@uhcakip Casablanca, 12 Angry Men, White Heat, Strangers on a Train. En een paar neo noir films, The French Connection, Serpico o.a.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SquidRash Love it. Kind of jazzy neo-noir comedy with an amazing soundtrack.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CHarrisESPN: Oh, and hey, if you've enjoyed the neo-noir blog at all, maybe check out my novel, The Big Clear? http://t.co/YEe0vRmyod
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KcEazyworld: Review: DEAD MAN DOWN, a slow neo-noir thriller that really makes audience wants to lay down. http://t.co/fNIV5bw6AP #movi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Review: DEAD MAN DOWN, a slow neo-noir thriller that really makes audience wants to lay down. http://t.co/fNIV5bw6AP #movietwit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@spookynico Are you a neo-noir fan? Drive is fantastic.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Huge thanks to @noirwhale for the great review of my writing and @NobregaPaul 's voice talents!  Cheggit:  http://t.co/u1x896JVJx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oh, and hey, if you've enjoyed the neo-noir blog at all, maybe check out my novel, The Big Clear? http://t.co/YEe0vRmyod
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Tawag Ng Kallag" (Ghost Calling) is a neo-noir ethnic music that I ominously wrote and composed a month before my... http://t.co/umjYY8ddzz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I want Christopher Nolan to get the next crack at Gatsby.  I want a gritty neo-noir take on it....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Zodiac highly underestimated. One of the best neo-noir films, by far.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	so glad this white-trash neo-noir ryan gosling movie place beyond the pines ended with a bon iver song jesus christ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#BazLurhmannPresents THE MALTESE FALCON as a neo-noir set in the grimy underbelly of New York, with a real eagle. D-Box enabled.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @wickerkat: Get your neo-noir short stories ready. Dark House Press will open our doors for the Exigencies anthology on June... http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @wickerkat: Get your neo-noir short stories ready. Dark House Press will open our doors for the Exigencies anthology on June... http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @wickerkat: Get your neo-noir short stories ready. Dark House Press will open our doors for the Exigencies anthology on June... http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Get your neo-noir short stories ready. Dark House Press will open our doors for the Exigencies anthology on June... http://t.co/09kwK5fTLU
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Royal Opera House's neo-noir mural depicting animal rights
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@WadjetEyeGames Oh wow! That’s exciting. I haven’t been this captivated by an adventure game for ages! Love the neo-noir/cyberpunk vibe.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wtf? Why do all the good characters die? Oh right I'm watching a neo-noir. Everyone's fucked.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I had forgotten how intense the beginning of this movie is. And those 80's neo-noir opening titles!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @darkhousepress: DHP is a new imprint of @CurbsidePress, @wickerkat as Editor-in-Chief. We will publish neo-noir, speculative fiction...
</tweet>
