<tweet>
	the ghost of you- my chemical romance <3
goodnight bastards///
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A simple girl transforms into an extraordinary life http://t.co/QEDO6YUDnn @LoriARamsey #samplesaturday #romance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@itsJulia_Montes: READ: Will Enchong Dee and Julia Montes give romance a second chance? http://t.co/cJOCQQwevU …"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@_eilatanXo I suck at romance come over tomorrow ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Photoset: silvermoon424: THE MIRACLE ROMANCE THAT TRANSCENDS TIME AND SPACE, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.  http://t.co/cbTZPKmG6Y
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bad Romance *baila*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	my chemical romance put me in such a good in the morning
</tweet>
<tweet>
	romance de amour
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Scorpio likes to be the more domineering partner which the flexible Gemini finds easy. http://t.co/ZbZJjzcEjl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BenSaadna @djcharlottes I'm not really sure if there's a show for that... Like comedy, drama, romance? Can I get a genre lawl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lady Brianne Of taph vs Sir Jamie Lannister the Kingslayer 

Budding Romance
#GameOfthRoNes
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I always do your favors thats romance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love is more than mystery, and romance can survive intimacy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I told my older brother My Chemical Romance broke up in March and he laughed. Thanks for the sympathy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@iQuoteGreys: Meredith: The romance will fade, things will happen, people will change, love will die... but maybe not today. #greysanatomy"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Nice people dating enjoy a groovy kind of love! If you are fed up with being single - join and take the first step to romance. #bizitalk
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In Need of Romance. New kpop movie. Yahooo!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ThisIsCrewe: CREWE HOROSCOPE: Taurus - You'll find romance on Gresty Rd with a beautiful stranger wearing a high vis & smelling of flap…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TScpCancer: Cancer and Scorpio are two of the most well-matched signs of the zodiac. http://t.co/ToEu4aAspf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WulanMathers: before you judge My Chemical Romance make sure if you already listen to all their songs and knows the meaning behind thei…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TScpCapricorn: Capricorn teaches Sagittarius how to be more practical minded and responsible. http://t.co/HWmYoU36v4
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Finally saw True Romance last night. Wonderful film #mustseefilms
</tweet>
<tweet>
	before you judge My Chemical Romance make sure if you already listen to all their songs and knows the meaning behind their songs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Putting in headphones to avoid peoples  bullshit at work .. ?
And listen to music ?
To romance your heart ???

#work #my.status.now
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Can you imagine no love, no first dance, or no freeze dried romance? ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	alert: a wild @ianjay has farted at me as revenge for my hummus-breath. this shoujo romance is OVER
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i ship larry as a bromance, but elounor as a romance ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @coreti_iza_cunt: My Chemical Romance fans will get this http://t.co/Ly2bZsZzJt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Romance between an Egyptian Muslim and a Christian http://t.co/dEfs7AfOOK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Romance between an Egyptian Muslim and a Christian http://t.co/j0TqJzlbFV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My chemical romance in the morning
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I guess I never experienced romance lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Push_Mina: Will Enchong Dee and Julia Montes give romance a second chance? http://t.co/wQb9MnuyuM …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Push_Mina: Will Enchong Dee and Julia Montes give romance a second chance? http://t.co/PVBuUAtpFd
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How cruel life was to steal this man from her #kindle #MMA #Romance  http://t.co/H46YfFibHG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@mercurialblonde precious. now i want a romance comic done by you
</tweet>
<tweet>
	READ: Will Enchong Dee and Julia Montes give romance a second chance? http://t.co/9Ipjpcp9TO …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@Push_Mina: Will Enchong Dee and Julia Montes give romance a second chance? http://t.co/9Ipjpcp9TO …"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I've been romance but its been a long time & I mean #DAMN Mr. Jackson did that! #Unexpected night swim, facial & dinner, wine #allsmiles
</tweet>
<tweet>
	He said I twisted my ankle so kissed my ankle now that's romance lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	? I am listening to MCR - Cemetery Drive by My Chemical Romance #MP3MusicDownloader 

I MISS THIS SONGGG~~~
</tweet>
