<tweet>
	RT @caybaybay11: "But at the end of the day he's a GDI, and that makes the romance impossible"- @shishimariee
</tweet>
<tweet>
	She's shaking in the car with a gun in her hand. Falling over love and sweet romance.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"But at the end of the day he's a GDI, and that makes the romance impossible"- @shishimariee
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@linnbhalton writes stories about love with a physic touch! Love, life & beyond, but it's always about the romance! http://t.co/fH3gvxNURz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	B'munich and gotze romance is so pathetic...let him play!!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love is when u taKe away the feelings passion and romance in the relationship and find out u still care for dat person
</tweet>
<tweet>
	can someone send me some good short stories?? particularly in the romance genre?? need inspiration for my creative writing exam
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@EatTweetBlog Mood for touching romance - Ashiquie 2.
Mood to laugh your ass off - Go Goa Gone
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@RevealMag: Rita Ora & Calvin Harris confirm romance? Seen holding hands on night out. New pictures, http://t.co/ZJVdZo3M3m” ? ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Snippet Sunday - Feast of Candles 99 cent contemporary romance  http://t.co/g5sBJfdwIe via @StephBurkhart
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TedOfficialPage: Smart man + smart woman = romance

Smart man + dumb woman = affair

Dumb man + smart woman = marriage

Dumb man + dumb…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	There may be trouble ahead
But while there's moonlight and music, and love and romance
Let's face the music and dance #NatKingCole
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Jealousy in romance is lyk salt,4 little cn enhance d flavour,bt 2 much cn spoil d pleasure n unda certain circumstances,cn b ife threatenin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That's not just friendship, that's romance too. You like music we can dance to.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You and me could write a bad romance...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nikolePar: Graded B by the Cinema Evaluation Board! #Bromance My Brother's Romance showing na showing na bukas!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sometimes I need that romance/ Sometimes I need that pole dance/
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“Romance is the glamour which turns the dust of everyday life into a golden haze.” #bot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Killllakev: Live the full life of the mind, exhilarated by new ideas, intoxicated by the romance of the unusual~
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Imma pimp by blood not relation
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Push_Mina: Will Enchong Dee and Julia Montes give romance a second chance? http://t.co/PVBuUAtpFd
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Women who are romance novel readers are reported to make love 74% more often with their partners than women who do not read romance novels
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Girls & Romance Novels - http://t.co/wHc3mFpLyZ - We've all seen the covers—a couple, locked in a passionate embrace, surrounded by...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@allalleysway ..i love you...and always will...when you get off...come over ..i wanna romance you
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@taimoorkhan99  Thanks for following, but to me, politics should be "commitment" for social justice & equality rather than "romance".
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @krc_castro: I hit it , I hit it , I hit it , I hit it , I hit it , I hit it first.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@robertortegajr CONGRATS PO SIR FRED.,.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SteezyStazzay: sometimes I need that romance, sometimes I need that pole dance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How wonderful wonder is.
Ancient things make it up a romance.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @__AsiaP__: To love one's self is a lifetime romance.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Having to play a My Chemical Romance on piano for my music performance upsets me :c
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How wonderful wonder is.
Ancient things make it up a romance.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Readers are saying that they can't put HEART LIKE AN OCEAN down. http://t.co/bGxXyqiJ3P #historical #romance #amreading @chrissteen1991
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ChrisPetersenTX: ENDLESS SUMMER-A summer vacation goes horribly wrong - A ghost story, a mystery-tear jerker ending. http://t.co/tRex1R…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @instyle_UK: WATCH: The cast of the Great Gatsby talk romance and film magic http://t.co/NNbiEuMci8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@waeyeon @thatssosoo @amberoppar @hyohomie love rain/t3h tbh. lets not even talk about fashion king and wild romance.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @JoyceDeBacco: Take a vacation to the #PoconoMountains and stay at SERENDIPITY HOUSE for #Romance & friends who become like #family. htt…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	my eyes were opened wide to our sweet romance and, Wallahi, she is perfect...did I mention that yet? ?Mamaa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rita Ora & Calvin Harris confirm romance? Seen holding hands on night out. New pictures, http://t.co/cqlDpP1YOs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PhilipArdagh: I discovered from yesterday's Guardian Quick Crossword that 'Cameron' is an anagram of 'romance', and felt the need to sh…
</tweet>
