<tweet>
	@InhaleSoFrench I didn't ask for science fiction Samantha lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Nah word the buns game on the east coast in our beautiful nation is fake science fiction
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WilliamShatner: Was your career choice affected by watching Star Trek?  Tell me about it.  I want to know.  MBB  http://t.co/GRYcTR6BSm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WilliamShatner: Was your career choice affected by watching Star Trek?  Tell me about it.  I want to know.  MBB  http://t.co/GRYcTR6BSm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WilliamShatner: Was your career choice affected by watching Star Trek?  Tell me about it.  I want to know.  MBB  http://t.co/GRYcTR6BSm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Off to Future's annual editors' conference. Science fiction, please try not to do anything important or interesting until I get back, ta.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Science Fiction Covers Up Science Fact. Stargates Are Real.http://t.co/JqzNxru8cJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@WilliamShatner Fair I to say I am very interested in both Science and Science fiction due to Star Trek.  Hoping to write sf  some day.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WilliamShatner: Was your career choice affected by watching Star Trek?  Tell me about it.  I want to know.  MBB  http://t.co/GRYcTR6BSm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	fantasy v. science fiction
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“The story is amazing, I finished it in under a week!” REAPER Book 2 #Horror #Scifi #Teen http://t.co/CMywwgQMxI
</tweet>
<tweet>
	George R. R. Martin wrote: "World building is part of what gives epic fantasy its appeal." The same goes for science fiction.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ItsTheDoctor: They call it Science Fiction because it's what will happen if I'm not around to save the day. #DoctorWho
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kelvin III Throop~ Isnt it interesting that the same people who laugh at science fiction listen to weather forecasts and economists
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Now, THIS is what I call science fiction! http://t.co/q2h0KThLCa via @youtube
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I Am Evangeline, new Christine Rogers film, to begin filming in June. http://t.co/WwopCVXxUI
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Essential Science Fiction Novels for Understanding the Economy - Io9 http://t.co/gWBM0QJngt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Richard Curtis does time travel! He's managed to rom-com science fiction. First trailer for @universaluk About Time: http://t.co/0GZeJkrdFi
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Science fiction is any idea that doesn't exist yet, but soon will, and it will change everything for everybody
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	... Just like in science fiction from the era...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Best Hard Science Fiction Books of all Time http://t.co/fOMQ0MXdiS via @prismatic
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Submitting two proposals for science fiction TV series. They are entitled “Evolutionary” and “Reality Squared”.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WilliamShatner: Was your career choice affected by watching Star Trek?  Tell me about it.  I want to know.  MBB  http://t.co/GRYcTR6BSm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	John Garrett Interviewed on Genesis Science Fiction Radio http://t.co/b3P9LgDUtK via @johngarrettX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Sechervalle It's reading and writing science fiction, so we read 1984 by George Orwell and random excerpts of famous sci-fi books
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WilliamShatner: Was your career choice affected by watching Star Trek?  Tell me about it.  I want to know.  MBB  http://t.co/GRYcTR6BSm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@gerribowen 5* A science fiction- romance- space opera? With dragons! It was good, very good..Flawed GodsAmazon http://t.co/jECdAXIUjT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Interesting article on the 'exhaustion' in modern science fiction: http://t.co/YDQaf5S3L6
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If you're a Christian and also a fan of science fiction, you would probably be enthralled by Ray Bradbury's short story "The Fire Balloons".
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What do you get if cross a science fiction film with a toad? Star Warts!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@EatTheMoon WHAT IS SCIENCE FICTION CLASS????? WHY DON’T WE HAVE COOL THINGS TOO? WHY WHY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Is Iron Man Science Fiction? The Military’s Most Science-Fictional Projects i.e. Exoskeleton http://t.co/y6ZWFiFaD8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Sechervalle Science Fiction professor for Science Fiction class? XD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What do you get if cross a science fiction film with a toad? Star Warts!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@EatTheMoon Wait......  You have a science-fiction professor? What is a science-fiction professor?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Science fiction spoof next in film series - NEagle - Science fiction spoof next in film seriesNEagleThe movie is a... http://t.co/cQjPhCYiTB
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Considering current internet speeds here in SA, the promise of 5G sounds like science-fiction: http://t.co/q9OTYoSKfG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That's the best kind of science fiction for tv imo
</tweet>
<tweet>
	except sci-fi RT @rippingseams: I'm killing myself by watching all these romantic comedies. ugh this is why I stick to science fiction
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Brockway_LLC: We live in a reality far more ambitious than most science fiction.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WilliamShatner: Was your career choice affected by watching Star Trek?  Tell me about it.  I want to know.  MBB  http://t.co/GRYcTR6BSm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Rosannaopph: Kelvin III Throop~ Isnt it interesting that the same people who laugh at science fiction listen to weather forecasts and e…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	S.I.N. Theory picked up for distro out of Canada thanks to our European team. Science Fiction at its best http://t.co/iu5pXMEz2p #filmmakers
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Science fiction spoof next in film series - NEagle http://t.co/uo62ZyV5ml
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Science fiction spoof next in film series - NEagle http://t.co/iYwYqfYiMJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Russian billionaire wants to create cyborgs ~ 
In science fiction, one of the most popular concepts is the cyborg... http://t.co/3kuo28Yf82
</tweet>
<tweet>
	John Carpenter Wants to Adapt 'Dead Space' - Science Fiction: If you are a fan of horror, you know the name Jo... http://t.co/pzbbh8YSjM
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Honestly I mostly watch cartoons, anime, superheroes, and anything to do with science fiction/fantasy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm killing myself by watching all these romantic comedies. ugh this is why I stick to science fiction
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WilliamShatner: Was your career choice affected by watching Star Trek?  Tell me about it.  I want to know.  MBB  http://t.co/GRYcTR6BSm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Jitterbug PR presents: The Writer’s Workshop of Science Fiction and Fantasy http://t.co/F9Ow3i5XcX via @SelahJanel
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Looking for a science fiction book?  Get ideas about what to read from a compiliation of recommendations, call number: PS374.S35 B763...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Essential Science Fiction Novels for Understanding the Economy" http://t.co/LhGN08yaPg
</tweet>
<tweet>
	http://t.co/MZLzHQsIJM Meet Aussie science fiction writer Nina D’Aleo in an interview today! From @ZucchiniBikini http://t.co/ROGh8a8k1o
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Today on the 5: I finally got around to watching a gem of 1980s science fiction, Cherry 2000. http://t.co/hRcv1WnEuN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	1963:The BBC broadcasts the first ever episode of Doctor Who which is the world's longest running science fiction drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	STAR TREK INTO DARKNESS will B next week - U ought 2 watch 1 early 1902 SCIENCE FICTION films  - A Trip 2 the Moon - http://t.co/dUvpW2paSY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WarwickADavis: Today @AnnabelleLDavis starts her GCSE exams. Her brain is full of science (hopefully not the fiction kind) for biology.…
</tweet>
