<tweet>
	I hate when I don't get my way
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WiIIFerrelI: I have a friend named Jay. We call him J for short.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	.@FlawlessShort need funding to help make their film about domestic violence, do check out their @Indiegogo campaign: http://t.co/o2AKyniSG6
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DalzielRugby: Following a short interview process, we are delighted to announce that John Mathieson has accepted the... http://t.co/7AX…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @drkerrynphelps: South Australian data show that HRT does increase breast cancer risk. Recommends short term use only
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Natural_beauty1 lol well my dreads still short so I'm out of this
</tweet>
<tweet>
	http://t.co/l6sHgBzPJ0 Love this #video. A short #love story between a man, a woman.. and a #bentley.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"RT @idillionaire: Life is short, time is fast. No replays, no rewinds. So just enjoy every moments you have and make the best out of it."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MaggieQ: Love and Gratitude to all of you who made Season 4 possible. It will be a short one, but we will go out with a bang!! Promise.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Anyone up for a short jog? Can't sleep. To many all nighters. Sleep schedule is beyond fucked up...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I reckon being back at work is causing big fluctuations in my mood- more than usual as well. But what do I do about this, short of resigning
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @FrankOceaan: Life is short, Time is fast, No replay, No rewind. So enjoy every moment as it comes
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @QuoteMaxx: The best remedy for a short temper is a long walk. - Jacqueline Schiff
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @theECU_GDI: This girl with short hair working at SupDogs is so gorgeous.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	dont mingle ur feelings with ur lust in short no strings attached
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TradeStocksAmer: We will make money in both directions buying long and selling short in all markets. Stocks make their biggest moves in…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@_ItsFatimah long hair or short hair ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Do you have short or long docs that you own the rights of? We are looking for all types of content for a distributor client. #docs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Short post about RPGs, check it out http://t.co/jik81Iabcs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Your short?term actions multiplied by time equal your longterm accomplishments. Chris Widener"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is too short to wake up with regrets, so love the people who treat you right, and forget the ones that don't.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Short sellers should not think of shorting till 6039 atleast
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Miss_Bere: Hey @DannythatGuy can you check this out - new short filmed in Istanbul by @DerechoVisuals https://t.co/zZaIipJPDP would lov…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Manny Ramirez slides 15 feet short of second base trying to break up double play in Taiwan" : http://t.co/mBScyxyBLy via @YouTube
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@anydaysuk: check out the new Retrospective #thetoeragsessions here's a short film of the studio  http://t.co/AtAFqTrHnq” cool VT ,)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @takecareofUUU: Whatever you need to do to be happy, please do it. Life is short. Spend it chasing dreams. Looking back with no regrets …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @lucee_chick: Life is too short to be wasting your time, tears, and emotions on bullshit. Live it up while you still can.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is too short...live life to the fullest! #iwanttotravel #europe
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bo_devin oh gosh I am right there with you! ? I don't want to cause I feel like it will be so short even tho I know it will be healthy and
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is too short to worry about stupid things. Have fun. Fall in love. Regret nothing, and don't let people bring you down.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Meagan Good really looks nice with this short hair.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Kamuzu was really short
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Another amazing short movie by the Wong Fu Productions. & beautiful scripted too : To Those Nights http://t.co/0o9CBP1TnV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @NormaniKordei: Great seeing you ! YOU LOOKED FABBB @ddlovato you rock that short hair XOXO
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Short girls are the best girls
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @zeezee_88: Life is too short to be serious all the time. So, if you can't laugh at yourself, call me... I'll laugh at you.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @YenWen6: “My hair is at such an awkward length right now...it's not long..and it's not short..I want to cut it again but I want it long…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @claratania: Life is too short to waste time hating anyone. Don't like someone? Leave.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@Amandiiizzleee: Life is short and if you're looking for an extension , you best do well ." TEAM JESUS NIGGA! !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @alsiewalsie: Went to see myself in a film (student short) in @IFI_Dub today. Another ? on the bucket list :-) @RossKeane @thatOReillyone
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Short guys Are not your type but you have a crush on MI. You must Be Mad !!!!"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @lucee_chick: Life is too short to be wasting your time, tears, and emotions on bullshit. Live it up while you still can.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WagTanga: Life is short, time is fast, no replay, no rewind so enjoy every single moment.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @lnsaneTweets: My hair is at such an awkward length right now...it's not long..and it's not short..I want to cut it again but I want it …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Off to nap. Super short nap.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@daisydroplets they WANT but they're not gonna.. Cause i'm short. They wanted to be nice. ://
</tweet>
<tweet>
	MT @SocietyHAE @DynamicAfrica Angolan artist Nastio Mosquito’s captivating short video makes use of historical images http://t.co/imKNaSO7Nf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	!!! RT @ii_Am_Anathi: I think so too RT"@aykay_101: I think school uniforms look neater with short skirts."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New  fitness regime: 6:30 AM short jog to the leisure centre, 45 mins non  stop swimming laps and short jog back home = ENERGY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ThatDopeBlasian: #IfOnlyPeopleWould realize that life is too short to be starting unnecessary drama.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How to Short-Circuit Conflict
http://t.co/DKexFFadZV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Short memories...the bump was dead a couple of yrs ago when Franklin kept getting pinged....unless of course you are that diving grub Thomas
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MARK_McMUFFIN: 19:your short lol but pretty ? I don't really know you! But your cool your cool! ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I do n always will love short girls
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I hope you make your Sunday nothing short of spectacular . . . everyday deserves that anyway.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@WizKhalllifa: Life is too short to spend with someone who makes your days difficult.”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Its very rare that I find a girl who can pull off short hair but god do I love it haha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I want to make a short film . I need ideas tho.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ladies with short hair trying the Wiz Khalifa. look (/_\) ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	that was the short fuck
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Mr502XxX That's called being sanitary. House training is for pets, not human beings. Stop selling yourself short.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is too short to be wasting your time, tears, and emotions on bullshit. Live it up while you still can.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @jmacdonaldseo: Ha someone just asked which gym here's a link to it http://t.co/WLEGi11f0m - Ok looks like short for virgin but it is not
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@LauraHal2010 it's boiling I've got me short shorts on yoooooo #Zeus
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@iampjingxp in short. 4chan is too messy and too nsfwish crazy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@diegopetrucci The short answer: yes. The longer answer is more subtle and nuanced and probably too big for a Twitter reply.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	To talk about next time that may never come when now is right in front of you...Life is too short for that.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SallyNana_95: THATS not fair lie is lie is only pleased u for short period but the true is true whether its bitter but u have the reali…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@The_O2 Erm, well long story cut short Hammersmith Apollo is trying to contact you regarding complimentary tickets for 2nights show, have
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is truly short but not as short as M.I
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Paper or Plastic" a short film by Doug Smith: http://t.co/NIHDMrdshD via @youtube
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Inspiring_Rss: Life is too short. Enjoy your days, laugh at every chance, cry only if you must, and never let others bring you down.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sdsanddunes Youth only care abt short term
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @blaisegv: Psychometrics short queue for airline desk is attractive, long queue for nighclub is too. Context is key.  #istrategy
</tweet>
