<tweet>
	@Sensual_SG ayyyy short one, happy birthday darling; have a good day?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HueyP_In_LouisV: @SpanishCurls_ im just a short bitter black man looking for some love, but i appreciate that!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"schizophrenia susceptibility genes encode proteins that…directly interact and form a densely interconnected network" http://t.co/DL9BKVCB6Z
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When I had my hair cut short!! http://t.co/u87ov7SAwr
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Ahrawsilly: I’m ashamed of my gage yrs. I was really short and fat. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Short BBC film building the Borders railway in 2013 All my dreams came true  http://t.co/2rWhODA0NW
</tweet>
<tweet>
	made this short post 10 Important Signs That Your Job Sucks http://t.co/yXUbt7LgDr
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @aaronmichael714: Better to have a short life that is full of what you like doing than a long life spent in a miserable way
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@nicsopana as you should be! :D BTW, you want the Movement #1? Not gonna collect the series & it would only get lost in some short box!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@OG_Fatt_ prolly somewhere suffering from short man syndrome lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I WISH I HAD LONG HAIR, MY HAIT IT TO SHORT?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MikeCarlton01 i for one will be avoiding all budget coverage. Life's too short.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ohteenquotes: Life's short. Laugh crazy. Love everybody. Forgive quickly. Ignore the haters and never regret anything that made you smi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GracieAirs: @olympia_house , where we now have a permanent space, is only a short walk from #Chesterfield town centre and Chesterfield …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Strawberry niggas got short cake!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Woag woah wiah some chapters are just so short and some are mega long
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@k_10mu A Stractural study of Alhumaid short story
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cat get on my car tonight neighborhood gon be 1 short
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Laptop kya hona hai bathroom me bhool gae honge. Gr8 Fakhru is Ghajni of Pakistan. Physically tough, bald with short term memory loss.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ThatKidFromLA_ ahahah I don't know. But that's what I was about dragon ball sucked and short guy looks like poop, in a tan skin color...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @FrankOceaan: Life is short, Time is fast, No replay, No rewind. So enjoy every moment as it comes
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I’m ashamed of my gage yrs. I was really short and fat. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Readers Receive a Collection of Short Stories in Summer Lies  http://t.co/TSAu087x1I  RT @Bozeman_News
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Kim_Rudo @Tarinhe so u guys are the couple of filmakers i know on here & thought ud like this short  http://t.co/qSi5F9Dhqo
cc @Miss_Bere
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I can't sleep on my right side. Ugh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Don't take a short-cut. Short-cuts lead to dead-ends! Take the long road. Enjoy the view. Learn from the journey.... http://t.co/4EUMGf6Iro
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @rubenthijssen: Coding Guidlines, a short must-read for devs (yes that also means you peeps who build small scripts) - http://t.co/4EHP2…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @djcaspergmf: Short preview of what we have cooking in the studio https://t.co/AoYbpiBarF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I was feelin myself for a minute. Then I wanted short hair so snip snip lol.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life's to short to not do what you want #FuckTheSystem
</tweet>
<tweet>
	hair looks so short today because I've curled it, omg what is life
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Henrik Ibsen~ What ought a man to be Well my short answer is himself.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Batman Beyond was an awesome show. I'm really sad at how short it was. & Return of Joker? So good. SO GOOD. Now sleep so I can make robots.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is too short to wake up with regrets. So love the people who treat you right and forget about the ones who don't.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Here follows a short list of things that are sore today; feet, head.  Thanks go to @timbowtwit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is too short to be wasted in finding answers. Enjoy the questions #PC
</tweet>
<tweet>
	So many people I have briefly met that have already passed at such a young age. It's crazy. Life is truly short. #CherishIt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ratigirl SC has slapped Modi Govt so many times on handling of Guj riots investigations. I know memory can be short, as per convenience.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ShivaKap @timesnow Saar, this is where the media falls short on delivering the truth as it must be told.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @djcaspergmf: Short preview of what we have cooking in the studio https://t.co/AoYbpiBarF  Check out the fan page https://t.co/3PpTs5z0uY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Luke is hot with short hair ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wake Up/Good Nite & CaveStøry are both featured on The DiØS Tape but will only be up for a short time// plz indulge
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Too few the days of life
Too far the journey lasts
Too dear the life we live
Too short the time in ways
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i like po bcuz hes a strong independent short sassy teletubby that dont need no baby sun
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AnthoniaOrji: Life is short, live it. Love is rare, grab it. Anger is bad, dump it. Fear is awful, face it. Memories are sweet, cherish…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is short, Time is fast, No replay, No rewind. So enjoy every moment as it comes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheLoveStories: Life is too short to settle for someone who doesn't know what they want.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We starve look at one another short of breath walking proudly in our wintercoats wearing smells from laboratories facing a dying nation
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @yukisatellites: WN is short for Weighed and Normalized / ×WIN7 rating
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @wongfupro: Thank you all for the incredible initial response to our new short #ToThoseNights. Enjoy in this late night http://t.co/NqD5…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“The best remedy for a short temper is a long walk. - Jacqueline Schiff”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LiIReese300: yo stop sneak dissin before u get banged I know u want to live long enough to see yo short ass dreads grow @Wale
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Short RT"@Questionnier: Describe your night in 1 word? #QnA"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Gulf Keystone – The Short Term Bull Case & a Prize Competition for Gulf Bulls - http://t.co/CMlTwiomh1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	AND THEY'RE SHORT AND PUDGY LIKE ME
</tweet>
<tweet>
	just saw pollard's innings.. perera bowled full,short,good length eveything but still got hammered..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LiLeeePad: Let's get this straight, if you don't get what you put in.. you're selling yourself short. Know your worth.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @AnthoniaOrji: Life is short, live it. Love is rare, grab it. Anger is bad, dump it. Fear is awful, face it. Memories are sweet, cherish…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@actualbaconslut I'm short too so it's okay.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is too SHORT to remove the USB 'safely '
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I would be a lot more comfortable with my body if I had normal person legs... #short & #fat
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @FrankOceaan: Life is short, Time is fast, No replay, No rewind. So enjoy every moment as it comes
</tweet>
