<tweet>
	RT @617Bruins: RT @michaelFhurley: my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@NatalieZisa: Attention: My sister went to a sporting event. The world must truly be ending.” Hockey's different. There's fighting.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	best sporting event I've ever been to / Boston Bruins' Game 7 comeback one for the ages http://t.co/3hhE9pAqZf via @sharethis
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Russia drops visa requirements for major sporting event-global entertainment news - Global Entertainment News http://t.co/2QiioSoaC2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Today I was at a sporting event for my school. The opposing school: 

        Today I was at a sporting event... http://t.co/GtOmza1iIz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t.co/Z0msIuwR20
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_TyAnderson: RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read: http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read: http://t.co/uBAK3W7amy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @connor_foley5: Greatest sporting event I've ever been to
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Bcoopaa: Most insane sporting event i have ever experienced feel like i broke my wrist hitting the glass behind felger after the game
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The internet after a large sporting event reads like a bad porno dialogue: "HUGE HUGE HUGE" "OH MY GOOOOD" "TURN IT ON, TURN IT ON AGAIN!"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Utter joy - This Is The Most Unbelievable Finish To A Sporting Event So Far In 2013 | http://t.co/ljUG5M04DG via @SI_ExtraMustard
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Don't give your followers a play-by-play or box score of a sporting event. If they are interested, they are watching.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Until today, I'd never been to a pro sporting event where the team I'm rooting for lost. I guess there is a first for everything. #Angels
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @FitzyGFY: Photo: In every sporting event there are winners, and there are losers.  And being a loser sucks harder when... http://t.co/a…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Most insane sporting event i have ever experienced feel like i broke my wrist hitting the glass behind felger after the game
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I can sit and watch an entire sporting event without getting bored but as soon as I try to watch a movie I lose interest fast.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I think every sporting event against CB some how the cops always show up!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Jayyyne sporting event in the WORLD next to the Olympics so college football, in my opinion can not be better....basketball is debatable
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BestofGemini: Bring your #Gemini date to a movie, concert, sporting event - anything lively and filled with stimulation. They will eat …
</tweet>
<tweet>
	represent us getting through hard times . Especially since the bombings happened during a sporting event. So don't tell us we are idiots
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @adrianmata30: Honestly, taking a girl to a professional sporting event sounds like an amazing date... FOR ME???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Most Epic Finish To A Sporting Event So Far In 2013, you have to see this - http://t.co/FgCmatQTjw
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@DANGambar: Take me on a date to a sporting event."http://t.co/1Dz3rP9hD1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If you think the "fix is in" for any major sporting event, you're nuts. Sure, refs are not always fair, but they're not league puppets.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Honestly, taking a girl to a professional sporting event sounds like an amazing date... FOR ME???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TurnpikeTodd: @SixFootGoddess money marathon is the only sporting event Im in tune with fuck that ball playing shit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SixFootGoddess money marathon is the only sporting event Im in tune with fuck that ball playing shit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Best sporting event I have ever seen in Boston live!!! Go Bruins!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Today I was at a sporting event for my school. The opposing school had a band, which over  http://t.co/1o9oNNjaKH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @gjohns: The Most Unbelievable Finish To A Sporting Event So Far In 2013 | http://t.co/x2WanJdRmK via @SI_ExtraMustard
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@EmmaEm13 haha largest single sporting event in the world though!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Most Unbelievable Finish To A Sporting Event So Far In 2013 | http://t.co/x2WanJdRmK via @SI_ExtraMustard
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i wanna be at a sporting event when my team wins the championship thats probably the most exciting thing ever
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @erichansen24: I don't get why they don't show it when someone runs on the field during a sporting event, we should get rewarded for wat…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DAurora24: No greater sporting event than the NBA playoffs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LatinaGirlProbl: When your ENTIRE family goes to your sporting event and cheer you on obnoxiously #latinagirlproblems
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TracyGOAZCATS Yeah...I don't see that one getting played again at any stadium or sporting event anytime soon.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Note to all persons considering running on the field at a sporting event: it will always end up with said person in cuffs.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I don't get why they don't show it when someone runs on the field during a sporting event, we should get rewarded for watching the game live
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Um no. “@DAurora24: No greater sporting event than the NBA playoffs”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Greatest sporting event I've ever been to
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@The_X_Man12 I'll help you out at the next naz sporting event haha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Having an identity crisis because I stayed up this late for a sporting event, but MAN, it's goooood to be a Memphian! ??? #grizzlies
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BlueWAUGHful @CPWrestlingFan @SkeezMcsneez we've chanted USA at almost every sporting event this year EXCEPT when we play South
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm at a place in my life where I could definitely get into a verbal altercation at a sporting event.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @FitzyGFY: Photo: In every sporting event there are winners, and there are losers.  And being a loser sucks harder when... http://t.co/a…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@baby_maty: #perksofdatingme I will go to every sporting event possible" You get that from me :-)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @FitzyGFY: Photo: In every sporting event there are winners, and there are losers.  And being a loser sucks harder when... http://t.co/a…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @baby_maty: #perksofdatingme I will go to every sporting event possible
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#perksofdatingme I will go to every sporting event possible
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Twitter is the best when everyone (excluding women) is watching the same sporting event
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RJ_urzendowski: National Anthem should be sang at every sporting event in America no excuses
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Know that if you refer to your tv room as your man cave or paint your face at/for any sporting event you are a dingleberry
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AllisonFial @Adamn_Brotertin not sure if that's a sporting event... BUT WHY THE HELL NOT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RJ_urzendowski: National Anthem should be sang at every sporting event in America no excuses
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Photo: In every sporting event there are winners, and there are losers.  And being a loser sucks harder when... http://t.co/aloNKEC4q9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	No greater sporting event than the NBA playoffs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AllisonFial @JenniferOwsian every sporting event
</tweet>
<tweet>
	That qualifies as one of the worst in  game song ever. I like MGMT but it does nothing to pump me up for a sporting event.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @emitche11: I don't understand how people say hockey is boring. Playoff hockey is the most entertaining sporting event. Except maybe the…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MsKrissyNicole Holding non-sports conversations during a sporting event is a turnoff!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Photo: spiritgun: LMFAO RAGE QUIT lmaoo she legit rage quit in a sporting event http://t.co/q3TIZV6v79
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RJ_urzendowski: National Anthem should be sang at every sporting event in America no excuses
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@MrCheeks14  RT @MBeaty11Cubs: Hopefully I'll never get to the point of tucking in my jersey at a sporting event
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I don't think it's ever a smart move to yell "ref, you suck!" at a sporting event.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RJ_urzendowski: National Anthem should be sang at every sporting event in America no excuses
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Not that I'm mad at it, but why is every sporting event using "My Songs Know What You Did In The Dark" in clutch moments?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Toogull That DJ is hella old, and fired. There's no reason that song should be played at a major sporting event anymore.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	As a matter of fact the best sporting event I have ever been to#thecomeback
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @michaelFhurley: I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just posted my story from the most incredible sporting event I've ever attended. Please read, if you'd like: http://t.co/yk1kEXy5ml
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @njlitigator: The Bruins Game proves one thing. Never, ever leave a sporting event early.   Now Go Rangers!  Beat Boston!
</tweet>
