<tweet>
	Come to discover how two passions meet: the #Qatar Sports Film Festival
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Come to discover how two passions meet: the #Qatar Sports Film Festival
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@QatarSportsFilm: See Sport from another way, as Art and a Passion. Meet you at the Qatar Sports Film Festival, May 24-25, ALRIWAQ DOHA"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Come see short films about #sports and a healthy lifestyle at the @QatarSportsFilm Festival on 24-25 May @ALRIWAQDOHA http://t.co/wCHulhCuR4
</tweet>
<tweet>
	See Sport from another way, as Art and a Passion. Meet you at the Qatar Sports Film Festival, May 24-25, ALRIWAQ DOHA
</tweet>
<tweet>
	See Sport from another way, as Art and a Passion. Meet you at the Qatar Sports Film Festival, May 24-25, ALRIWAQ DOHA
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My friends and I film a low/no budget NBA "talk show" - this is our latest episode. [Re-post from r/nba] http://t.co/Pp54MbwWYj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@FemmePolitique yeah, he is putting his hand in everything these days. Music, sports, film, business. What's next?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KushedUpBobby: Jus seeing tha homie @JetLifeJamCam film today motivatin me to get on this sk8 shit hard like I hate watchin ppl do spor…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Jus seeing tha homie @JetLifeJamCam film today motivatin me to get on this sk8 shit hard like I hate watchin ppl do sports I could learn
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sora was also a possible candidate, but Yuri was chosen for the role. The film will be a youth sports drama, showing the competition and
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Vicksburg to film fishing show for Cooking It Wyld Style with host Larry Levine on Velocity Channel and Fox Sports. @vaportrailscents.com
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Beasley_15: Check out my Highlight Film by @UL_Sports Watch it and Retweet http://t.co/v8Bstqr0xa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My friends and I film a low/no budget NBA "talk show" - this is our latest episode. [Re-post from r/nba] http://t.co/Pp54MbwWYj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Leafs-Bruins Game 7 overtime and the landing of @Cmdr_Hadfield on earth feels like the climax of some weird sports/sci-fi film.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oh really I can't stand here? I film D1 sports on the field. I know my sh** lady. #backoff #goawaykimosabi
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CoachZBarbados: But how CBC does only got 1 camera to send to any sports in #Barbados but going send a whole camera to Japan to film th…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CoachZBarbados: But how CBC does only got 1 camera to send to any sports in #Barbados but going send a whole camera to Japan to film th…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	But how CBC does only got 1 camera to send to any sports in #Barbados but going send a whole camera to Japan to film this shite
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DavidAmerson1: Good work today in the film and weight room..picking up on things pretty quick...feels good to b back in football mode..…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @avventualy24: @Chris_Roling I watch hours if film and like youni write for a sports site, DIFFERENCE IS I PLAYED 12 yrs n coached anoth…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Chris_Roling I watch hours if film and like youni write for a sports site, DIFFERENCE IS I PLAYED 12 yrs n coached another 10. WATCH THE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Our Father’s World – A Film about Christianity and the Environment  http://t.co/xYKJqq6ZDe RT @Green_Register
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Uptown_Chic Hey I'm not a fan of #lahhatl. Sports is my thing. However if you could elbow your way in making the cams film you, I'm there.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OU_Football: How good was LB Rod Shoate? Check out the film courtesy of @SoonerSportsTV and see for yourself! #Sooners http://t.co/UFNM…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@WhyMeJesus @WhyMeJesus oi do not disrespect that film its a cult classic. I'm thinking of hitting a sports bar still!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Think @Jakeable93 should drop sports direct, and become a bloody film critic, all I see on my news feed! Aha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Five Hype works with Personalities (music, sports, film, etc), Brands, Non-Profits, Public Officials, & the Community.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Big sports night tonight
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I thought I'd fly Ryanair for my holidays, to film volcanic activity on Stromboli. But £60 per suitcase? Is a tripod 'sports equipment'?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TommyPowell3 teachings, camp reps sports etc there's loads!!!! My friend from holland did a film studies course it looked amazing :) x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Enjoying my Apple on this beautiful day...walking to go film some sports. #sportslife This Apple is pretty good actually. #Summertime
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@cazillo i've shot sports (horse racing, mostly) since the film days..always in shutter priority....1/500 to 1/1000 sec
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My friends and I film a low/no budget NBA "talk show" - this is our latest episode. [Re-post from r/nba] http://t.co/Pp54MbwWYj
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @30for30: Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Do you think you have what it takes to be a sports agent? Check out the film THE DOTTED LINE by @MorganSpurlock, tonight at 11pm ET on ESPN2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And in a little over a week we'll be off to Wembley to film Champions League excitement for Fox Sports.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LeeMinho_Heirs: Park Shin Hye and cast of Kolon Sports attending the press conference for the short film. Park Shin Hye looks... http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Political thriller and sports film are 2 genres what #bollywood is missing @RajeevMasand
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ZBerm: Eagles S Earl Wolff prepares for games by watching film of Brian Dawkins. Now, he's trying to fill that lasting void: http://t.c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@amynotley I aint wearing no sports right. Stomach wobbles like jelly. Probably just get a black top. And wrap myself in cling film #sweat
</tweet>
<tweet>
	(Video) New #ArtOfTheCraft episode, focusing on the minds that guide the hands that shape the boards we ride.
http://t.co/Ry4ZEJmoi6
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ZBerm: Eagles S Earl Wolff prepares for games by watching film of Brian Dawkins. Now, he's trying to fill that lasting void: http://t.c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The volunteers application form for Qatar Sports Film Festival.
 
 Apply now at http://t.co/spRPdJrnuH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Auburn OL coach J.B. Grimes stopped by Albertville (Ala.) today to watch spring film on OT Tyler Jones. http://t.co/iBhL9DkvRs #Tigers
</tweet>
<tweet>
	THOUGHT BENEATH FILM w/ The Vertigo Hallucination & Vincent Tompa’s Rhythm Church @ Loto’s Sports Bar #hamont http://t.co/REdXtmJAxl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Park Shin Hye and cast of Kolon Sports attending the press conference for the short film. Park Shin Hye looks... http://t.co/sADO2mn3KK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ColinGlover2 @CarlisleCC what events? Keswick has jazz, mountain, film, beer festivals, Christian convention, sports event & more...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Film Study: ‘Doin’ It In The Park: Pick-Up Basketball, NYC’ http://t.co/o8pdzykN0F via @asportsscribe
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Smalls is still killing me. http://t.co/fVuUkV2g2y
</tweet>
