<tweet>
	VIDEO: Mancini's reign over at Manchester City http://t.co/OpE0PRk6ik
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Would you rather have Moyes or Pellegrini? It seems the latter is heading to Man City... http://t.co/uTxnWiIwMS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Arsenal pocket £3m bonus for Barcelona winning the Spanish title - The Sun http://t.co/ne9auGRA9M
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just love watching the "celebs" having a handbag fight. Should become an olympic sport
</tweet>
<tweet>
	[BBC-????] Van Bommel ends career with red card http://t.co/8aawNXfyF3 Preview followed by live covera..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Football ?? love the sport!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Little competition for All Black hookers: The All Blacks will be forced to stick with their incumbent hookers,... http://t.co/c83m3AD78H
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BumperGraham: “@ianherbs: Ciao Mancini; a privilege. But often a nightmare for those who had to work with you. http://t.co/Wu7HcXSIAw #…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Sport_360: Pirelli under siege as @redbullracing lead attack on #F1 tyre failings. And with good reason too!  http://t.co/UmeKmdvonF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The sport and leisure website http://t.co/CJ7r5y0trA
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @CenterSneak: Assuming these pics are real, its fantastic news that Moyes is involving Giggs at this level http://t.co/p6ya3VZ5sL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“I’m not going to lie, I am absolutely gutted about missing out again." - @Tom_Varndell on his England tour omission: http://t.co/Y4rA3oJMuq
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Alan Pardew: We will be better next year http://t.co/YeCemaMUka #NUFC
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Alan Pardew: We will be better next year http://t.co/9NvFDAqKrQ #NUFC
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @four33sports: Arsenal have reached an agreement with Real Madrid to sign Gonzalo Higuain, [Spanish source Sport.es]
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ESPNUK: Apparently Roberto Mancini 'failed' Man City by not winning a major trophy: http://t.co/8Susy6Om0l So should Fergie have gone l…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Football - a sport where you can be sacked a year into a 5yr contract and get more in compensation for doing a crap job than  your salary
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NickGwalton Robson beats Venus Williams in Rome http://t.co/vxSMO0MglJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Super Frank! Sportsmail's tribute to Chelsea's all-time record goalscorer with the ultimate breakdown of… #MailOnline http://t.co/M2E27g9wn2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@voiceofrally This sums up the glamorous side of the sport! WRC Academy mechanics during Spain 2012. http://t.co/9OFVqTG0LM
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@KarlTGL if you're coming home. I'm at the spot, old sport.?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BarclaysLeague: David Luiz hungry for Europa Cup title on special day: Chelsea's David Luiz has the appetite for success in We... http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@rosemaryCNN @vausecnn 3. hour of WR should be permanent. Taped World Sport at the top of the hour does not belong on a news channel.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@charleenetowe calm down old sport
</tweet>
<tweet>
	LancTelegraph: Claret Kevin’s in the game for the Long run http://t.co/D6ak9l29vB #twitterclarets
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wayne Rooney really needs to think again over Manchester United exit, says Fergie  http://t.co/AVXEbKRDB8
</tweet>
