<tweet>
	RT @PawsForAll: ?#GTOAntitaurino Do you think this horse thinks this is "sport" or "art"? If a tradition is cruel THEN STOP IT!!! http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BarclaysLeague: The likely contenders to sign Wayne Rooney: With speculation growing by the day that Wayne Rooney will leave M... http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	David Luiz hungry for Europa Cup title on special day: Chelsea's David Luiz has the appetite for success in We... http://t.co/5g215JizG9"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @voiceofrally: To me this pic from Rally Jordan  sums up why our sport is so brilliantly unique. Drama, tension, bravery, challenge http…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@arnoparigi super je suis a la salle de sport
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lennon in Leicester City link as Celtic celebrate - Scotsman http://t.co/GhzaALcAs8 #Leicester
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @winkerwatson1: Here's the link for live NW200 practice this morning. 

http://t.co/y7jBVnJ7BE

Raining at the moment - could be a delay.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The likely contenders to sign Wayne Rooney: With speculation growing by the day that Wayne Rooney will leave M... http://t.co/58KVIIhJ47
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The likely contenders to sign Wayne Rooney: With speculation growing by the day that Wayne Rooney will leave M... http://t.co/NjnutIaGZf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Telegraph: The likely contenders to sign Wayne Rooney http://t.co/QoMLbDeizy #mufc
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SophWinder sport, business and travel&tourism- no exams but shit loads of coursework -_-
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SwansonQs: "We can't have raccoons for the Christmas thing. They'll hunt the children for sport."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BBCFootball1: Nothing can rain on Ferguson's parade: "There was singing. Lots of singing. There was also chanting, whistling... http://…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Avec stephanie on va pas en sport, on a besoin de repot!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @winkerwatson1: Here's the link for live NW200 practice this morning. 

http://t.co/y7jBVnJ7BE

Raining at the moment - could be a delay.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@GeelongCats So every single tackle should be a chargeable offence? It’s a contact sport, there is always potential for injury.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@J_Sport_: @LKRGIRL i hate when we don't talk all day” me too ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@ESPNUK: Roberto Mancini's Man City exit is set to spark a domino effect at the club: http://t.co/6vhs5PWebK”RT long over due..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LMSCambridge: First @LastManStands game of the season Thursday, @LIVING_SPORT v @BBCCambsSport @ Histon CC. Come and have a watch if in…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Independent: Roma fined for racist abuse aimed at AC Milan players http://t.co/zFRD2FzEYm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mancini sacked for failing to "achieve any of the club's targets" and the players who failed on the pitch - nothing
 http://t.co/QjyOCU2dRG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BeardedGenius: I love these images of Fergie, Giggs & Moyes leaving a 'summit' meeting. Brings to mind dozens of mafia movie scenes. ht…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	DailyMail: What the back pages say on Tuesday, May 14: Roberto Mancini sacked as Manchester City brand I... http://t.co/ItVXHLVrFe #avfc
</tweet>
