<tweet>
	RT @Layyyyyne: We found it. In case the suspense was killing you.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@theweeknd is that all we get?? The suspense is just tooo much!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My dreams have lately been like movies; total strangers, a lot of suspense, and sometimes with subtitles! I should start #writing movies!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Bestdietbook: Read THE TANGLED WEB by @jpLANEauthor “You'll be charmed, frightened, and most of all entertained.” #Suspense #pdf1 http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This suspense is terrible. I hope it will last.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @THEkarenkae: Don't know what/how to feel about this. No more suspense please. I need an answer so we can move on with our lives. Zzzz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ill trade a little peace for some suspense. And ill let it fall wherever it will take me, I love a mystery in the making
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@divyaspandana tell me mam, dnt keep suspense!!! I think i am rit, wat u say!! Is rapheal is coming or not mam,yes or no temme sweet heart
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why can't Made In Chelsea be on every night, sneak peeks of next time leaves me in suspense.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Revenge is just getting way too hectic right now, so much suspense #WaterWorks #NeedANewEpisode
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Don't know what/how to feel about this. No more suspense please. I need an answer so we can move on with our lives. Zzzz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PESPerformance: RT launch of our amazing #Golf #sportsperformance team project wt amazing partners in @TheTodaysGolfer mag on Thursday.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You thought that it'd be funny to leave me hanging in suspense.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Loving the mixed opinions about the daft punk album. Magnifies the suspense for me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My four year journey in choir is over. OR IS IT?!? *suspense*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@snookerbacker1 The suspense is unbearable. #whatwillrodwin
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I should have come on Twitter after watching the finale episode of #HIMYM . Now the suspense is already revealed :(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@skywardbieber REALLY? IT DIDN'T SCARE ME AT ALL TBH LIKE THE PARTS WHERE THE SUSPENSE WOULD BUILD UP BUT IT WASN'T VERY INTENSE SO
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KathryneArnold: Love that The Fear of Things to Come hit #16 on Amazon Best Sellers Top 100 Free ebooks in Suspense! #Thriller #Crime h…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	the whole suspense. ruined by a FB post. the himym FB fan page admin is a moron. :/ #wemetthemother #spoiler #himym
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PESPerformance: RT launch of our amazing #Golf #sportsperformance team project wt amazing partners in @TheTodaysGolfer mag on Thursday.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love that The Fear of Things to Come hit #16 on Amazon Best Sellers Top 100 Free ebooks in Suspense! #Thriller #Crime http://t.co/YfSaYrcqBH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Crime Writers Who Make Me Laugh: Robert B. Parker http://t.co/mPNVf7KJSN #Suspense
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TheBigDowg kahani -  the best Indian suspense movie I've ever seen.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@reetisingh4 I never said it's bad! :) But some matches are extremely boring. Like the rcb vs kkr one. No sixes. No suspense. Nothing!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BiigDickCheney I COUNT IT AS SUSPENSE.......
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sink or Swim Mystery-Romantic Suspense Novel Now an #Audiobook http://t.co/pO5iWW6BUg via @stacyjuba
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The charm is important, because attempts at generating suspense rarely work. #JTF #JTFast #Fast6 #FF6

Read more: http://t.co/jeFzsdpuUq
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sink or Swim Mystery-Romantic Suspense Novel Now an #Audiobook http://t.co/iJYcdZsnzd via @stacyjuba
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@azumayarin I thought of watching it after it's finished. datte... if I watch it now, I'll get suspense & overly excitement~ xD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@StarWorldIndia he is a writer...he writes suspense thriller novels!! :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Suspense :P
</tweet>
<tweet>
	OMG grade my shit, it had to be perfect and on time two weeks ago stop taking your sweet ass time to grade it, the suspense is killing me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A Scary Movie that has me on the edge of my feet that is full of suspense and that even has me afraid hours after are the ones i like
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We found it. In case the suspense was killing you.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DavidCCassidy: 5* “A gripping read. At times chilling, at times humorous, at times deeply moving.” VELVET RAIN http://t.co/C62KhbcTVR #…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WodkeHawkinson: He makes her breathless with desire. But soon, he will have her panting in fear. ZEKE http://t.co/Z3CJYLVKbm #books #su…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	5* “A gripping read. At times chilling, at times humorous, at times deeply moving.” VELVET RAIN http://t.co/C62KhbcTVR #THRILLER #SUSPENSE
</tweet>
<tweet>
	keep checking my email, suspense killing me +_+
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WodkeHawkinson: He makes her breathless with desire. But soon, he will have her panting in fear. ZEKE http://t.co/Z3CJYLVKbm #books #su…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WodkeHawkinson: He makes her breathless with desire. But soon, he will have her panting in fear. ZEKE http://t.co/Z3CJYLVKbm #books #su…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Brock_Corfe The suspense is killing me!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Review: "Not since the original Tremors has a tale skirted the line between comedy and suspense so adroitly." http://t.co/g2TB5nRKqj
</tweet>
