<tweet>
	Love that The Fear of Things to Come hit #16 on Amazon Best Sellers Top 100 Free ebooks in Suspense! #Thriller #Crime http://t.co/CuI7bJoUwF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Read THE TANGLED WEB by @jpLANEauthor “You'll be charmed, frightened, and most of all entertained.” #Suspense #pdf1 http://t.co/477RAhtVX6
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Bestdietbook: Read THE TANGLED WEB by @jpLANEauthor “You'll be charmed, frightened, and most of all entertained.” #Suspense #pdf1 http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JaredLeto Hot damn that was a good stinkin' movie! And I hate suspense movies ugh #whydoyoumakemeloveEVERYoneofyourmovies Why?!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In a Playoff said to be devoid of drama and suspense, boy am I enjoying my popcorn. Way to go Grizz!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You will have a hard time putting The Mistaken by @nancysthompson down once you start it. Suspense at its best! http://t.co/qdQNBcRCsb
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@megha_dxt They were clever about it. Now I can cut my right arm off for Season 9, there's so much suspense, in spite of showing the mother.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DatBoiJermy seems like more of a suspense movie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	these days horror movies aren't really horror, it's just suspense and gore and murder. where's the psychological mind screwing part??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	*** 99-cent SALE! ***
My award-winning romantic suspense, DEADLY OBSESSION, is on sale for only 99 cents through... http://t.co/EumrvYgiwy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How hard can it be to kill one woman? Read BLOOD POOL and find out. http://t.co/WeJGloiUL3 #amreading #thriller #suspense #books @The1Agency
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cnt wait mehn.."@VibeMagazine: Good news for '24' lovers: The suspense series & Kiefer Sutherland will return to Fox May 2014
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VibeMagazine: Good news for '24' lovers: The suspense series & Kiefer Sutherland will return to Fox May 2014 http://t.co/KaT2pB3sVH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VibeMagazine: Good news for '24' lovers: The suspense series & Kiefer Sutherland will return to Fox May 2014 http://t.co/KaT2pB3sVH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i just dont want suspense accounts to come up. fuck
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's a glorious day. The 8 years of suspense had led to this moment. Ted moseby finally meets the mother :D
#wemetthemother #HMYM
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@BBCNewsbeat man city is so overpaid and overbudgetted that by now they just expect to win wheres the challenge and suspense in that?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VibeMagazine: Good news for '24' lovers: The suspense series & Kiefer Sutherland will return to Fox May 2014 http://t.co/KaT2pB3sVH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	AAAHHH “@VibeMagazine Good news for '24' lovers: The suspense series & Kiefer Sutherland will return to Fox May 2014 http://t.co/KPKim7UYKJ”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cancel the show already. You boxed yourself in where you know how the story ends. Where's the suspense? #Batesmotel
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @raccoon_party: You love the past because you hate suspense.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PESPerformance: RT launch of our amazing #Golf #sportsperformance team project wt amazing partners in @TheTodaysGolfer mag on Thursday.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AChristensen01 lol sorry bout the delay. Prob added some suspense. Some people don't have smartphones tho.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You're not perfect, sport, and let me save you the suspense: this girl you've met, she's not perfect either.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oh?RT @VibeMagazine: Good news for '24' lovers: The suspense series & Kiefer Sutherland will return to Fox May 2014 http://t.co/Gbwdg1HZWh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VibeMagazine: Good news for '24' lovers: The suspense series & Kiefer Sutherland will return to Fox May 2014 http://t.co/KaT2pB3sVH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I miss the suspense of waiting 20 minutes for a picture of a naked girl to load on dial-up Internet, then finding out she has a dick.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@VibeMagazine: Good news for '24' lovers: The suspense series & Kiefer Sutherland will return to Fox May 2014 http://t.co/rPSyBRpez7”???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Good news for '24' lovers: The suspense series & Kiefer Sutherland will return to Fox May 2014 http://t.co/KaT2pB3sVH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Dont leave us in suspense, i you got tea spill a little lol RT @mrLdavis: Just got off the phone with D, and the plot thickens.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Oh the suspense of not knowing what the six mark question is going to be about
</tweet>
<tweet>
	?? ????? ??..

RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@whimsyprawn But what flavour lolly? I can't handle the suspense.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Need arsenal to do the buisness tonight.can't take any more suspense this season!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bowtieboyz28 such an awesome show man! So much suspense, national security, CIA, terrorism and great acting! Has to be my favorite show
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love that The Fear of Things to Come hit #16 on Amazon Best Sellers Top 100 Free ebooks in Suspense! #Thriller #Crime http://t.co/zcDKiU4ki8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iamjeffmote: BREAKING: Parliament has just remixed the sound of suspense and drama from 'Teren tereen' to 'Serem sereem'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#KOAN "@SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/QHlHz4Ujb8"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SPORTBILD_eng: Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @illumisharti: Lit been sitting around for the past like, 3 hours in suspense of my exam at 9.30
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Finally know Suspense Accounts, Control Accounts and Bank Reconciliation and I know they won't fucking come up #MyLuck
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Did #Neymar sign at @FCBayern? A report from Brazil keeps German sports fans in suspense: http://t.co/ktj3zfWcek #guardiola
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lit been sitting around for the past like, 3 hours in suspense of my exam at 9.30
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yo the suspense for summer break is so real.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The suspense is killer
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Try to take over the world. In #suspense https://t.co/c8ASEhAPDw
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Have the 1st one FREE ON ME! Anthology of Suspense, Murder, & Mystery & Romance http://t.co/63J1rrvrNS   The Bamboo Mirror #IAN1 #mustread
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT launch of our amazing #Golf #sportsperformance team project wt amazing partners in @TheTodaysGolfer mag on Thursday.@bizitweet #suspense
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @iamjeffmote: BREAKING: Parliament has just remixed the sound of suspense and drama from 'Teren tereen' to 'Serem sereem'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AaronH34 true but this one has cruel suspense with the two options
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Nura no Mago: Chapter 169. sebkrgwervghbtirhgnhb!!! The suspense is killing me!!! and the slow net isn't helping at all!! ;3;
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BREAKING: Parliament has just remixed the sound of suspense and drama from 'Teren tereen' to 'Serem sereem'
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ScrollsNInk: These Godrej ads started off so well, building all that suspense but have been such a wet blanket after that.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	These Godrej ads started off so well, building all that suspense but have been such a wet blanket after that.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sKrystine: Can @thebolts Wait Till we're Young music video come out yet the suspense is killing me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Spirit Dancer http://t.co/CoROqSTvz8 #INTRIGUE #SUSPENSE - recommendation from Sparkle Phillips... author of Finding Your Soul Mate
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How am I supposed to sleep when each episode ends with suspense!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ep 11 sucks!! ? I'm so thankful that Ep 12 comes out tmr!! Gu Family Book has the WORST cliffhangers ever, gaaaah super suspense!!
</tweet>
