<tweet>
	Made it to the last couple innings of the state championship. Glad I made it. Talk about a thriller! http://t.co/xGoyv87qI5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cannes: Abigail Breslin to Star in the Thriller 'Peste' http://t.co/ok4EwrM1MU”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In the vein of Ice Station Zebra, Castle Cape isn’t just a great #thriller, its also a great adventure. http://t.co/7T2tAio3GD #books #asmsg
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New issue of #Tetbury Life mag covers debut of my thriller Polar Nights - big thx to ed Rosie Sharratt for the story! http://t.co/ipjp4fzLuo
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RogerGrubbs: Deftly written..Top Pick..thriller..sure to please all said about Books by Roger D. Grubbs http://t.co/AxkRKdlB8F in profe…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“This thriller will make you believe you can sweat & shiver at the same time.” CASTLE CAPE http://t.co/7T2tAio3GD #thriller #suspense #ebook
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Listening to Thriller at night is SCARY >.<
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RogerGrubbs: Deftly written..Top Pick..thriller..sure to please all said about Books by Roger D. Grubbs http://t.co/AxkRKdlB8F in profe…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Carolina Dynamo advance to 2nd round of U.S. Open Cup after shootout thriller over Chattanooga FC http://t.co/2kP8Wbunkp #Raleigh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Michael Jackson was so damn fine in Thriller video !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	5 Stars for MADAM PRESIDENT. A Historical Fiction & Thriller in one. http://t.co/E4Nhk7pn66 @jerrybeller1
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Prepare to put your LIFE on hold. 5* Review A PERFECT HUSBAND by @DouglasWickard #thriller #suspense http://t.co/vXteyk2At7 #RT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheReunionFilm: @sihorrock Supporting our fellow indie thriller fam! Know anyone who might want to be an extra? #zombie #film #extra ht…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@mattsinger will be from Saturday! With @LostWaxProcess and @handheldcamera Have you seen our pitch? http://t.co/4bC9x9HlWk Can you help?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New: Cannes: Abigail Breslin to Star in the Thriller 'Peste' http://t.co/kZbwtnYHEf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Netflix how the fuck is vanilla sky a psychological thriller
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@PeteTheFreak lol I wanna do a routine to thriller ooft #HouseDown :D x
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bradley's last-gasp homer lifts Tigers in thriller over USC Upstate:  Kevin Bradley picked a good time to hit ... http://t.co/VYCASng4mz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nigelfloyd: RT @mike727360: BIG BAD WOLVES - Magnet Releasing Acquires North American Rights To Critically-Acclaimed Thriller http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hard at work on my new supernatural thriller "Poultrygeist vs. Poltergoose: Fowl Play"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@PatrickStump Yesterday before going to bed I listened to thriller and cried thank u i love u pls come here soon
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WHY R THEY PLAYING THRILLER I DONT UNDERSTAND LOL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RibbonsandTulle @rocketfairydust at the minute we are reading #TaintedWaters by @MaggieThom2 id put it under #Thriller ~N~
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PandoraOL: My mother's ringtone has been Thriller since Michael Jackson died. Since-since. I don't hear it anymore even. Blegh.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nigelfloyd: RT @mike727360: BIG BAD WOLVES - Magnet Releasing Acquires North American Rights To Critically-Acclaimed Thriller http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Calling everyone who #commutes to #work! Read what happened on the #JubileeLine in #London  http://t.co/XY0CPENLVS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HEJoyce1: #PSYCHOLOGICAL #THRILLER
Behind her was an unsettling blackness, a void where moments before she had trod.
http://t.co/7iiZux…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@rrconner no thriller lol. Remember the Time
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My mother's ringtone has been Thriller since Michael Jackson died. Since-since. I don't hear it anymore even. Blegh.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nigelfloyd: RT @mike727360: BIG BAD WOLVES - Magnet Releasing Acquires North American Rights To Critically-Acclaimed Thriller http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It may not be fiction of the highest order, but it sure keeps me turning the pages. "Inferno" by Dan Brown is quite a thriller.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mike727360: BIG BAD WOLVES - Magnet Releasing Acquires North American Rights To Critically-Acclaimed Thriller http://t.co/ma18GJsGP5
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT~FREE Romantic Thriller~The bullet lifted him. He rocked sideways from the impact ON ICE #IRInk #bynr #WriterRT http://t.co/r5oQtxxAvZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Horror worth reading ~>>>TWISTED VENGEANCE by @TweetTheBook When one good cop gets caught up in terror. http://t.co/zrAsgdvkEQ #Kindle
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Going to see Thriller on Friday #anygood?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I also found him to be well-versed in the technology of weaponry, crime scenes and forensics. http://t.co/Anp2NR8Kbs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Hanuman.com an action paced thriller starring @prosenjitbumba. Catapooolt has taken this movie to #Cannes! http://t.co/dXvK5gcIxa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @daesha_zoee: i love scary and thriller movies
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SterlingGate: Our thriller novel The Ninth Orphan (The Orphan Trilogy, #1) is currently in the bestseller list on Amazon UK http://t.co…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i love scary and thriller movies
</tweet>
