<tweet>
	Is it just me or does the new Muse song sound weirdly like Michael Jacksons Thriller?!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love that The Fear of Things to Come hit #16 on Amazon Best Sellers Top 100 Free ebooks in Suspense! #Thriller #Crime http://t.co/CuI7bJoUwF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	5 Stars for J.P. Lane’s The Tangled Web: an international web of intrigue. http://t.co/WmHKv7FTjd  @j.p.LANEauthor  @AuthorAlliance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Christopher Cain At Helm Of Indie Eco-Thriller ‘Terra Infirma’ http://t.co/S9X6I6YmKw via @nikkifinke
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The most awaited Robert Langdon thriller, #Inferno @AuthorDanBrown is now available at @bookadda at a special price! http://t.co/0CH7ZWAyv8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @K_Double_K: “Keep in mind, knowing we could fail is our biggest advantage.” – Michael Colt MASON DIXON: GENESIS #ASMSG #SciFi #THRILLER…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @WritersDigest: Example of what a synopsis should look like: THE IDES OF MARCH (2011 film) http://t.co/U3AZFegwKD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Happy day! A Fatal Verdict is Thriller of the Month on http://t.co/YKtPfz1eQl Many thanks to Wendy Cartmell for kind words! Pls RT. #ASMSG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	How hard can it be to kill one woman? Read BLOOD POOL and find out. http://t.co/WeJGloiUL3 #amreading #thriller #suspense #books @The1Agency
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@zeldawilliams @fromNed @GuyEndoreKaiser I think this has just become a thriller...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@WeChatIndia Q for Varun :What do you prefer more - Romcom or thriller? And please say 'I love u' to me once Love you-Oishika ;
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Khannabond: catch the first look of D DAY an edgy thriller from the stable of Nikhil Advani on yutube.. Enjoyyy...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Two Days in the Smoke's Darren Ripley co-leads in this new thriller feature with Mamma Mia!'s Rachel McDowall.... http://t.co/wBZ7Cn1IWG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	No joy! roadblock with lightening source-time to quit for the night! SECRET THOUGHTS #Medical #Thriller video http://t.co/HuoGqdIw73 #kindle
</tweet>
<tweet>
	MARITIME DISASTER FIVE TIMES MORE DEADLY THAN THE TITANIC http://t.co/jgZISqNGBb #FatalReturn #kindle #thriller #amazon
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#  Update: Emraan Hashmi and Kunal Deshmukh team up for a thriller to be produced by UTV Motion Pictures.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's here. The most awaited Robert Langdon thriller, Inferno - Dan Brown is now available at Bookadda at a special... http://t.co/WVkTdjlQ7N
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Astute readers will enjoy Etier's witty wordplay, pop culture references, and double entendres. http://t.co/CvQZRlbyd4
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nerdsherpa: Just watched RED EYE. It's a surprisingly good and unfortunately little known thriller with Cillian Murphy and Rachel McAda…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When it comes to sex I'm similar to the thriller in Manila
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Just finished Tom Rob Smith's Child44. Fantastic, well researched snowy thriller set in Stalin's Soviet Union. Now to work...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love that The Fear of Things to Come hit #16 on Amazon Best Sellers Top 100 Free ebooks in Suspense! #Thriller #Crime http://t.co/zcDKiU4ki8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The mystery of crime writer @mc_beaton http://t.co/HVJvvXZ8h9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @K_Double_K: When the call came they would be trained ready and waiting. MASON DIXON: GENESIS #ASMSG #SciFi #Combat #ParallelUniverse #T…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Titanic: The Rise, the Fall and the Birth of a Legend http://t.co/COWYC5f9ba #FatalReturn #kindle #thriller #amazon #ebooks
</tweet>
<tweet>
	goodnight canada RT "@Deadspin VIDEO: Bruins game-winner, Jack Edwards call and Toronto reaction. Jesus. http://t.co/IDzcTetMpW"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @blakecurse: Review of The Blake Curse "This is an excellent thriller with a..." http://t.co/JSyOgM2VbR
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @K_Double_K: When the call came they would be trained ready and waiting. MASON DIXON: GENESIS #ASMSG #SciFi #Combat #ParallelUniverse #T…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	ok,what game? RT @IamSleepWalker: maybe you need to play a game RT @sayusra: After watching thriller film, i think i need to watch barbie..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @toolazyfortweet: "The QWERTY Affair"  A fast-paced thriller in which a famed typist uncovers the shocking truth about the world's keybo…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Gutted to be missing first semi Finals of eurovision tonight, hope this Danish thriller is worth it.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Khannabond: catch the first look of D DAY an edgy thriller from the stable of Nikhil Advani on yutube.. Enjoyyy...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	catch the first look of D DAY an edgy thriller from the stable of Nikhil Advani on yutube.. Enjoyyy...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why is Torino bumpn thriller in the shower!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It is a short thriller which started off very slow, mid part still slow but a lil comedy in eg... #TableNo21 #GetGlue http://t.co/pT5kFmVaPZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have #DanBrown ‘s new book #inferno on my kindle! Now to find some time to read it.. #thriller #reading #newbooks #bookworm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@WalkingDead_AMC put one episode that all of the zombies, dances thriller. please.
</tweet>
