<tweet>
	@laNatalina Whos shopping? What are you guys getting? Im going for a TV and movie spree lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	IMovies Legal Movie Downloads: Download unlimited full movies to watch on your computer, tv, portable device o... http://t.co/BEumL5zMtK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	IMovies Legal Movie Downloads: Download unlimited full movies to watch on your computer, tv, portable device o... http://t.co/JqEubYKKSX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	HAPPINESS NEVER COMES ALONE – The Movie http://t.co/NdNdUob5uu
</tweet>
<tweet>
	HAPPINESS NEVER COMES ALONE – The Movie http://t.co/nvxcoNRJZ9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hate seeing one of my bitches in a movie or tv show and they all up on some random nigga.?? Better use listerine hoe.! And bring my money
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Latest Star Trek movie awoken your inner Trekkie? Check out Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home on @Film4 today. http://t.co/m883Ed82zZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AuthorDanBrown - If it saves some wonga I can play myself in the movie adaptation... I've been on TV before you know?!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	[Info]Hongki is scheduled to do a coverage of TV,newspapers,magazines & press conference to promote his movie in... http://t.co/DLGw2WFYHF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	New ‘Man of Steel’ TV Spot and Posters: Join Superman in the Sun http://t.co/RQCz00dQmz
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sanitagroen :) I agree. It was surprising to see how an animated movie  teach us more valuable lessons than what's on TV cc @Aslam_Levy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i would love to get a part on the new star trek tv show if they do it.. and the new star wars movie..would be a dream plus
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Whos shopping? What are you guys getting? Im going for a TV and movie spree lol @Banes_Voice6
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Pawan kalyan & Samantha's Trivikram movie produced by B.V.S.N.Prasad is shooting currently in Ramoji Film City http://t.co/1QM4uU1TOu
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I hate when i'm watching something happy on tv & then a fucking scary ass trailer for a movie comes on why?! ???????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	REPEAT: Why not let the kids tune in to KidsZone? It's an hour of their favourite TV & movie songs- & we're sure they'll love it! #SDSKZ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Alarm went off in the movie and my tv was loud , mom woke up thinking somebody stealing her car again ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i would love to get a part on the new star trek tv show if they do it.. and the new star wars movie..would be a dream plus
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When I say "ending the night with netflix," that actually means "tweeting while some insignificant movie is playing on my tv"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@fucktyler @JasperDolphin  looks like his soul was just stolen from the girl from the movie the ring who came outta the tv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @G_Kontos: Good Will Hunting is on tv right now.. Such a great movie... "You like apples? How you like THEM apples!?!"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Even your dreams become more pedestrian with age. A good one is you're watching a movie on TV and nobody bothers you.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@xhoneybee I know bby.  Watch a movie or tv or listen to music.  Anything to take your mind off of it.  Okay?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	where is a  good movie role or tv role when u need one??? HELLO OUT THERE!!! need the fun of it!!! so enjoyable
</tweet>
<tweet>
	SO, YOU WATCHED A HORROR MOVIE ?  Where did you watch that ? at the TV or the MIRROR ? :p  #bitter
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ZapAppleBloom @SweetieBotatDD Bay involved? That explains why Hasbro is bold enough to take a Made-for-TV movie to theaters! :D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheGoogleFactz: The movie “Cast Away” was originally pitched as a TV show and lead to the creation of “Lost.”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	OMG!! The Scream series is being produced into a TV show! YES! My obsession with Scream is coming true!! ? http://t.co/M3AWW4lbR8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@_lycheemonster Okay, so one time I saw a made for TV movie where the first English voice actress for Sailor Moon fucked a robot!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	They should make the house of night series into a movie, or tv show.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's 3 in the morning out here. Ain't shit on TV. I wonder if I order a movie would coach get mad mmmmm?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	She Yelling At Da TV She ready To jump in Da Damn Movie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @kayla_schafer: #9O21O NEEDS a tv movie! I REALLY want to see what happens in everyone's future especially Silver! @JessicaLStroup @stug…
</tweet>
