<tweet>
	@Hitokiri1 @SirTobbii Life Model Decoys. They appeared in the LA Nick Fury TV movie I believe (with the Hoff as Fury ^^U )
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This film, a Made-for-TV movie, was directed by Charlton Heston - http://t.co/ef4Smt7PAA
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Time to get tweeting! 28 days later....I love how this movie opens - the tv show of insane riots to absolute stillness. #zombielove
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ameyc: @SardesaiM Mainly Coulson. No other big names from the Avengers movie are in the TV series.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When I say "ending the night with netflix," that actually means "tweeting while some insignificant movie is playing on my tv"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why can't they put @NitroCircus TV series on Netflix too. I've watched the movie way too much !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i would love to get a part on the new star trek tv show if they do it.. and the new star wars movie..would be a dream plus
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My sister @PimpnAlTheseMen got me watching some weird movie on tv...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	watching nandha ön sun tv.an awesome movie.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TrevyKnox </3 we can have a tv night,.instead of a movie one.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just saw an ad for a Nickelodeon movie that said they were reuniting the cast of the Sopranos in this TV movie. Do kids watch the Sopranos
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Omg Honey boo boo is coming on Britains tv.will the theme from the movie Deliverance be playing in the background.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OnlineSRKfans: If u r at home u have 2 options on Tv.
One 2 Ka 4 movie on Sony Max
Duplicate Movie on Star Gold.
#SRK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Carrie Fisher is using a personal trainer to get into shape for the new Star Wars movie. http://t.co/jEGsYzOMvt #celebritypersonaltraining
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If u r at home u have 2 options on Tv.
One 2 Ka 4 movie on Sony Max
Duplicate Movie on Star Gold.
#SRK
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheOnly_Jesus: What Caleb did to keep Drew alive was some shit you see in a movie or on TV, not in real life. For that I respect you br…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Someone in my household is watching Argo (2012) http://t.co/suzFfpOI1m #trakt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Really excited for this! For awhile the only well done vampire movie/tv show that I've enjoyed has been True... http://t.co/yqKIOrcbPV
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Someone in my household is watching The Amazing Spider-Man (2012) http://t.co/jXNcDeiiwc #trakt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Someone in my household is watching The Avengers (2012) http://t.co/YUKPXqVNh7 #trakt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When I say "ending the night with netflix," that actually means "tweeting while some insignificant movie is playing on my tv"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i would love to get a part on the new star trek tv show if they do it.. and the new star wars movie..would be a dream plus
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheOnly_Jesus: What Caleb did to keep Drew alive was some shit you see in a movie or on TV, not in real life. For that I respect you br…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheOnly_Jesus: What Caleb did to keep Drew alive was some shit you see in a movie or on TV, not in real life. For that I respect you br…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@fucktyler if you could get a prop from any movie or tv show what would you choose?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Director of movie Buster and creator of TV show Bridezillas, David Green on the shock of Mancini's... http://t.co/mts156Kjl2 #SportsNews
</tweet>
<tweet>
	why? “@JNisaisquoi Watching TV show/movie relationships makes me mad sometimes lol”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Vintage tv is showing Bros- I owe you nothing frm 1988 who'd have thought there was a face for a vampire movie staring out #blade
</tweet>
<tweet>
	TV and movie companies making it harder for us to watch their content online by setting up individual pay monthly streaming services suck.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Wtf @spotify, no more horror movie/tv ads. Thought this was some sick joke for an actual spotify promo #thepurge
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I can't sleep and there's nothing but porn on my movie channels! *turns tv off*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Where is my tv show/movie romance? & yes it does exist dammit! Lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @G_Kontos: Good Will Hunting is on tv right now.. Such a great movie... "You like apples? How you like THEM apples!?!"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@RyanxWrestling go to google, type in project free tv it'll pop up and you type in a movie or show. Lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watching TV show/movie relationships makes me mad sometimes lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheOnly_Jesus: What Caleb did to keep Drew alive was some shit you see in a movie or on TV, not in real life. For that I respect you br…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheOnly_Jesus: What Caleb did to keep Drew alive was some shit you see in a movie or on TV, not in real life. For that I respect you br…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The fact that I'm not really sleepy yet, there's nothing on tv, and there's not a movie I wanna watch <<<<
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My Moms Facial Expressions Wen Shes Watching Tv Or A Movie....... So Not Cute LOL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ChrisTrondsen: In Pt. 1, To Be One tells u what movie roles they would want & talk about favorite TV show theme songs! @tobeone - http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When I say "ending the night with netflix," that actually means "tweeting while some insignificant movie is playing on my tv"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hate when I'm about to shower then something good comes on tv even if it's an old show/movie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What Caleb did to keep Drew alive was some shit you see in a movie or on TV, not in real life. For that I respect you bruh @ProdaJayy2296
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Do y'all ever get those tingles in your hands whenever something awesome happens in a movie or TV show? Or is that just me?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Well this one of my favorite movie so ima curl up and glue my eyes to the TV ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The dumbest movie is on tv.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i dunno if i should watch something on tv, listen to more songs, or watch a movie. #thestruggle
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@jreezy_easy read what I said dumbass. I never said a movie on tv is a show
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Fyre_flye probably when they stop letting marketers be the final say for what goes in a movie/tv show/videogame et cetera
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bout to find me a good movie on this tv til i fall asleep.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Deyvid_Bee So a movie shown on TV is a show? Yeah you sound stupid bro lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	GRAVITY New Movie Poster and Trailer http://t.co/6aW6zTtfrT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When I say "ending the night with netflix," that actually means "tweeting while some insignificant movie is playing on my tv"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@iLab1D @Gomezology GoT isn't a movie tho it's a tv show but anyways yes she needs to but she can't and i'm ok with that but :(((((((
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @blakeshelton: Movie on the TV.. Miranda is looking at her laptop... I'm looking at Miranda...
</tweet>
