<tweet>
	Is Cameron's Britain what we fought for in the war? | Harry Leslie Smith http://t.co/HpbFVHH41n via @guardian
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @QueenBlair_Bass: If you want peace, always be prepared for war.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thenicolabryant: Tragic & beautiful:“@jackshebang: A Paris apartment, was abandoned when the Nazis invaded, has lain empty until now. h…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Only the dead have seen the end of war." 
— Plato
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@elite_gohan No, but I have few time left to master the Dragon Fist. I'm fighting Bills the first day of war.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AnglinBrooke ok and if you want to spend more on military on this war on terror  you are not a fiscal conservative either
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Its really funny how human rights in the USA talk about the starvation in Africa; in contrast, they stupidly overlook the civil war in Syria
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Then he made us watch the all blacks war dance thing and i was like beside myself bc scared
</tweet>
<tweet>
	All Is Fair In War And Love?(2) http://t.co/R1ih4QzRGj via @vanguardngrnews
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@farzana_versey Nothing. They are good businessmen, they can sell a 'war' too, if needed!! @timesofindia
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @The__Chauvinist: What is it going to take to convince Indian Congress-voters that Congress along-with Muslims are at war with us to Isl…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	R u really better parents then terrorist cuz u raise ur kid 2 18 2 die at war 4 freedom that doesn't apply 2 u as much a those who r richer
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I sense war ><
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Love ? at war ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sammy_wammy21 you won the fight but not the WAR!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In the first Indochinese War, the French General was General Navarre and the Viet Minh's lead was General Vo Nguyen Giap. So there.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hope the 8 mark essay is about why the reds won the civil war! ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hashtag war going on here ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	religion is just a war against who has the best imagination (@YouTube http://t.co/1IJ3WFQ0xG)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What is it going to take to convince Indian Congress-voters that Congress along-with Muslims are at war with us to Islamise ~ India Shining?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BlueNRedState: Remember when Bush admin lied us into a war & then changed talking points on a weekly basis & the right & the media went…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PsychoticFreak_: "You lost a part of your existence in the war against yourself."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BlueNRedState: Remember when Bush admin lied us into a war & then changed talking points on a weekly basis & the right & the media went…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	CAN'T BEAT THESE FUCKING MONSTERS IN GOD OF WAR. BEEN TRYING FOR TWO HOURS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@bubblyz20 @MaryamNSharif Correction Please...WAR GYA PAKISTAN ..Invitation to Indian PM,GAWADAR and pipe line projects stopped prof of it..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Japanese mayor says second world war 'comfort women' were necessary

 http://t.co/pNv5kPUYud
</tweet>
<tweet>
	THE Japanese government has distanced itself from comments by a prominent politician that the so-called ???comfort women??? of World War ..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Come at me, now this is war.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LarsBit: Gulf states, fanning the flames of war in Syria, shut their doors in the face of Syrian refugees http://t.co/JH3GJIO3VI #KSA #…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	BEIRUT: Syria wants details on a U.S.-Russian proposed conference to end the war before it makes it decision to attend and says the role ..
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @stephendoss: If it is true that Jamaluddin Jarjis will move from the war room to the cabinet, then wht lessons hv been learnt?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My Grandad is always going on about how he fought in the war. At 94, he was the oldest of the troops in Iraq.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @1LadiWhite: Im at war with myself
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@LOVE_1N_WAR your side sound like something off of lifetime while mine sound like cinemax
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just know i have a 75% discount coupon for Total War Shogun 2 in Steam. Who wants it?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Why am I still awake? Hey B... @CannonKCCO lets have a silly face snapchat war. Lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We headed for war
Like your uncle JT done years before
No pussy no dope this ain't Saigon
But keep your heads up for roadside bombs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TedZeUndeadBear eh no lorh world war 1 & 2 and gulf war and whatever since im a geog student war not i cause one hor
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@inouifemme Thanks, its a tug of war ;-)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I want to win Injustice: Gods Of War and a new games console - http://t.co/1kt0ACdmzC Follow @t3dotcom & RT to enter #t3techwin #T3gow
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @IDFrabbi: And if you go to war...against the enemy, then you shall blow an alarm with the shofar; and you shall be saved from your enem…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Playing God of War Ascension
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It's a constant battle. A war between remembering and forgetting.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"What if Marshall McLuhan was right?" is one of those troubling questions. http://t.co/OM5S5g0iAC
</tweet>
<tweet>
	And the epic war after a year of studying begin.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ObsNewReview: The War On Drugs: America's longest war. Join David Simon and @EugeneJarecki, who made The House I Live In on 23 May http…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @P_Hamilton_PUP: @peterf225 @gerrymcguinnes1 know your engagement of War, hospitals are Red Cross should be none targets but republicans…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	War between Fats and Thins just with do your favorite sport. #TrustMeItWorks #ICanUCan @LMen  #LMenQuiz #NX300 http://t.co/8BrdUsAi9W
</tweet>
<tweet>
	One half of the WW II Memorial, including the ATLANTIC Arch http://t.co/MvOxZKibzE PHOTOS
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @__MICHAELJ0RDAN: can u imagine a world without war or pizza? i surely cant
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mas ok ng friend ang julie-lauren-rita kasi cool lang sila,walang war :) #peace
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SuperiorF_Gohan @king_reborn WHAT has the war started already
</tweet>
