<tweet>
	RT @Toddkkxy: I also saw the "God of War Saga" for $40, so that'll probably be another investment down the road.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Memorized till world war 2 brb dying.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AJEnglish WAR MATERIALS DEMAND SPUR SENATE_CONGRESS INSIDER TRADING OPPORTUNITIES & LEGISLATIVE RACKETEERING http://t.co/RT6Wp9PTx0
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @syriano100: NYT:"Obama and Cameron expressed hope that Putin  would join efforts to end the #Syria/n war but offered no evidence that h…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Maaaake looove toooo meeeeeee . so when the world is at war , let my love heal us all <3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tea and coffee at war over national drink status - The New Indian Express http://t.co/5dcmwZJTto  via @NewIndianXpress
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @susanas4321: Do you or someone you know have #fibromyalgia so do I. join us we are site of resistance to the war on welfare http://t.co…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@foxnewspolitics wtf. liberals you will be made the dogs of war.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	???????????Japanese mayor says second world war 'comfort women' were necessary http://t.co/gMxFxgWezO via @guardian
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @asifkapadia: Great film: “@ObsNewReview: The War On Drugs: America's longest war. @EugeneJarecki The House I Live In on 23 May http://t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @cattfincham: @nickgasmic same it's like a war of love and hate in my mind
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Into The Eyes OF Hell: A Forgotten Conflict (Vietnam War) ? http://t.co/K884rct4jY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	teach the younger generation about love and sharing and God and Jesus instead of war hate and slavery
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@worldmist1 This is why we need 2 stop thinking linearly (D or R?) & start thinking pragmatically (Hmm, I cant vote 4 any war criminals...).
</tweet>
<tweet>
	EU gives $85 mn humanitarian aid to war-torn Syria
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I'm now ranked Experienced (top 60%) in God of War: Ascension on Raptr! http://t.co/IFqYwyEinv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DerbyTelegraph: War veteran: Russians have treated me better than my own country http://t.co/1p4tD2R1dj #derby
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@nickgasmic same it's like a war of love and hate in my mind
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Do you or someone you know have #CRPS so do I, join us we are the site of resistance to the war on welfare http://t.co/soKtPib986 RT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	DARPA project for war-fighters to scale walls in full gear.

if u like that kinda stuff..... http://t.co/uFQgvLvgNw
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TellyStern then why didnt we go to war with them the other 50 times they did the same thing???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Italy always bring white flag when war #itabot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	‘World War Z’ Scribe Makes Directorial Debut With Garrett Hedlund http://t.co/kmg6aPhJCT via @nikkifinke
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Japanese mayor says second world war 'comfort women' were necessary--Bitch? http://t.co/cUrebj3TWP
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Benghazi is not the biggest scandal since Watergate, the Iraq War is!! Iran Contra pretty bad too, but Fox won't tell their base what it is
</tweet>
<tweet>
	??? I would go to war with God for u baby
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This is a cold war we're fighting, and if you even cared at all you wouldn't have start this cold war
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Baron finna play tug of war right now but girl not about it
</tweet>
<tweet>
	So 3000 more troops are being deployed cos The Un is intervening in the DRC incident? "We are going to war" this ... http://t.co/LDqotmi0De
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @steventaylorsa: @CrimeLineZA We cannot win the war on drugs if we allow our borders to be open and anyone to enter. We need to clamp do…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I also saw the "God of War Saga" for $40, so that'll probably be another investment down the road.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Play God of war III :o
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @__MICHAELJ0RDAN: can u imagine a world without war or pizza? i surely cant
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"Isn't war horse when they get 2 horses on stage, one from England, one from Germany and they have a war" omfg ????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @_Mitchr: #Giveaway! Two 75% Total War : Shogun 2 Steam vouchers I just recieved from them, follow and re-twet! It's that simple to ente…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have two tickets to a 75% reduction in steam for Total War: Shogun2 to give, if are interested: p
</tweet>
<tweet>
	and the war begins.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	War
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@callofduty bring back the game mode WAR #blitzkrieg
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Now that you people have witnessed my, um, mental war, it's time to say ttyl. Ttyl.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	When boys get jealous it's kinda cute but when girls get jealous it's like World War III is about to happen.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@buk_shawn . I ain't tryna do that war shit I ain't got no guns my ass is done . I thought it was Greatness when u said turbans LOL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Waltz with Cannes: 'Bashir' director moves from war to wow in animated sci-fi film http://t.co/8LtpvBFlbJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @VacciNewsNet: The taliban has ended its war on polio vaccination workers and admitted that immunisation protects the children http://t.…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I always seems to be at war with myself, and have the cuts and bruises to prove it...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @susanas4321: Do you or someone you know have #arthritis so do I, join us we are the site of resistance to the war on welfare http://t.c…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sobiazia @ShireenMazari1 There should be NO war anywhere. Just be smart about your relationships. Read dialogues between Ind-Pak over 20yrs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I want a girl to play that intellectual tug-o-war with...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sorry but Chill?I can't.
I ship CrissColfer.I do not like ship war ,either.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @IamKagi_STYLES: "Life is way to short to spend another day at war with yourself"
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @simplynonna: Dirty Wars, Filthy Hands: 5 Unsavory Ways America Conducts Its Global  War on Terror  http://t.co/pToiwnoHCv
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ChelseaSpencer3: Just told charlotte I know nothing about Cold War, she then informs me that the exams about the Cold War
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@wacarmaker That's funny. My brother is a Civil War historian, teaches @ W WA U, Bellingham, now in Italy teaching.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @susanas4321: Do you or someone you know have #fibromyalgia so do I. join us we are site of resistance to the war on welfare http://t.co…
</tweet>
