<tweet>
	RT @BBCBreaking: Boat carrying up to 200 Rohingya Muslims capsizes off western #Burma in evacuation ahead of Cyclone Mahasen  http://t.co/n…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @lets_be_humane: Even nature is against them. :( 
"@RT_com: Boat with up to 200 Rohingya Muslims sinks off western Myanmar –UN agency ht…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Good, The Bad, and The Ugly. Even though it's a spaghetti western, it's still a piece of rugged Americana.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @DavidKenner: AFP journalists travel along with the Syrian army as it surrounds the western town of al-Qusayr. http://t.co/Q1GcCHtTZT
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I forgot Iowa Western is actually still a place
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If you try to pursue a relationship with me I'm going to assume you will end up leaving me it's nothing personal it's just from experience.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KARAKTER_S: Homes for the aged: opportunities that are just as huge for Western firms http://t.co/L23lCC1HaI
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Police confirm Western Greyhound bus fire "may have been started deliberately".
Any info - call police 101, quote ref. GC/13/151.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Feds gear up for dangerous fire season in Western U.S. - http://t.co/wjiZ4YHNlm http://t.co/xZpNdEnz9j
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Syrian Crisis Part of Western Geopolitical Strategy, Says #Catholic Patriarch http://t.co/rcUkAkX5Vj #Syria
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Ai yahhh! You western countries stress me out aru! -China #bot
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Is China Readying to Kick the U.S. Out of the Western Pacific? - Video - http://t.co/Va7OTipAK9 http://t.co/fnPzExuGVN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Is China Readying to Kick the U.S. Out of the Western Pacific? - Video - http://t.co/rbG4MpCLMz http://t.co/QwIpsPPXdX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Homes for the aged: opportunities that are just as huge for Western firms http://t.co/L23lCC1HaI
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Correction: We HAVE clinched the Western Conference! #whoopsie
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ZanJabyl: The Western World need to be aware of that, the Adhalath Party of Maldives is fully financed by Laskar Tholibaan.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Mohandas Karamchand Gandhi~ (On Western civilization) I think it would be a good idea.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BBCBreaking: Boat carrying up to 200 Rohingya Muslims capsizes off western #Burma in evacuation ahead of Cyclone Mahasen  http://t.co/n…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ArashMarkazi: Did anyone predict a Grizzlies-Warriors Western Conference Final?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@PartyGoth there it is. western civilisation in the 21st century summed up in a nutshell
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Airlines that Fly to Edinburgh http://t.co/lBSHk6kBhF
</tweet>
<tweet>
	FYI @iKirann_ Tropical #Cyclone #Mahasen Calcutta (Kolkata), India, will be very close to the western side of the storm system
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Former Western Leaders Like Tony Blair and movie stars like Angelina Jolie and George Cloney come to Africa... http://t.co/iys59BrTL0
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@USQVC: Signing contract with Mayor Ray Brown Western Downs RC for research into the digital future for the region. http://t.co/CM1e3FCzYj”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The end of western civilisation will be traced back to when we started pulling suitcases instead of carrying them. #GetOutOfTheWay
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BreakingNews: UN agency: Boat carrying 100 Rohingya Muslims capsizes off western Myanmar while evacuating from storm; unknown number mi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I say.... Memphis vs Golden State in Western Conference. That match-up EASILY favors Memphis, but I wouldn't count Curry out
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Lady_Vx: What character would you be in a Western? I think Id be the tumbleweed rolling along in the middle all peacefull like,just chi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @msnNOW: Massive poop spill closes highway in worst Monday commute ever http://t.co/W9CE5yoBrx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @paprilia: Burritos bowl @MOJO_Jkt yummy, it seems like korean food, but this is with western style..yummy @openrice_id  http://t.co/nTa…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Rohinya boat sinks off Burma: A boat carrying Rohingya Muslims has capsized off western Burma, aid agencies sa... http://t.co/WldhTm62ex
</tweet>
<tweet>
	FYI @Syed_29 Tropical #Cyclone #Mahasen Calcutta (Kolkata),India, will be very close to the western side of the storm system intensity 75mph
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @thumbfighter: filming on Cowboys and Engines in the very hot desert and really loving the cast and crew of this Steampunk retro/futuris…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	[??] Follow me if you love western music<3
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Literally started crying becasue of All Quiet on the Western Front. #goodbooks
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BreakingNews: UN agency: Boat carrying 100 Rohingya Muslims capsizes off western Myanmar while evacuating from storm; unknown number mi…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Burritos bowl @MOJO_Jkt yummy, it seems like korean food, but this is with western style..yummy @openrice_id  http://t.co/nTaNitbTpy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BBCBreaking: Boat carrying up to 200 Rohingya Muslims capsizes off western #Burma in evacuation ahead of Cyclone Mahasen  http://t.co/n…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ABCNews24 #auspol Bad news there is no mines or heavy industry in Sydney western suburbs or likely to be so sit on arse wait for job futile
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @BBCWorld: Boat carrying up to 200 Rohingya Muslims capsizes off western #Burma in evacuation ahead of Cyclone Mahasen  http://t.co/VEjl…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@HayleyRictor : / probably not..but I will be going to Western soon! That's close by
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Swinny_95 @alex_spanner all is quiet on the western front
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @tamzinmart: Looking for ex-teachers to deliver on a Numeracy and Literacy programme, Grade1-6, for the next 2 years in the Western Cape…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DrMarcusP  there are many in the western alliance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @andywest21: You hear about teams in the 80s it's just 76ers, celtics lakers and pistons. No other western conference team.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Signing contract with Mayor Ray Brown Western Downs RC for research into the digital future for the region. http://t.co/NFTG9gQRBl
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@AhBoon_426 That's why I wanna marry a western guy :(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	filming on Cowboys and Engines in the very hot desert and really loving the cast and crew of this Steampunk retro/futuristic western
</tweet>
