<tweet>
	@nick_gia10 working in Fairfield,  North western suburbs trust it to happen there lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @MortenHj: #Salafi freedom; firebomb shops, beat people, harass, mafia work. Yeah thanks for imposing these dogs on #Syria Western brain…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#bath Western Daily Press published Jenson Button: McLaren form is a little embarrassing: Article     http://t.co/6DvbeCZSe0
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A reminder for our Thursday #ODL seminar: Opportunities and Policy Challenges of Distance Learning in Western Balkans http://t.co/TRShgfp1Kd
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Beautiful town Dingel in western Ireland http://t.co/6QE3x2CH0t
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The remains of Skylab can now be seen in a museum in Esperance, Western Australia. It fell back to Earth in 1979.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@JackiJing awesome interview...Western Mass still misses you. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Massive fire at Western Greyhound depot, Summercourt near the A30: Read more: http://t.co/2jmrPrJqPN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ActuallyNPH: Shooting scenes for @SethMacFarlane ‘s awesome new western film. You won’t believe what I’ve done all day. #physicalcomede…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Waaaa not bad. Changes to a positive way in the faculty. They got western food here and the girls here also hmmm interesting.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@ThelIluminati next Western Civilization. y'all swear y'all nice when it come down to simple talkin sh!t, we cud freestyle on TV and shIt
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@africageobirds  2 new birding routes launched in Western Cape: Swartland Birding Route & Rocherpan Nature Reserve https://t.co/eRYKFUNVBh
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@dana_nighs Western Pennsylvania lol now you mean like Washington the state right? lol
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Redi speaking to Cape Town Mayor, Patricia de Lille, about the deplorable sanitation services in Western Cape townships. #RediTlhabiShow
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lil boiz will gold change everywhere doing western union. Delaying me for that matter. Wonder who is sending those illiterate money
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Western margin of #MakarskaRiviera, #Vruja area or Well area in English with astonishing view. Wann join us here? :D http://t.co/zPVbyF3PzU
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@steph_chai yup, heard dat b4, dont be surprise, next time will say, prefer western than asian food :(
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My TopTeacherIT is unfortunate that misinformed people select leaders. now it is going to be  the teachers. god save from western culture
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Western civilization means white domination
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Optometrist Jobs in the Western Isles - Western Isles - Flame Health Associates LLP #optician #jobs http://t.co/YWlLBSPoJ2
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@saclubrugby so what happens when the varsity clybs end 1st in the western province and KZNRU unions do they head to community cup?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Western Indian Ocean earthquake and tsunami hazard potential greater than previously thought | News | National Ocean http://t.co/n3EcrFXLIa
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Private Kitchen: The best of Western and Oriental cuisines http://t.co/5sptcl46Bx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Chicago Blackhawks resume rivalry with Detroit Red Wings in Western ... - Fox News http://t.co/JxInvK0uPs
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @guardianworld: Many feared dead after boat with Rohingya cyclone evacuees capsizes http://t.co/70ksC22ImD
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@StandUpForBarry IF that's the case, then now they must do what they can to help revive the club. If they won't - Western League will...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Our favorite campgrounds in the Western US http://t.co/UVsVyCQrCD via @AnOutsideMom
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Recent reports state boat carrying 100 Rohingya Muslims has capsized off western Burma after slamming in to rocks on Monday night.
</tweet>
