<tweet>
	FINAL FANTASY ALL THE BRAVEST is here! An easy-to-play adventure with massive battles awaits! #FF_ATB http://t.co/FzCSNyFne8
</tweet>
<tweet>
	kat library bukak ghost adventure kuat2. YOUR HOUSE IS IT?!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@jillcoursen that’s ok, Thursday is just a short trip, we will still do our longer adventure scouting trip later this month, right? :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Gonna pretend I'm a kid again and watch Adventure Time all night #bestshowgoing
</tweet>
<tweet>
	life is adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @sadieebby: Could use a little adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@TheAmazingFatty and listen to some tunes by adventure club and seven lions. awesome wubology.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@charleyboorman just watched final episode Frontiers Canada tonight! Loved it! Great job showcasing Canada! Bring on your next adventure!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#nowplaying Do I See Color - Adventure Club
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Time for a new adventure #change #???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Fin watch adventure time and smoke the crackhead torch dab bong till I pass out, wake up, lift weights, practice 8 bars like a fucking fag
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Chiaki747 Sonic Adventure is only worth playing on Dreamcast. Even then it's only OK.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	In the vein of Ice Station Zebra, Castle Cape isn’t just a great #thriller, its also a great adventure. http://t.co/7T2tAio3GD #books #asmsg
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Raaiq17: Keeen for an adventure to a far away land where no one knows me #LetsGetLost
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @bdgrabinski: I'd pay a monthly fee if I could get Siri to sound like BMO from ADVENTURE TIME.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Cruisin' with people. The small car adventure.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Thanks for the adventure ;) @michiemarquez village hopping huhhuha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @GeminiTerms: A #Gemini woman craves adventure and will try anything new and interesting.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	She act cool cause she know she bad, but bitch I prefer to watch adventure time!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	It was the most amazing adventure with a completely brilliant group of people & I'd go again in a heartbeat
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @FuckColtynRay: COLTYN SAFFORD ADVENTURE “@JosshYoung: all I want is a cool camera and a bag of doobies. then you can set me free into t…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@Raaiq17: Keeen for an adventure to a far away land where no one knows me #LetsGetLost" @XxSidLeYxX
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stuck between new and old. Although I'm up for adventure, I am fond of what I already know...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have a whole group being made of Digimon Adventure tamers c: I can't wait! http://t.co/71JCNjOcdG
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @freddeemercury: go on an adventure with me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	adventure time in 10 mins! fasten your seat belts!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My life is turning into one giant adventure :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The adventure times :D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I really want to explore and adventure the world. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I just entered the "Embrace the Adventure" Sweeps from Rosetta Stone for a chance to win a 10k Trip Giveaway! http://t.co/EA7wMPsK1i
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DaniiVivass dope! Sounds like it'll be a fun adventure ??
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @mmdk17: Close, but not close enough.! 
Now its time to drink a beer or five to end this season. Soon a new adventure will start.! #DKis…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@DrDreaaaa @amybbylove I agree. Do it! Worth the adventure.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	definatly just watched 3 hours worth of adventure time
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#Android CastleAbra Studios announces new adventure game CastleAbra. Coming this summer http://t.co/yG2ibeH241
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure Time button designs R2 are done. Posting tomorrow with special new prices~
</tweet>
<tweet>
	COLTYN SAFFORD ADVENTURE “@JosshYoung: all I want is a cool camera and a bag of doobies. then you can set me free into the wilderness. bye.”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @ednition: Don't you wish you were part of the adventure and not just reading it?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I need one more adventure, Murs and 9th.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#iPhone CastleAbra Studios announces new adventure game CastleAbra. Coming this summer http://t.co/yG2ibeH241
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Radiator Springs - the highlight of our day in California Adventure! Tip: Skip the ridiculous fast… http://t.co/AoEUbiRTWr
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is an adventure, dare it.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Elmo Storybooks, Activity Books, Adventure Cards AND Backpack only $7.95!

Grab This Awesome Deal >>> http://t.co/ihdeDeF7Xw
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Its one in the morning... Maybe I should get some sleep lol Going to Adventure Zone tmrw :)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@Moodyshittink actually it's adventure time come on grab your friend i win
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I liked a @YouTube video from @ldshadowlady http://t.co/SArQDbKUxD The Trust Game Adventure Map
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Trust Game Adventure Map: http://t.co/f9KHuya9xE via @youtube
</tweet>
<tweet>
	If you like A Curse from Heaven then you must love a good adventure http://t.co/oSToW1KVCm
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@League_Elise He is joining me on a adventure.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	See you later baby!! @alicemjhill go and have the most amazing adventure ???? xxx
</tweet>
<tweet>
	need more adventure during the day...
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I wanna go on an adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Watch,The Adventure of Merlin.           @Diva Universal 11.35 PM
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @3rdwashscouts: Fantastic night for a walk as we get ready for an expedition #iscout #outdoors #adventure http://t.co/HfciGF2xWR
</tweet>
<tweet>
	After tomorrow I have 3 days off, lets adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	go on an adventure with me
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Raaiq17: Keeen for an adventure to a far away land where no one knows me #LetsGetLost
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is an adventure, and I like the way mine is starting out. ? #content
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What I wouldn't give for some adventure I should have been a flight attendant or a cruise director for a line that's not carnival
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @melissa_munley: I need to adventure
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure time at an abandoned school *.*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Scooby Doo , Adventure Time , And Justice League And Fish Hooks My Favorite Cartoons Fuck The Rest
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My recent piece on the Elephanta Caves, a mid-sea adventure from Mumbai. http://t.co/H91h4rjoBN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@SLVLearn @RADower Yayyy!! What great adventure that looks like! Oh, wait, I'm on it too. Congratulations, Ruth, top marks.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PapiKathi: Gonna get a one way ticket and won't be coming back for long time. I just want adventure and less ignorant people in my life…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Anybody like Adventure time. Tweet Minecraft Xbox and tell them to put a Adventure Time skin pack in. It needs to be noticed :D thankyou
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Finn in Adventure Time is so horny.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Adventure Time time!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I wanna go on an adventure.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @staceynutt2: Had a wonderful adventure at the park:)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	SHOPPING ADVENTURE: Bear Creek a respite from stress: Don't mistake Bear Creek Herbary for an herb farm. It is... http://t.co/hU5uZXxLdH
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @shelby_ness: I want to go on adventure but everyone is passed out.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Keeen for an adventure to a far away land where no one knows me #LetsGetLost
</tweet>
