<tweet>
	for Free Tickets to Uptown Comedy Clubs Sunday 8:00pm Show Go to http://t.co/JQU1Medai5 And Enter PromoCode: TWITTER
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#TheOffice was awesome. My favorite comedy series ever. Excellent casting, directing, writing, editing, & acting. I'ma cry Thursday LOL
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Kristianthony_: #onlyinmoval will you have your TL full of racist tweets that are comedy af. LOL.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	black adder, Monty python, with-nail and I, the life of Brian, the holy grail. All classics comedy is rarely this funny anymore!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The surprisingly subversive album that changed stand-up comedy forever http://t.co/Pm2RMeug4S
</tweet>
<tweet>
	This is comedy lol ?????
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I do not like vulgar comedy......
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OhMrWonka: My life is like a romantic comedy except there's no romance and it's just me laughing at my own jokes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Australian comedian Celia Pacquola will perform in Luxembourg http://t.co/GsCLlt8fZ9
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Bobby comedy tho
</tweet>
<tweet>
	broda mi!! thanks RT @why_jay: @ola_micah happy birthday and many more years in the comedy industry
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Kristianthony_: #onlyinmoval will you have your TL full of racist tweets that are comedy af. LOL.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Me & my brutha was rollin the other night at his house watching that white dude on that comedy shown
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The best dog gifs of all time. Ever. Ever. Ever, Ever. http://t.co/J6VHo7NRmf
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Lee Evans signed items in Comedy Gala charity auction for @GreatOrmondSt @LeeEvansTour @LeeEvansNews @offthekerb http://t.co/FvR7R9pOoN
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Being A Google Intern Is So Funny, Hollywood Made It Into A Comedy. #fb http://t.co/wneXzbYkox
</tweet>
<tweet>
	For Free Tickets to the Best Comedy Show: The 8:00pm Show @ Uptown Txt Full Names to 678-223-3699 Now! http://t.co/xil9BACKnd
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OhMrWonka: My life is like a romantic comedy except there's no romance and it's just me laughing at my own jokes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@juijuijuijui tadi malem nonton stand up comedy ga seru bgt kalo ga ada lo bang :D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheLamadrid: These tweets are comedy if you get offended you're a communist.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My life is like a romantic comedy except there's no romance and it's just me laughing at my own jokes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	What kind of movies do you like? — Comedy or drama. Mostly feel good movies or classics. Whatever is good... http://t.co/zwcw8c4n1n
</tweet>
<tweet>
	See Comedian Corey Holcomb Live This sunday Uptown Comedy Club! For Your FREE Tickets Call 678-223-3699 Now! http://t.co/0nCTK1iWdr
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I have my window open, there's a lady out there with an horrific laugh...and she's watching a comedy...fuck
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I need to drop a comedy mix-tape
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Hey @surefirelogos followers, follow my comedy twitter at @jomazzcomedy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Kristianthony_: #onlyinmoval will you have your TL full of racist tweets that are comedy af. LOL.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@NatalieStronge we so should have gotten tickets to go to the comedy thing this year !
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @catlclark: Just seen the @danisnotonfire and @RealDMitchell YouTube Comedy Week advert on TV! So proud!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@y2james_ its bo burnhams comedy central special. You should watch it he's hilarious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Come see Comedian Corey Holcomb Live sunday @ Uptown Comedy Club RSVP For FREE Entry Txt Names to 678-223-3699 Now! http://t.co/s6vmNxut6h
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Stand up comedy >
</tweet>
<tweet>
	See Funny Comedian Corey Holcomb this sunday @Uptown Comedy Club! For Your FREE Tickets Call 678-223-3699 Now! http://t.co/xil9BACKnd
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @TheLamadrid: These tweets are comedy if you get offended you're a communist.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@FTIIndia #MyFamilySolution a stand up comedy night at home. 
Where members mimic each other! 
It'll be hilarious. :D
</tweet>
<tweet>
	“@TheLamadrid: These tweets are comedy if you get offended you're a communist.”
</tweet>
<tweet>
	UK's top comedians and entertainers in Comedy Gala charity auction for @GreatOrmondSt @clbleakley @eBayforCharity http://t.co/4PKg46MrnM
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Life is a tragedy for those who feel, and a comedy for those who think.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@sumona24 Haha now I can watch comedy circus again..Hope you are paired with Kapil..my all time-favourites..you look gorgeous as always.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @adornmelea: Twitter to go tonight was comedy all bc of kenia luv u made my night ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @The12Signs: If you live with #Sagittarius, they'll be your endless source of comedy.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	just finished god bless america, Awesome dark comedy on the sad truth of modern culture, A+
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@PaulKagame It is nice to meet you. Have you ever thought of doing a romantic musical comedy (movie) Rwanda style to boost tourism?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#onlyinmoval will you have your TL full of racist tweets that are comedy af. LOL.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @nicepeter: I’m spending the week getting ready to perform a rap battle live on youtube’s comedy week.  Can you guess which one we’re do…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @Tweets4Pay: Passive aggression is the worst way to express yourself, but at least it's hilarious for us! http://t.co/5J9iQJPAWA via @To…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Twitter to go tonight was comedy all bc of kenia luv u made my night ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	These tweets are comedy if you get offended you're a communist.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@KateHardie2 ahem. I woke up and said 'Think ill need the ark today' !!!! Hahahahaha. Before you ask, no I've had no comedy training.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Tati threw some coater at Chelsy and I threw my cup at her. Lmfaooo. That mess was COMEDY
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@phanfeels where?:o doing standup comedy yes?
</tweet>
