<tweet>
	My chemical romance. \m/
</tweet>
<tweet>
	We fcked a hoe together. Now that's romance. ?
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Carmine Cafe, was the Bill Brauer painting of my notion of romance. I could never tell, from their stance, the nature of their dance.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @emarxbooks: "When all hope is lost, one vampire will fight unto death for his forbidden love." #Paranormal #Romance 4.7 stars/23 http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @SusanAylworth: Cool spring evenings need warm, cozy reads. FREE 1st-of-a-series #romance recommended by Debbie Macomber. #ASMSG. http:/…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Welcome to the Black Parade - My Chemical Romance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I Wana Go To Venice.. Pure Romance?:)!! Riyaaz Take Me There:'(!!!!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Elizabeth Ashley~ In a great romance each person plays a part the other really likes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OhMrWonka: My life is like a romantic comedy except there's no romance and it's just me laughing at my own jokes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @XSTROLOGY: #Libra loves a little romance. You can never go wrong with flowers.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	GAGA u la la la la la la . WANT YOUR BAD ROMANCE ;)
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @XSTROLOGY: #Libra loves a little romance. You can never go wrong with flowers.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	The Ron Swanson Guide To Romance Leads The Daily Links http://t.co/tsPPQQXjPg
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @LeislLeighton: Just looked at Destiny Romance website to see my cover and bio up there. http://t.co/hHhVmys3LE http://t.co/PVEwCyemB4
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @OhMrWonka: My life is like a romantic comedy except there's no romance and it's just me laughing at my own jokes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Yeaa Family Guy ma shit
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"@ShakzE72: What if every band had the word gays in them?Sleeping with gays, Green gays,Forever the gays,One direction,My gay romance."
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@amitsawhney @_karanmehra #YRKKH is d best serial.Emotion,love,respect,fun,romance everything r in this serial.Full Entertainment packege
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My life is like a romantic comedy except there's no romance and it's just me laughing at my own jokes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @miikkkaaaa: Um a romance book that has a wreck this journal in it what
</tweet>
<tweet>
	@katrinakaif4444 just imagine srk in mission impossible 1 he can do it very well srk is that person who can do both action and romance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#follow to #download Greek Alexander Romance @RepairGuides
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i dont want romance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Sad romance
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Another beautiful old-fashioned procedural masquerading as tech. Romance. http://t.co/NyRPTZR19L via @Wired
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Um a romance book that has a wreck this journal in it what
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PiscesAreUs: We know #Pisces are a handful but that also comes with passion, romance and a storybook relationship.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @KarenRoseBooks: Live in Atlanta?  Planning to go to the Romance Writers of America convention in July?  Check out this link to... http:…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	A cute romance. Please. ???
</tweet>
<tweet>
	i make a short-romance story on my essay hahahahahhahahahaha
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @whatdidKEITHsay: "You are the most romance novel bitch I've ever met in my life!!" Lmao #done
</tweet>
<tweet>
	once i received roses and was so embarrassed that i hid them in my closet for months until they were black and fuzzy with mold *~RoMaNcE~*
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @RarestFacts: Women who read romance novels have sex twice as often as those who don't.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Live in Atlanta?  Planning to go to the Romance Writers of America convention in July?  Check out this link to... http://t.co/UyMJPlnnFJ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @tomlins0nkisses: rt if you ship larry as a romance, fave if you ship as a bromance. im really curious
</tweet>
<tweet>
	"You are the most romance novel bitch I've ever met in my life!!" Lmao #done
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @dreramos12: Every Disney and romance movie ruins love for girls! Why get our hopes up!? It doesn't happen that way!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	For The Love Of Money- Will the super success of Aashiqui 2 now turn romance into a bankable genre once again? http://t.co/WxWznSNOSy
</tweet>
<tweet>
	You carried romance in the palm of your hand.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	They say the best part of wakin up is breakfast after a nut and that's romance lmao
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I can't believe how much I loved My Chemical Romance ? 
#SoWeird
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PiscesAreUs: We know #Pisces are a handful but that also comes with passion, romance and a storybook relationship.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My life is a romantic comedy minus the romance just me laughing at my own jokes.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Final word count for yesterday's efforts on The Exhibition, 4.5K. I'll take it!
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @PiscesTerms: We know #Pisces are a handful but that also comes with passion, romance and a storybook relationship.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	*np My Chemical Romance - I Don't Love You
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Suka film bergenre romance dan drama #stellafact
</tweet>
<tweet>
	My Chemical Romance....
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Unconditional love? It exists. Love for Beer. We let you romance your beer under the starlit sky! #PerfectDate.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	#np My Chemical Romance - Famous Last Words
</tweet>
<tweet>
	30 Seconds To Mars - A Beautiful Lie.
</tweet>
<tweet>
	[ TAO X SUHO X KRIS ] Give me a smile http://t.co/ArdzBsgNVQ
</tweet>
<tweet>
	RT @HaleyHarden6: I'm such a hopeless romantic, it's fucking ridiculous. I really need to stop watching romance movies but I can't help it?…
</tweet>
<tweet>
	WHAT I LIKE ABOUT YOU~
You really know how to dance~
You go up down, turn around~ talk about true romance~
 ohoh ohohoho~
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Too many brothers wanna be lovers but dont know what romance is
</tweet>
<tweet>
	Moms all ill&tired in bed. All she can hear is My Chemical Romance and me falling into my wall.. Oops
</tweet>
<tweet>
	I still remember your physics romance <3 heheheh @TudioHiong
</tweet>
